I'm going to Tokyo!
I'm going to Tokyo.
I'll become a different Banri and start over.
Thank you.
Huh?
Thanks to you, I feel like I've suddenly become free.
Oh, okay.
That's great.
Let me do something to thank you.
I know!
If I see your friend at the hospital, I'll give him a message.
A message?
I promise I'll tell him.
So you shouldn't come here alone anymore.
It's dangerous.
Your signal will reach him eventually.
I'll make sure it does.
My signal...
It's too late for my signal to reach him.
I didn't make it in time.
Huh?
There's nothing I can do anymore.
The only way I can think is that
if I'd made it in time,
that wouldn't have happened to him.
What's wrong?
If I'd made it in time...
I would've held his hand tight
and never let go!
Never!
Sorry.
I'm going now.
Hey, what's your message?
Tell him, "You can do it."
Oh...
I'm not supposed to say that kind of thing.
Again? Why do I keep having that dream?
What...
did Linda say to me then?
Summer Has Come
Ah, if I met you in my dream, would I be able to say it?
aa yume no naka de aetara yueru ka na
The sorrows alone scatter down from the sky
nee kanashimi dake sora kara maiochite
That voice torments you to this day
sonna koe ga kimi wo ima de mo kurushimete
Even when I put my hand on yours, I can't get over these feelings
soba de te wo kasanetemo kono omoi wa kienai kedo
When our eyes meet, even if you don't say what you mean
futari me wo awasetara hontou no koto ienakutemo
Your words shine my world brighter than anyone else's
kimi no kotoba dare yori mo sekai wo terashiteru
Next to me, you say "Goodbye" when you mean "I love you"
tonari de kimi wa sayonara wa aishiteru tte sou iu no
I can't be honest
sunao ni narenai
When I'm singing about my loneliness alone
watashi dake kodoku wo utatte mo
I can't smile
egao ni narenai
If you say "Thanks" to mean "I'm in love with you"
arigato wa koi shiteru tte sou iu no
This is love at the end of the world
ai no world's end
The time came for our first event of summer vacation.
It's the Awa dance festival
the Festival Club is participating in.
Other universities and Awa dance
preservation societies are here as well.
There they are.
It's so hot.
Wow, they look like girls!
You're right!
There are girls in our club!
Oh, shut up.
It's so hot. Fan...
It's so hot.
I'm amazed you guys can hang around here.
The building's air conditioned, and it feels great inside.
We let you use that space so you could change.
Oh, right.
Sorry.
Huh?
We match.
Yeah, that's right.
Today I'm a beautiful woman dressed as a man.
That's great!
You're so handsome!
Thanks.
I'm so handsome today.
Linda-senpai, you really do look better than me.
You can tell I'm not used to these clothes.
Don't worry. It's a battle of charm.
Anyway...
your girlfriend's having a problem.
A problem?
Kouko...
What a hunk of junk.
She's a modern-day Yaoya Oshichi.
Isn't this a job for her boyfriend?
Right.
What's wrong?
Get it together.
Banri...
What's wrong?
Is it heat stroke?
No, that's not it.
She had lots of energy until a minute ago.
Th-They're right.
I'm just n-nervous.
Wh-What?
I can't do it!
I'm going to the bathroom again!
Sh-She's walking funny.
Kouko!
Linda-senpai.
You're fine.
You've already been to the
bathroom about thirty times.
N-Now that you mention it, that's true.
Your bladder's empty.
There's nothing in there.
Listen to me. Calm down and think carefully.
Your urge to pee...
My urge to pee...
...is a phantom urge.
...is a phantom urge!
Linda-senpai!
There, there.
Oh, my.
Come on, over here.
We still have time.
Try to calm down, okay?
She's even more of a hunk of junk than I imagined.
Looks like she's out of oil.
Let's put on your lipstick, okay?
Come on, RoboGirl!
You can do it!
Fight!
No help for it.
Let's go.
Goodbye, RoboGirl.
I won't forget how funny you were.
Wait.
Adieu, RoboGirl-chan.
Hey...
We'll meet again.
No, no, no!
Don't give up!
You'd leave one of our own behind?
We don't have a choice, I guess.
Kosshi-senpai, hasn't the time come to teach the first years about that ?
"That," huh?
You're right.
We're going to do that ?
Looks like we have no choice.
She's right.
It's our only hope.
Huh?
Wh-What do you mean?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Huh?
What?
What's going on?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Ahoy, ahoy, ahoy, ahoy.
Together, now!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Banri!
N-No!
Someone help me!
Come on!
Kouko!
RoboGirl!
Stop!
I can't do it!
There's no way I can do that!
I can't!
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey!
All right!
Let's go to our first festival!
Yeah!
Good work, guys.
Good work, everyone!
You're dismissed for today.
There's a fireworks show later at the riverbank near here.
Feel free to attend.
All right!
Changing's too much trouble.
Let's go like this.
Let's at least change into sneakers.
Kouko, Tada Banri.
The next time we meet will be at camp.
Yeah.
Good work today.
Thank you for everything.
Linda-senpai was wonderful.
You danced well too.
Yeah.
I'm a ghost again.
My feelings for Linda still remain in Banri's heart,
but...
Until now, I've thought of him as my younger twin.
Even if he didn't notice me,
I thought he respected the
feelings I'd always nurtured.
But he abandoned me.
Kouko, have you been to a fireworks show before?
Yeah, I have.
Even though he still has feelings for Linda,
Really?
The booming explosions are amazing.
he's forced himself to pretend there's nothing.
Really?
He rejected the feelings I had to leave behind in this world.
I'll curse you.
I'll become an evil spirit and make you unhappy.
Prepare yourself.
What's this?
It suddenly started raining!
We've gotta hurry up and find shelter!
Banri, I'm scared!
Canceled?
Yeah.
The seminar house we got for our camp is closed for repairs.
I see.
See you in September.
Later.
You've gotta be kidding.
It's been like this since summer vacation started.
The fireworks display was canceled,
I missed the film showing,
and Yana-san suddenly canceled our plans to hang out.
On top of that, it's so hot every day.
Guess who?
It's me!
Hey, my lover.
Were you surprised?
You were, weren't you?
Yes, I'm a surprising woman.
You took the stairs?
Yes, I sprinted up them.
Why?
So I could surprise you as you came to meet me.
You were surprised, weren't you?
And that's...
the spice...
of love!
Because of that, I ended up like this.
It's okay.
I'll make you a curried yakisoba that's so delicious,
it'll blow your pain away.
Huh?
Yakisoba?
I bought ingredients,
and I'm ready to go.
Look forward to it.
Ta-da!
Great! That's great!
Seriously great!
It looks fantastic on you!
Come on, you're exaggerating.
I bet you wear that whenever you cook at home!
Huh?
Well, yeah, I do.
Are you serious?
You're so feminine!
You really are a surprising girl!
I love it! Love it!
Well, then.
What should I do?
I'll help you with whatever!
You can't do that!
Wh-Why not?
You don't have to help me.
I want to make it for you.
It's a girl thing, okay?
So please, just sit.
Oh...
Okay.
I thought I might need this.
I'm glad I brought it.
Huh?
Why do I have to wear this?
No reason.
Okay, put your hands here.
If you take them out, it's game over.
I'm kind of scared.
By the way, Banri, do you know about that man?
What man?
In a snowy village,
there's a middle-aged man living an ecological, healthy,
and sustainable life with his mother.
And you see...
that man is having sexual relations with a bird.
Sexual...
But that's not the important part.
What's important is the sad truth that the man is a peeping Tom.
What are you talking about?
The bird is chirping suspiciously— chirp, chirp, chirp—
and acting strangely behind the door.
The man can't contain his curiosity, and in the end, he commits the crime.
Because of that,
his strange but happy life with the bird comes to an end.
Are you talking about the crane wife?
Put simply, yes.
In other words, um, it means...
Don't watch you while you cook?
Right!
What a terrible storyteller.
In any case, you'll make me really nervous if you watch.
So stay right there.
Please! Please! Please!
Well, if you insist...
Good! Face the other way and don't move.
I'll do my very best.
My curried yakisoba will be delicious.
By the way, Banri, did you hear that our trip was canceled?
Yeah, just now.
It's too bad, isn't it?
I thought we could reminisce about the time we got lost in those mountains.
I don't think that was such a great memory.
Huh?
Well, camp or no camp, we'll always be together.
Time to wash some vegetables.
Time to cut some vegetables and meat.
Time to sauté some vegetables and meat.
Time to add the noodles.
Now I'll season them and quickly finish them off like I always do.
It's almost ready.
Look forward to—
K-Kouko?
It'll burn.
Were you watching?
This isn't what you think it is, Banri.
What is it, then?
A joke!
A joke?!
It's my best joke!
Air yakisoba!
Air yakisoba?!
Aren't you surprised?
Laugh, Banri!
Try laughing!
This is...
the spice...
of love too!
I really meant to make it myself, at first.
But while practicing at home,
I started getting nervous,
and I couldn't even hold a knife properly.
You're so weak under pressure.
So then our maid saw me and started making it herself.
She said, "You're useless! Give me that."
I'm amazed she called her
employer's daughter "useless."
She has a foul mouth, but she's really nice.
She even lent me this apron.
Hey, can we talk a little more?
Maybe I'll attend a proper cooking school.
You don't need to do that.
Normal's fine.
Normal's not good enough.
I want to make you think, "She's awesome! Her feminine charm is through the roof!"
This summer vacation,
maybe I'll throw myself into the culinary tiger's den and train.
Culinary tiger's den?
Maybe I'll do that...
and cancel my family vacation.
Barcelona, right?
A long vacation sounds nice.
But... Banri, you'll...
Don't worry about me.
If you spent it with me, you'd have a boring summer just killing time.
I wish we could be together the whole time too, but...
Really?
Really.
Of course I do.
I see.
L-Let's go.
Y-Yeah.
Hey, Banri, you're forgetting something.
Sorry! Thanks.
"Don't go to Barcelona. Stay with me."
I can't tell her to do that.
You can't complain if she abandons you eventually.
Someday a better man will appear, and...
Goodbye, Banri.
Find someone who can make you delicious curried yakisoba.
Kouko!
I'm not done yet.
I'll make you even unhappier.
What was that voice?
No, no, that's not what I'm getting at
chigau yo mou chigau tte ba
Ah, you still haven't noticed
aa mada kizukanai no ne
Since a couple of hours ago
nisanjikan mo mae kara
I've been dying to grab onto your arm
sono ude ni furetai no ni
I have so many pent-up feelings that I want to let out
sakebitai kimochi wa hora komaru hodo aru no ni
But why? Why can't you take a hint?
dou shite dou shite chitto mo aa satotte kurenai no
Hey
nee
Are you really, really in love with me?
hontou ni hontou ni watashi ni koi shiteru
You can skip the sweet talk
kosobayui kotoba wa iranai
Love me semipermanently
han'eikyuuteki ni aishite yo
I don't care about five thousand years in the future
gosennen go nado kyoumi wa nai
My life's not endless
watashi endoresu de wa nai no
I'll die someday
itsuka wa shinu no yo
Telling me you'll love me forever
eien ni aishiteru yo nante
Won't make me happy
iwarete mo ureshikunai
For now just focus on
mazu wa watashi wo shinu made
Loving me until we die
ai suru koto dake wo kangaete
Ladies Talk
Amazing!
That's amazing, Kouko!
I love your air yakisoba!
No! Stop! Forget about that!
Huh?
I want it to be our secret. It's a girl thing!
This is... the spice... of love!
I see...