No!
It's really not like that!
This isn't what I meant to do!
I thought it was normal for a girlfriend to check her boyfriend's mail while he's away.
But once I got to his apartment, I wanted to go inside.
Stupid, stupid, stupid Banri!
But I love, love, love you!
Kiss me!
Oh, it smells like Banri.
Exorcist!
My Hometown
Ah, if I met you in my dream, would I be able to say it?
aa yume no naka de aetara yueru ka na
The sorrows alone scatter down from the sky
nee kanashimi dake sora kara maiochite
That voice torments you to this day
sonna koe ga kimi wo ima de mo kurushimete
Even when I put my hand on yours, I can't get over these feelings
soba de te wo kasanetemo kono omoi wa kienai kedo
When our eyes meet, even if you don't say what you mean
futari me wo awasetara hontou no koto ienakutemo
Your words shine my world brighter than anyone else's
kimi no kotoba dare yori mo sekai wo terashiteru
Next to me, you say "Goodbye" when you mean "I love you"
tonari de kimi wa sayonara wa aishiteru tte sou iu no
I can't be honest
sunao ni narenai
When I'm singing about my loneliness alone
watashi dake kodoku wo utatte mo
I can't smile
egao ni narenai
If you say "Thanks" to mean "I'm in love with you"
arigato wa koi shiteru tte sou iu no
This is love at the end of the world
ai no world's end
Are you sure you're not crazy?
I heard noises next door even though my neighbor's away, so I came to check it out.
I-I'm sorry for making you worry.
But that thing.
The exorcist.
I think that's pretty good.
Why don't you perform that at our concert?
What?
The theme is "fear."
Fear...
We want to perform something fresh and striking that will shock the audience.
I wasn't sure what to do,
but I found something that might work.
No, no, no! I couldn't!
I'm really not...
Just make about five laps around the stage in that pose.
I can't!
I can only move about five centimeters.
I'm still just a novice.
I see.
Nana-senpai!
Wh-What are you—
Please!
Don't tell Banri I sneaked into his room and did the exorcist in fit of passion!
Please! Please!
I... I can't breathe... s-seriously...
I'll do anything to help, other than the exorcist!
Okay? Okay? Okay?
I'm so glad you understand.
You said you'd do anything besides the exorcist, right?
Huh? Oh, yes.
Okay, then.
I'm going shopping.
You stay here.
Um...
Nana-senpai?
Where did she go?
Huh? Wh-What is that?
Yo! I know you're in there, bitch!
Why do you have a knife stuck in your stomach?
Why is your white suit soaked in bright red blood?
Tell me, sir.
Tell me...
Mister Yakuza Man.
I ended up like this because you ran off with the money!
Get the hell out here!
I'll kill you, too!
What on Earth did Nana-senpai do?!
Where are you hiding?!
In here?!
Exorcist!
Take this!
Kouko attack!
Huh?
What'd'ya think?
What?
Were you scared?
Y-Yes.
I'll be including this performance in the show, then.
The yakuza will crash the concert.
By the way, this guy's Tomoyasu.
He plays bass in our band.
You're saying this was all an act?
You said you'd do anything to help.
So I had you be my guinea pig.
And you moved fine while doing your exorcist.
Why don't you try doing it onstage?
I can't take it anymore!
Banri, come home soon!
Oh, my.
Linda-chan.
It's good to see you again.
You've changed so much.
You always used to keep your hair long.
I thought it was time for a change.
Banri, Linda-chan's here!
I heard you're attending the same university.
I was surprised to hear you two are hanging out again.
I was surprised too.
I ran into him on the day of the entrance ceremony.
Thanks for coming.
Banri!
You're doing well!
You haven't changed at all!
I'm so glad!
Well... um...
Should I get some bananas?
I have some in the fridge.
Oh, it's fine.
Don't worry about him.
Come on. That's annoying.
But...
Sorry, Banri.
This is my older brother.
You can call him "Bro" if you want.
Come on, cut it out, you gorilla!
I'm not a gorilla!
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
When I saw your face, these feelings came bubbling up!
Anyway, Banri, how you doing?
What?
Just tell him you're doing great.
Y-Yeah. I'm doing great!
I see!
All right.
Well, let's go to the reunion, okay?
What is that?
It's a mirror Kouko gave me.
It's kind of a protective charm.
You're nervous.
A little.
Actually, kind of a lot.
Freaking out now won't do you any good.
If anything happens, I'll help you.
It'll be fine.
Thank you.
Wh-What?
You really are like a senior and junior.
It's like I'm hearing a club party skit.
It's not funny!
Oh, right, Banri.
Don't use formal language today.
We're classmates of the same age, you know.
What?
If you use formal language, I'll fine you 500 yen!
What?!
High School
Okay, let's go.
I'm here.
I'm finally here.
Banri?
I'm kind of scared.
What should I do?
What are you so afraid of?
Just everything!
Banri...
I'm not the Tada Banri everyone wants to see.
I don't have my memories.
I don't know who anyone is!
They'll definitely wonder who the hell I am!
Oh, come on.
Banri, close your eyes.
Huh?
Like this?
I'll walk you there like this.
Keep your eyes closed.
Okay, we're moving forward.
O-Okay.
Watch your step.
Linda, listen...
Hm?
I know I've told you before, but...
Thank you. Thank you so, so much.
You've done so much for me.
And not just today.
And... I'm sorry for causing you trouble all this time.
I said before that I wanted to pretend the past never happened, but I regret that.
I don't know why I couldn't be happy, even though we got to meet again.
I came here today because I want to change who I am.
You think I can change?
Linda?
Are you listening?
Oh... what?
You are Linda, right?
What?!
Oops!
Busted.
Um, it's been a while.
You're...
an old dude!
An old...
I'm your classmate.
I'm not an old man.
Sorry, sorry.
This is Koichiro.
He's your classmate.
I saw you on the way to the meeting place.
I thought, "Oh! It's Tada Banri!" I couldn't help myself.
Oh! Tada Banri!
It's Banri!
Isn't that Banri?
It's been way too long!
Banri!
Tada Banri!
Whoa, it's really Banri!
You haven't changed at all!
Yeah!
Except you're taller!
I heard you're at the same university as Linda.
So you guys stayed friends even after graduation, huh?
Well... um... that is...
Banri
Here, Banri.
Put this on.
Huh?
We're going to play dodgeball.
During the fall sports festival of our third year,
our class split into red and blue teams and played dodgeball.
I pegged you with the ball,
but you insisted the ball hit your face and got to stay in.
Out!
That allowed your team to make a comeback,
so your red team won, and my blue team lost.
But I definitely didn't hit you in the face.
So today we're going to settle the score.
You jerk!
Prepare yourself, Banri!
Out.
That was dirty, Linda!
I thought you were aiming for Banri!
Shut up!
That play took brains!
Banri, the rest is up to you.
G-Got it!
Go, Banri!
Wipe the floor with Linda!
Settle this two-year-old score!
Okay! I'm playing for real now!
Prepare yourselves!
H-Hold on, Banri.
It's me.
I'm your senior from the Festival Club.
Did you forget you owe me for looking out for you?
Who's the one who just said she'd fine me 500 yen for using formal language?
Well, we should really treasure our senior-junior relationship, after all!
Shut up!
You're just Linda!
Whoa, there!
Gotcha, moron!
What?!
Face ball.
Safe.
Hey, Linda...
Are you okay?
Banri...
This is how you use the face rule.
There's a baby
inside me!
What?! You have a kid?
Yeah, and the father is...
Huh? What?
Not... me?
Of course not.
Her husband's that guy.
You've been dating since middle school, right?
When did you get married?
Um, this time last year, I think.
It's been a while, Banri!
Are you feeling better now?
We've been together since middle school.
Does this face ring any bells?
Sorry.
I really don't remember anything.
Oh, it's fine.
Don't apologize.
Just getting to see you again is enough.
Well, you haven't changed at all.
I'm relieved.
Your hair has changed, though.
It wasn't like this before?
He changed his look after graduation.
Speaking of hair, yours was terrible at one point.
You suddenly said you were gonna grow it out.
Yeah, yeah.
You did it because you wanted to ask a girl about borrowing her hair tie.
What? For that reason?
Oh, what's up? Telling stories of Banri's past?
I know one too.
You used up all your erasers just so you could ask a girl about borrowing her eraser.
~Growl~
You went on a diet so you could ask a girl if she could tell you'd lost weight.
H-Hold on!
You're... kidding, right?
Unfortunately, Banri, they're all true.
Yeah. We speak no lies.
And this is just the tip of the iceberg.
I-I was even more hopeless than I thought.
Sensei!
Hey.
It's been a while, guys.
Is Tada Banri here?
Yes, I'm here.
I'm glad you could come today.
You always cry when you're not with everyone else.
What? Cry?
I do?
He does, right?
Yeah, he does.
Yeah, he cries.
He cries a lot.
Yup, yup.
You can't be serious.
I'm not a kid.
No, you really do cry.
Whoa...
Sensei, I want a picture with you!
Me, too! Me, too!
I'd like one too, please!
Me too.
Oh, really? Sure thing.
Let's go, Banri.
Come on, Banri.
It's your chance to get your picture taken with girls.
All right!
It was worth coming home so I could have my picture taken with girls!
Linda!
Let's take one together.
Okay.
You know those sport singlets?
The ones with our names on them.
Yeah.
Everyone wore them for my sake, using dodgeball as an excuse, didn't they?
I guess they all tried to think of things they could do for you.
But I'm impressed you decided to come.
Maybe Kouko-chan's accident the other day influenced you.
Yeah, it did.
The good... the bad... the unexpected accidents.
All kinds of things happen in life.
There are things you can't avoid, even if you don't like them.
Yeah.
I decided I don't want to be controlled by what happened to me.
I want to live.
I just want to be alive.
I'm living now, right here.
I'm living because I want be alive.
Are you thinking, "What is he saying?"
I'm thinking, "He finally said it."
Until now, you've seemed like a reluctant survivor.
It made me pretty mad.
You're kidding.
It's true.
"Then why'd you come back, you jerk?!"
I felt that way sometimes.
I was glad to see you again.
But I was just a nuisance to you.
You wanted to pretend the past hadn't happened.
You were cautious around me.
I had no idea what I should do.
But you've chosen to be yourself.
Your past self is part of that.
Right?
That's right.
I am who I am.
It's all me.
Actually, if I hadn't met you,
I might not be around right now.
What?
During the accident, just before we crashed,
I heard a voice telling me to "just press on."
It made me reflexively press the brakes.
That voice saved me.
Your message from back then reached me.
I see.
So there was meaning in our meeting again.
We're a senior and junior in the same club,
you have a girlfriend named Kouko-chan, and I...
Well, it doesn't matter.
In any case, there's nothing wrong with the way we are now.
It may even be the best!
Yeah. I agree.
It's the best.
Could you wait here?
I'm going to take a picture of the bridge.
What? Now?
I want to show Kouko!
I'm fine now.
Leave me.
Are my memories returning?
No, no, that's not what I'm getting at
chigau yo mou chigau tte ba
Ah, you still haven't noticed
aa mada kizukanai no ne
Since a couple of hours ago
nisanjikan mo mae kara
I've been dying to grab onto your arm
sono ude ni furetai no ni
I have so many pent-up feelings that I want to let out
sakebitai kimochi wa hora komaru hodo aru no ni
But why? Why can't you take a hint?
dou shite dou shite chitto mo aa satotte kurenai no
Hey
nee
Are you really, really in love with me?
hontou ni hontou ni watashi ni koi shiteru
You can skip the sweet talk
kosobayui kotoba wa iranai
Love me semipermanently
han'eikyuuteki ni aishite yo
I don't care about five thousand years in the future
gosennen go nado kyoumi wa nai
My life's not endless
watashi endoresu de wa nai no
I'll die someday
itsuka wa shinu no yo
Telling me you'll love me forever
eien ni aishiteru yo nante
Won't make me happy
iwarete mo ureshikunai
For now just focus on
mazu wa watashi wo shinu made
Loving me until we die
ai suru koto dake wo kangaete
Night in Paris
Linda, you and your brother don't look anything alike.
Well, actually, he isn't my biological brother.
What?
One snowy morning,
he was standing in front of the zoo with a banana, and...