Hello? It's me.
Oh, 2D-kun.
What's up?
I heard you're lonely.
Huh?
Ladies Talk
Ah, if I met you in my dream, would I be able to say it?
aa yume no naka de aetara yueru ka na
The sorrows alone scatter down from the sky
nee kanashimi dake sora kara maiochite
That voice torments you to this day
sonna koe ga kimi wo ima de mo kurushimete
Even when I put my hand on yours, I can't get over these feelings
soba de te wo kasanetemo kono omoi wa kienai kedo
When our eyes meet, even if you don't say what you mean
futari me wo awasetara hontou no koto ienakutemo
Your words shine my world brighter than anyone else's
kimi no kotoba dare yori mo sekai wo terashiteru
Next to me, you say "Goodbye" when you mean "I love you"
tonari de kimi wa sayonara wa aishiteru tte sou iu no
I can't be honest
sunao ni narenai
When I'm singing about my loneliness alone
watashi dake kodoku wo utatte mo
I can't smile
egao ni narenai
If you say "Thanks" to mean "I'm in love with you"
arigato wa koi shiteru tte sou iu no
This is love at the end of the world
ai no world's end
Yana-san told me on the phone yesterday.
He said you've invited him to hang out several times,
but the timing's never right,
and he felt bad turning you down.
Is that why you called me?
Yeah. I thought we could hang out.
You're so nice.
Aren't you busy with work, though?
No, I have the day off.
Don't you have plans to see Kaga-san?
I wouldn't call them plans.
She comes to my place almost every day.
So if you come over, the three of us can hang out.
Should I call Yana-san?
I tried calling him earlier, but he's busy again today.
I see.
That's too bad.
We haven't hung out in ages.
I wish we could at least meet up.
You know, I've been thinking. Maybe he found a girlfriend!
What?
You mean like a romantic relationship?
Yeah.
He's been turning down our invitations since summer vacation started.
When I call him, he seems kind of flustered too.
If you're right, it must be...
Huh?
What are you doing, Kouko?
It sounded like you were on the phone, so I tried to sneak in.
Who were you talking to?
H-Hello?
Hello.
Oh, it's you, 2D-kun!
Good morning.
Huh?
Mitsuo has a girlfriend?
Is it Miss Ultrasonic?
You're kidding.
Yeah, we should definitely find out.
Find out?
It's all right.
I'm a professional.
I'm used to stalking Mitsuo.
Wait! What are you...
Now then, Banri!
Yes?
Today's going to be busy!
So that's Miss Ultrasonic's place?
Banri, I'm surprised you knew where this was.
I got her address before summer break,
so I could send her a summer greeting card.
Is Yana-san really going to come here?
He will if he's seeing Miss Ultrasonic.
Knowing Mitsuo,
he should be devoted enough to walk his girlfriend home after seeing her.
Mitsuo is busy today!
That means he has plans to go out with Miss Ultrasonic!
That means we'll catch him in the act if we wait here!
My logic is flawless!
But... isn't it too hot to be stalking someone today?
I'm already kinda bored.
Why don't we go somewhere and get some shaved ice?
That sounds good.
Shaved ice?
We can't do that.
Why not?
Isn't today a perfect day for shaved ice?
It'll make you need to use the bathroom.
Wow.
You really are a pro.
We can't get a good view from here.
Anyway, why is she carrying opera glasses around like it's normal?
That's just how she is.
Yipes!
What are you doing here?
Did you come to deliver your summer greeting card in person?
Ah, no, just...
It's summer break, so I thought I'd drop by unannounced for a visit.
What's with that?
You should've called me.
I'm free today.
I've been lazing around since this morning.
You're free?
You don't have plans?
You're not seeing anyone?
Not at all.
So I'm glad you came to hang out.
Huh?
Kaga-san?
What's she doing?
Oh, that's... um...
a comedy routine!
Kaga-san.
You! What are you doing here?
This is my house.
What am I doing?
I'm living here, I guess.
That's not what I meant.
We thought you were with Mitsuo.
What?
Me and Yana?
Why?
Actually, we thought Yana-san might have a girlfriend.
We thought if he was dating someone, it'd be you, so we came to check it out.
What? No way!
Not a chance!
I haven't seen Yana since summer break started.
Not even once?
Not even once.
Looks like you made a big mistake, 2D-kun.
It's my fault?
You're the one who was so sure Mitsuo would come here!
And you were the first one who said Mitsuo had a girlfriend.
Well, now that you're here, come on in.
Thanks for having us.
Kaga-san.
The moment you step over that threshold,
I'll officially recognize you as my friend.
Wha...
Tell me before I step over it!
If I'd known, I would've made myself stop,
even if an explosion was propelling me in!
Wow, Kaga-chan!
Your shoes are so cute!
If you call me that name in that tone again,
I'll self-destruct, expel my brain from inside my exploded skull, and become a local legend.
Huh?
They're such idiots.
My room's on the third floor.
You guys go on ahead.
Does Miss Ultrasonic's family actually live here?
Thanks for waiting.
Thanks.
You shouldn't have.
Miss Ultrasonic, are you all right?
Huh?
This place looks abandoned.
We're in the process of moving out.
I'm the last one left.
My dad's moving back home because of work.
My mom decided to go with him.
In other words, they left you here?
We're originally from Fukuoka.
I can't attend school from there.
So starting next month, I'll be living on my own.
I haven't found an apartment yet,
and I'm kind of worried.
I see.
So that's how it is.
Oka-chan... you've been through a lot.
Thank you!
Fukuoka's far away.
I'm jealous, though.
You get to live alone.
I guess.
I wanted to try living alone,
but now that I'm doing it,
I'm full of anxiety and fear.
Do you know where you're going to live?
Not at all.
I need to find a place soon,
and I want to save money too.
I was supposed to take the Okamera on a trip,
but this killed my plans.
I see.
That's sad.
The beach.
Huh?
Let's go!
You said you wanted to go, right?
Let's go with Oka-chan!
I'll bring a car.
You're right!
Let's do it! All of us together.
Miss Ultrasonic, do you have a swimsuit?
We're going to the beach.
M-My swimsuit should be around here somewhere.
When are we going?
I'll make proper plans!
Okay!
I'll invite Yana-san, and we'll all go together!
It's summer, after all!
This is the only summer we'll get this year!
I think I'm hungry.
Then let's get something to eat.
I'll show you where the Film Club gets food.
There's a place that's cheap but has good fried chicken.
I go there with the Film Club all the time.
Yeah, but we didn't have to come so close to the university for it, did we?
Now, now.
This will be one of our summer memories.
We might run into someone from the Film Club.
There it is.
And their fried chicken is great!
It's already open.
Yeah?
That was Yana and...
...Linda-senpai from the Festival Club, right?
What are those two doing together?
Huh? What?
Is Yana's girlfriend...
I thought Yana-san had unrequited feelings for Oka-chan.
Wh-What should we do?
Should we go to the same place?
Let's not.
I'm sure they have their reasons.
Let's leave them alone for now.
I agree with Miss Ultrasonic.
Let's just...
quietly watch over Mitsuo.
Yes?
Um, why are you dressed like that?
I'm engaging in espionage.
This is how I dress for stealth.
I think it makes you stand out even more.
Anyway, you'd better not tell anyone I came here today.
Why not?
Isn't it obvious?
I don't want anyone to think you and I are friends.
You're so shy.
Shy?!
As long as you're here, let's try to get along.
No! Way!
Oh, I have this.
Huh...
Anyway, did you figure anything out after that about Yana and Linda-senpai?
Nothing.
I haven't even seen them since then.
Why? Is it bothering you?
Not really, but...
Wait. This isn't the time for chit-chat.
We have an important mission today.
That's why I'm here.
Well?
This is my first choice.
S-Sure, why not?
But who shows up at someone's house and immediately strips?
I told you we'd be choosing swimsuits today.
Well?
Think this will charm Banri?
You want to charm him?
That's right.
I want to use the perfect swimsuit to make him fall completely in love.
I think he's already in love with you.
He's not!
I don't have nearly enough charm!
I feel like he's not even half-charmed yet!
What? Why?
I just do!
That's why you have to take this seriously.
I brought all the swimsuits I had at home.
What?
Why do I have to change into a swimsuit?
Because I don't want us to match.
If we do, you'll have to change.
Oh, this has suddenly become a lot of work.
Have you changed?
Yeah.
Here we go.
Ready and... go!
Weird!
It looks weird, Kaga-san!
It's too erotic!
I was going for a healthy look.
Sort of a Latin American island style...
No, no, no. We're in Japan.
Turn around.
A thong!
There's no way you can pull that off!
I thought it was cute.
I'm glad you decided to show me before we went.
I stopped you before you had an accident that would remain in everyone's memory.
Well, you're one to talk.
You're having quite the accident yourself.
What? You're kidding.
What is that?
What is it?
It's a swimsuit.
You look like a clay pipe.
What were you thinking when you put that on?
I thought it was cute.
Why?!
I don't like to dress too girly.
This looks like something you'd wear around the house!
Right?
Dress girly?
You're dressing like a pipe.
But I think the designer was going for...
a sort of French enfant look.
child
No. We're in Japan.
Right.
We're in Japan.
Next!
I really don't think you have anything to worry about.
What are you talking about?
Banri's in love with you.
It's as plain as day.
I feel like... Banri's afraid to try to get anything out of me.
You haven't even kissed yet?
We kiss!
Sometimes.
I see.
Are you sure you're not putting pressure on Banri?
What does Banri have to do to satisfy you?
Basically, I want him to understand how much I love him.
So you're saying, "Get your freak on."
"Follow your sexual desires and attack me like a wild beast."
"Come on."
Is that it?
Wh-What's gotten into you?
Do you think you can say whatever you want if you use that voice?
Huh?
In that case, putting it politely,
you're saying, "Make love to me!"
You're terrifying!
That's not what I meant.
I just...
I'm actually pretty hurt.
What's wrong?
The other day...
Kaga-san, your boobs.
Huh? Oh!
So, what happened?
I went to Banri's apartment.
On the way home, the mood seemed right,
so I went for a kiss.
And then?
He seemed troubled and didn't do it.
It's like wrestling alone.
I managed to smooth things over, but I'm a mess on the inside.
How were things going at his place before that?
Well, I made air yakisoba.
Air yakisoba?
No, I mean...
I made Banri happy by cooking for him.
We relaxed, enveloped in the smell of yakisoba.
Don't you ever feel in the mood...
when you're spending hours in your boyfriend's apartment?
That's the problem.
I don't at all.
I think I understand how Banri feels, though.
Really?
How does he feel?
That's just it.
It's that desperate face.
If you throw yourself at him like that,
you'll make him feel like a demon accepting a sacrificial virgin.
He's hesitating because he wants to show
that he really cares for you.
Then what am I supposed to do?
I know he cares about me.
But it's like Banri thinks of me
as a doll or something.
You're in quite a bind, huh?
This year, I have plans to go to Barcelona on my annual family vacation.
Uh-huh.
But secretly, I want to create a situation...
that will let me stay in Tokyo with Banri, at his place.
I see.
The beach is a prelude.
I want him to know I'm serious about our relationship.
Yeah.
I always feel uncertain.
Does Banri really love me?
Will Banri suddenly disappear one day?
Who is Banri, really?
What?
Is Banri still searching for himself?
What if he finds himself?
Will he leave me if he does?
Kaga-san?
Oh, come on!
I don't care about swimsuits!
I'm talking about what's inside.
About my feelings!
About fate!
That's what I'm talking about!
I'm going to wear the next one I grab.
I'll loan you the one I grab after that.
That will settle it!
What the heck?!
My swimsuit is...
this one!
And your swimsuit is...
Why do you have two school swimsuits?
That one's from middle school,
and this one's from high school.
They're not bad, though.
This might actually be kind of interesting.
What? Really?
Yeah, really.
This calls for the Okamera.
I can't do it!
This can't possibly be right!
No, no. Some people will like it.
I want to charm Banri, not "people"!
This might inspire a new fetish in Banri.
That's not what I want!
Come on.
Say something.
Sheesh!
Ahem.
I'm Kaga Kouko.
Miss Ultrasonic talked me into wearing this.
I'm Oka Chinami.
Are you watching, future me?
Come on, Kaga-san!
I'm K-Kaga Kouko.
Are you watching, Banri?
I love you very much.
I'll love you today, tomorrow, and the day after.
I'll love you forever!
We're going to the beach soon!
We're going to have fun and make memories that will last a lifetime!
Right, Kaga-san?
Don't make that face!
You have two choices.
Choose whichever you prefer.
This is the innocent pair I bought in my third year of middle school.
This is the toxic pair the president gave me after the party the other day.
Did you think there was any chance I'd choose the toxic pair?
I thought you might.
You seem like you might actually wear them.
I wish I could've invited Linda-senpai.
She said she's back home right now, so I didn't bother.
Oh?
I wonder where Linda-senpai's from.
Dunno.
No, no, that's not what I'm getting at
chigau yo mou chigau tte ba
Ah, you still haven't noticed
aa mada kizukanai no ne
Since a couple of hours ago
nisanjikan mo mae kara
I've been dying to grab onto your arm
sono ude ni furetai no ni
I have so many pent-up feelings that I want to let out
sakebitai kimochi wa hora komaru hodo aru no ni
But why? Why can't you take a hint?
dou shite dou shite chitto mo aa satotte kurenai no
Hey
nee
Are you really, really in love with me?
hontou ni hontou ni watashi ni koi shiteru
You can skip the sweet talk
kosobayui kotoba wa iranai
Love me semipermanently
han'eikyuuteki ni aishite yo
I don't care about five thousand years in the future
gosennen go nado kyoumi wa nai
My life's not endless
watashi endoresu de wa nai no
I'll die someday
itsuka wa shinu no yo
Telling me you'll love me forever
eien ni aishiteru yo nante
Won't make me happy
iwarete mo ureshikunai
For now just focus on
mazu wa watashi wo shinu made
Loving me until we die
ai suru koto dake wo kangaete
Accident Beach
Summer vacation!
Yeah!
Yes!
Summer vacation!
Hey!
Yay!
Speaking of summer vacation...
Shaved ice!
The beach!
Charming Banri! The Eiffel Tower!
That's...
What are you talking about?