Banri!
Linda-senpai?
What are you doing here?
Why are you dressed like that?
What about you, Linda-senpai?
Composing Message
Tada Banri
No Subject
W
Wh
Why
Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
Don't Look Back
hand in hand let's go party night
hand
in
let's
go
par
ty
night
My heart's dancing, and it won't stop
kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
We share so many memories, both happy and sad
naite waratte kimi to no kioku
I'll never forget them
zutto wasurenai
I'm supposed to find the real me and stuff
hontou no jibun wa doko ni iru to ka
Coming of age isn't easy
otona ni naru tte taihen de
But I guess I can forget about that for now
ima wa wasuretemo ii ka na
Because the night is waiting
yoru ga matte iru kara
When I think about seeing you, I get so excited
kokoro wo hazumase aeru toki wo
As I jump around in anticipation
hashagi mawareba
I might just notice the feelings inside me
tsutaetai omoi ni ima
That I want to get across to you
kizuiteshimaisou de
Even if we're afraid of the past and the future
kako to mirai osorete ite mo
We can't move on with nothing behind us
karappo no mama ja ugokenai
It's all right as long as we have fun
tanoshimeba it's all right
it's
all
right
Let's start
hajimeyou
ha
ji
me
you
When I forget everything I don't like
ya na koto zenbu wasurete
And dance through the night with you
kimi to issho ni odoriakaseba
I become a more wonderful person
motto suteki na jibun ni nareru
I can feel it
sonna ki ga suru no
let's get together
let's
ther
Our golden time will never end
owaranai golden time
time
As we pull each other closer
gyutto chikazuku kimi to no kyori wa
Not too close, not too far
tsukazu hanarezu
Even if we have to take the long way to get there
mawarimichi de mo
I'll cherish every second
taisetsu ni shitai
Yes!
Hey, you.
Yes?
That's quite a getup.
Do you always dress like that?
No.
It's for my job.
Hey, take a picture with me.
Me, too.
Just the two of us first.
Yanako looks really busy!
He's good-looking, after all.
I'm so cute!
I'm cuter!
What? Linda-senpai?!
Nana-senpai offered Linda-senpai a job too.
I just found out.
Don't be embarrassed.
You wear that look pretty well.
Linda-senpai, you look cool too.
In fact...
you look seriously hot!
I told you not to stare!
I have a message from the boss.
"It's a waste for you to be a waiter."
"Get on the stage."
What?!
He said he'll pay you ten thousand more if you do it.
Do it, Yana-san!
Earn funds for your summer vacation!
You talk like this doesn't concern you at all!
Come on. Just do it, Yanako.
Everything's an experience.
It's an order.
Come on!
I'll do it!
I'll do anything for money!
Go for it, Yana-san!
We'll be watching your display of bravery!
You don't have to watch!
Hey, do you have a girlfriend?
Huh?
What do you think of one-night stands?
Um... I...
Excuse me.
We need to borrow him over here.
Huh?
Thanks. You really saved me.
People take advantage of you because you get flustered.
Keep it together.
I've never experienced anything like this before.
I'm a little overwhelmed.
What you need is spirit.
Throw your chest out.
Right.
What are you looking at?!
Sorry, sorry.
Sheesh.
tada
Tesshi-chan, congratulations!
Thank you.
Working hard?
Yana-san.
You seemed to be having fun.
You might be good at this kind of work.
What? You can't be serious.
The guys around me said to just copy them.
That's all I was doing.
You didn't seem uncomfortable with it, though.
Don't you think so, Banri?
Yes.
Linda-senpai's right.
Hey, now.
Hey, Linda.
Lend me a hand.
Okay!
You really seemed to be into it.
You even got oiled up.
Are you sure you didn't actually have fun?
You're right.
It doesn't feel that bad.
It's like being a mechanism for heating up the party.
I think I know what you mean.
Yana-san was right.
On this insular night in the life of Tada Banri,
I actually found myself enjoying being in this environment I wasn't used to,
dressing as someone else, and becoming a working machine.
Linda-senpai really does look great.
Maybe I'll get a picture with her too.
Incoming Call
Kaga Kouko
Are you tired?
Doing okay?
I'm actually having fun.
I might even get into this.
I know what you mean!
This is actually the fourth time I've worked in one of the boss's events!
You two are so cute.
Can I get a picture?
Sure.
That's great.
Take some with this next.
This isn't what it looks like, Kouko-chan!
You're mistaken!
It's me! Me!
It's Linda!
Hayashida Nana...
I know that.
I'm so sorry!
I got carried away!
It's my fault!
I'm really sorry!
Don't make a fuss in front of the guests.
Come on.
Kaga-san, this way.
I'm working right now.
I'll explain everything later.
Wait until I'm done with work.
Okay?
You can't stay here, though.
I know.
My apartment.
Use this to get in.
I'll go there as fast as I can when I'm finished.
Work.
Sorry.
Yes.
Next: Tada Banri-kun!
Good work.
Thank you.
There's a lot in here!
Now I can make it through the summer!
Mine may have lost its usefulness.
Huh?
Oh, yeah!
I should text Kaga-san!
New Messages
No subject: Kaga Kouko
Received Message
Kaga Kouko
No Subject
Where are you?
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
Has your injury worsened?
No Subject
I'm going to your place
I'm here. Why aren't you?
I'll try the convenience store.
I'll try the family restaurant.
Did you get in an accident?
I tried calling the police.
Are you at Mitsuo's apartment?
Are you on campus?
I'm going to the festival club's training room.
TADA
Kaga-san?
Kaga-san...
Um, I'm really...
I'm sorry for throwing a drink at you.
For hitting you, too.
That's—
Your injury hasn't even healed yet.
I'm sorry.
Kaga-san.
I wanted to be a good girlfriend who wouldn't do those things.
I failed again.
I just can't do it.
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
Sorry!
I wanted to take you to the beach.
I didn't want you to pay for me.
I wanted to be a cool boyfriend.
That's why I lied and secretly took a job.
I didn't know Linda-senpai
would be working with me!
I got carried away by the atmosphere there.
It put me in a strange mood.
That's why I did it.
That's all. Really.
I'm sorry for making you worry!
I'm sorry for lying too!
I'm really sorry!
Then...
Why do you...
You said that was all.
Dumb Banri
Stupid Linda
Don't lie.
I'm sorry.
Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
Linda-senpai was a classmate before I lost my memory.
We were in the same class
and Track Club together.
We were friends.
I'd forgotten about Linda before I ran into her at college.
Linda recognized me right away,
but she didn't want to confuse me.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I didn't want you to know.
Why?
Before I lost my memory,
I was in love with Linda.
I didn't want you to worry about that.
You mean because I'm an annoying woman?
No.
Because you thought it'd be a nuisance if I made a big deal about it?
Because I felt guilty!
What?
My feelings return to me sometimes.
Out of nowhere, like flashbacks.
What do you mean?
I can't do anything about it.
Sometimes my soul screams like a storm...
that it wants to go back to Linda.
My memories don't return, but my feelings and desire to see Linda suddenly return.
I don't know what to do!
Why would you say that?
Kaga-san?
I wanted to be a good girlfriend.
When I found the photo, I decided to wait for you to tell me.
I wanted to stop interrogating you and becoming mentally unhinged.
I worked hard!
I did!
I was doing my best!
Kaga-san—
But if you say that, I...
What should I do?
It's all for nothing!
Everything's ruined!
Geez, just look at me!
This is what happens to me!
What should I do?
I don't want to be like this!
I don't!
I really don't.
Why would you say that?
Why?
Why did you tell me?
I wanted to be honest with you...
I didn't want to know!
Kaga-san, wait.
You're a storm.
You rile up my heart like a storm.
Don't remember anything else.
Please, don't remember the past.
That's the only thing I want from you.
Please.
I understand.
I won't.
Can I call you Banri from now on?
Yeah.
Will you call me Kouko?
Yeah... Kouko.
I love you.
I love you so much. I don't know how this happened.
But I really do love you.
I love you too, Kouko.
I must look terrible.
It's okay.
I don't think I got all my makeup off.
Why don't we get some makeup remover in the morning?
Huh?
We can leave it here.
Maybe I can use it when I stay over.
Ka...
Kouko.
Hey, Banri.
I feel uneasy.
Do you understand?
Will you understand?
I can't help but feel uneasy.
After all, we don't have anything.
We haven't spent a lot of time together.
We don't have experiences together.
We don't have any memories.
We don't even have any pictures.
In that case...
Do you want to take a picture?
What?
I want a picture with you too.
Let's start from there.
We don't need to rush anything.
I don't want to push you too hard just because I'm spineless.
Okay.
Tada Banri!
Did you wait long?
Anyway, sorry about last night.
I'm really sorry!
What should I do?
Kouko-chan was angry, wasn't she?
Of course she was.
I'm the worst.
Don't worry about it.
Kouko's fine now.
Really?
Why'd you come out to my place, then?
I wanted to talk about the past.
We weren't dating.
That's what you said, right?
Yeah, that's right.
I liked you, but you, Senpai...
Linda didn't like me.
Yeah, not in a romantic sense.
You were my friend, but I wasn't in love.
I didn't like you that way.
I wanted to confirm that.
Did you hear?
You can't go back to Linda.
Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
No matter how strongly you feel, that's a one-way street.
Stupid Linda
So just forget about her!
Disappear!
Stupid Linda
No!
I love Linda!
Stupid Linda
I want to be with Linda!
The truth is...
Stupid Linda
The truth is, I've been searching for Linda.
I've wanted to go back to Linda!
Thanks for everything.
But from now on, I want you to pretend we didn't know each other.
It's stressful.
I don't want to think about my amnesia.
I want to cut ties with my past.
You're not my former classmate anymore.
From now on, we're just a senior and junior in the same club.
You don't need to worry about me.
Honestly, Kouko's a little bothered by you,
so I want to put a clear distance between us.
I want to treat my girlfriend right.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I understand.
Yeah. That's what you should do.
Stupid Linda
We're doing the right thing, Banri.
It's all the opposite, Banri.
You're posing again.
It looks unnatural. Don't do it.
What? I wasn't posing.
You were.
I wasn't.
Hey, Kouko.
Why don't we take some outside?
Sure.
Let's go.
Banri, hurry up.
Okay, okay.
My favorite drink, a sweet caffè latte, in one hand
katate ni wa amaku shita okiniiri no kaferate
I enjoy the scent of love with a smile
hohoenda shunkan ni koi no kaori
I want to dress up perfectly
kanpeki ni kimetai no
I pick out a cherry-colored dress
cherii iro no wanpiisu
It looks neat and charming
sawayaka de tokimeite
Now I can go see you
kimi e isogou
Watch out for the sweet trap
ki wo tsukete amai wana
Yes, I'll whisper it in your ear
yes sasayaite ageru kara
Ah, I can't wait to see you
ah machidooshii kedo
What kind of smile should I greet you with?
donna egao de aeba ii
pretty love pretty love
You're so lovely
kimi ga itoshikute
under the sky under sunshine
Let's hold hands
te wo tsunagou
I can't bring myself to be honest, so take my hand
sunao ni narenai sonna watashi no te wo
And pull it toward you
hippatte ite ne
Summer Has Come
Wahoo! Money!
Kouko!
Banri!
That underwear was unbelievable,
Kouko!
but as long as Linda-senpai's there,
Banri!
I don't mind doing this job.
Kouko!
Banri!
Actually, sorry.
Kouko!
That's seriously annoying.
Banri!
Kouko!