Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
Horai Bridge
This is where I lost my memories.
Why...
Why don't I...
remember anything?
What was my relationship with Linda-senpai?
Banri?
Yana-san.
Listen, can I come over to your place?
I'm... not there.
Huh?
Body and Soul
hand in hand let's go party night
hand
in
let's
go
par
ty
night
My heart's dancing, and it won't stop
kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
We share so many memories, both happy and sad
naite waratte kimi to no kioku
I'll never forget them
zutto wasurenai
I'm supposed to find the real me and stuff
hontou no jibun wa doko ni iru to ka
Coming of age isn't easy
otona ni naru tte taihen de
But I guess I can forget about that for now
ima wa wasuretemo ii ka na
Because the night is waiting
yoru ga matte iru kara
When I think about seeing you, I get so excited
kokoro wo hazumase aeru toki wo
As I jump around in anticipation
hashagi mawareba
I might just notice the feelings inside me
tsutaetai omoi ni ima
That I want to get across to you
kizuiteshimaisou de
Even if we're afraid of the past and the future
kako to mirai osorete ite mo
We can't move on with nothing behind us
karappo no mama ja ugokenai
It's all right as long as we have fun
tanoshimeba it's all right
it's
all
right
Let's start
hajimeyou
ha
ji
me
you
When I forget everything I don't like
ya na koto zenbu wasurete
And dance through the night with you
kimi to issho ni odoriakaseba
I become a more wonderful person
motto suteki na jibun ni nareru
I can feel it
sonna ki ga suru no
let's get together
let's
ther
Our golden time will never end
owaranai golden time
time
As we pull each other closer
gyutto chikazuku kimi to no kyori wa
Not too close, not too far
tsukazu hanarezu
Even if we have to take the long way to get there
mawarimichi de mo
I'll cherish every second
taisetsu ni shitai
Until I was 18, I was Tada Banri.
The day after my graduation,
I fell off a bridge and left my physical body.
I was ejected and became a lifeless spirit.
The soulless and empty Banri
has been living as an amnesiac,
somehow becoming a college student.
Meanwhile, as a ghost,
I've been watching over the newly reborn Tada Banri.
But...
Banri can't hear me.
Let's go get our stuff from the club.
I want to talk to you afterward.
Oh, right.
Let's go get our stuff from the club.
I want to talk to you afterward.
That happened.
We've just met...
but being with you is so much fun.
It's true!
So I hope we can be good friends!
Tada-kun?
Nothing.
Anyway,
I want you to have this.
Now we match.
See?
It's a mirror of survival.
I had mine when we escaped from that cult the other day.
I see.
I left my stuff behind, remember?
But I had this in my pocket, so I took it with me.
Since then,
I've thought of it as a symbol of our friendship.
I wanted to give you the same one, so I bought this.
Please accept the gift!
Thanks.
Good friends, huh?
To commemorate the anniversary of our escape!
From your friend, Kaga Kouko
Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
What happened to you yesterday?
You sounded strange over the phone.
Oh, sorry.
Did you need something?
I thought I might've been a little hard on Kouko.
So you're worried about her after all.
Yeah.
And Chinami too.
Oka-chan?
My!
My! My!
Why, if it isn't my friend Tada-kun.
Good morning.
Now that I've run into you,
I'm sure this will be a splendid day.
We must be destined to be great friends from a previous life!
G-Good morning, Kaga-san.
Tada-kun, your voice is amazing.
Hey, have you ever thought about our previous lives?
What?
I have!
I was a postulant at a convent.
You were a shepherd living deep in the forest.
Every morning, you must've delivered cheese to me.
I'm sure of it.
Hey, isn't that romantic?
Thank you.
Thank you for everything.
I'm so grateful we were destined to meet again.
My, Mitsuo.
Ah, good morning.
Mitsuo, you must've been a solitary hunter wandering through the wilderness.
I can tell by looking at your face.
Given my quiet days of prayer in the convent,
perhaps we were never destined to meet.
Um, what should I do?
Ignore her.
That's what I do.
Hey!
Let's get started, Kouko-chan!
Sorry.
Linda-senpai was helping me register for classes.
This girl doesn't understand what courses are required.
I was telling her about some she could still take.
Tada Banri, what about you?
Have you already registered?
Yeah, I guess.
Oh, let me introduce you.
This is my friend Yana-san.
This is Linda-senpai from the Festival Club.
She rescued us from the cult's overnight trip.
Nice to meet you.
I heard my friend gave you a bit of trouble.
It was no trouble at all.
Anyway, is your registration going well?
Yeah, I suppose.
Civil law teacher?
Um... Tsukamoto-sensei.
What?!
You're taking Tsukamoto's civil law course?
That's not good!
Tsukamoto gives really tough exams every year!
Previous exams are no help,
and he's really strict about attendance!
Seriously?
Oh, my.
Mitsuo, you seem to have a problem.
How... sad... for... you!
I'm going to ask some other civil law
professors if it's not too late to register!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Fail all your classes!
Stay an extra year!
And cry!
Stupid, stupid!
What was that?
Mitsuo is such a child.
Oh, right.
Have you decided if you're joining the Festival Club?
We still don't have any new members.
Of course.
We'll both join.
We're great friends.
We do everything together.
Right, Tada-kun?
Um...
All right! That's two new members!
I hope we can be friends.
Right!
Right.
Linda-senpai, you must know who I am.
Is there some reason why
you're not mentioning it?
Kaga-san, didn't you say you weren't confident about your dancing?
Yes.
But I figured that's no reason to shy away from it.
A lot has happened recently.
After overcoming all of it, I'm feeling really positive.
I see.
That's good.
It's thanks to you, my friend.
I want to try new things.
You shouldn't be indecisive.
It's a waste of life.
Make progress every day.
I'm going to run myself to death with a super-positive lifestyle!
Why are you being so proactive?
You should be more positive too.
No, you have to be.
If you're not as positive as I am, you won't be the perfect friend!
Just because I rejected...
What did you say?
I didn't say anything.
But you almost said it.
I didn't, I didn't!
I really didn't.
Then take control of this awkward silence.
Fine. I'll handle it.
A-Anyway, that's that.
Let's give the Festival Club everything we have.
Y-Yeah.
I'm first-year law student Tada Banri!
Nice to meet you.
I'm first-year law student Kaga Kouko.
Okay!
This will help build momentum for our summer event.
What's happening this summer?
We're participating in an Awa dance event.
Let's start practicing.
Music.
Try imitating the people around you.
Okay.
It's all right.
I'm confident that I'll dance well today.
That sounds great.
Give it a try!
You're actually pretty good for beginners.
You'll get better.
Tada Banri and Kouko-chan, see you later.
Thank you.
I can't do this.
You're supposed to be my friend,
but you can dance!
You're so mean!
Traitor!
What am I supposed to do?
I'm sick of this.
I wanted to be positive.
Why does this have to happen?
It's nothing to cry about.
But...
Tada-kun, I'm sorry!
I know I'm just... lashing out at you!
Kaga-san...
You'll still be my friend, won't you?
I know...
I know you're just being nice to me.
You joined a club with me,
danced with me,
listen to me complain,
and worry about me.
I'm just taking advantage of your
kindness and causing you trouble.
You must hate me too.
Well, um...
Why don't you stand up?
She's been pushing herself really hard.
It's only been two days since Yana-san rejected her.
Your drink is crazy.
A latte with espresso, vanilla syrup, whipped cream, caramel,
and chocolate.
It's the greatest combination.
You seem to be feeling better.
I'm really sorry about earlier.
It was ridiculous of me to cry.
I've just been so hopeless...
lately.
Actually, I may always have been easily confused.
I'm stupid, hot-headed, and irredeemable.
I don't know what to do.
I thought I had to put my mistakes behind me as soon as possible.
And so, I panicked.
When you say "mistakes," you mean...
Yes.
I wanted to deal with my feelings for Mitsuo.
It's not as though I still love him.
It's just that...
my emotions still feel paralyzed.
Oh, no! My nose!
Just a second.
Tada-kun, you're using it.
Of course.
They're matching mirrors of friendship.
Tada-kun, you understand my worthless self.
You forgive me despite that.
And I took advantage of you and cried.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I'm a year older than you anyway.
Oh, right.
You're the same age as Linda-senpai.
I want to be like Linda-senpai.
I admire her.
Y-You do?
She's trim and seems to be positively enjoying life.
She's cool no matter
what she's doing, and she's pretty.
Maybe Kosshi-senpai likes Linda-senpai.
Wh-Why would you say that?
They seem close.
They don't seem to be going out, though.
Maybe Linda-senpai has a boyfriend!
After all, she is wonderful!
I bet she's really popular!
Linda-senpai.
Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
Hayashida Nana...
Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
Your temperature is normal.
Is something bothering you?
It's not about my health.
Each day, in the middle of the night,
I see a flickering light on that mountain.
Do you know what that is?
A light?
At night?
Are you saying you're having trouble sleeping?
You should've said something.
I'm not tired around 11:00.
It's lights out at 9:00 at this hospital.
You need to sleep according to a schedule.
I know they're worried about me.
After all, I have amnesia.
But...
I've been hospitalized for almost two months.
I feel like I've been confined for observation.
When can I leave?
There it is.
Could it be some kind of signal for me?
Yahoo!
This should be the right way.
Ouch.
G-Give me a minute.
I mean no harm.
Um, I'm from the hospital down the hill.
If you're wondering what I'm doing here,
it's because I can see that light from my room.
I wondered about it.
I came out here to find out.
A-Are you okay?
Sh-Should...
Should I get someone from the hospital?
No, don't worry about me.
So, anyway...
I thought...
someone was trying to signal to me with that light.
I thought they were signaling for me to escape.
I thought it said, "C'mere, c'mere!"
Like I was being led here.
Like I should run away.
Escaping?
In the hospital,
I feel like I'm being watched all the time.
It's suffocating and boring.
So today, I couldn't take it anymore,
and now I'm here.
Yes! I am stupid, clearly!
I see.
So what about you?
What have you been doing alone every night?
I've been coming to see the hospital.
My friend's been hospitalized.
I can't see him, though.
I thought I could at least drop by.
Is he from around here?
He's from Tokyo.
I go to college in Tokyo.
I'm home for Golden Week.
Oh?
Tokyo sounds nice.
If I got into a college in Tokyo,
I could say goodbye to this prison.
I feel like I could escape.
Prison? You mean the hospital?
That, and the human relationships restricting me.
All my ties.
Everything.
Come to Tokyo.
What?
It's fun.
Come.
Come with me.
Yeah, you're right.
I should go to Tokyo.
I'll leave the hospital, study,
and get into a college in Tokyo!
Thank you!
Thanks for your signal.
I know your signal wasn't meant for me...
but to me, your light was a sign for me to break free!
I'm going to Tokyo!
Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
That was Linda-senpai.
Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
Why hasn't she said anything, though?
About going to high school together,
or meeting me while I was hospitalized?
I don't get it!
Even though you have a body,
you have no memories from before you were 18.
Even though I have memories, I have no body.
I want to tell you...
what Linda...
meant to me.
My favorite drink, a sweet caffè latte, in one hand
katate ni wa amaku shita okiniiri no kaferate
I enjoy the scent of love with a smile
hohoenda shunkan ni koi no kaori
I want to dress up perfectly
kanpeki ni kimetai no
I pick out a cherry-colored dress
cherii iro no wanpiisu
It looks neat and charming
sawayaka de tokimeite
Now I can go see you
kimi e isogou
Watch out for the sweet trap
ki wo tsukete amai wana
Yes, I'll whisper it in your ear
yes sasayaite ageru kara
Ah, I can't wait to see you
ah machidooshii kedo
What kind of smile should I greet you with?
donna egao de aeba ii
pretty love pretty love
You're so lovely
kimi ga itoshikute
under the sky under sunshine
Let's hold hands
te wo tsunagou
I can't bring myself to be honest, so take my hand
sunao ni narenai sonna watashi no te wo
And pull it toward you
hippatte ite ne
Yes No
Whir, clunk. Whir, clunk. Whir, whir...
Kaga-san, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
Wh-Whir, whir, whir...
Boom!
Kaga-san broke!
Yana-san, what am I supposed to do now?
Ignore her.
That's what I do.