I hadn't said anything until now, but I think this is the time.
I only came to college to follow Mitsuo, after all.
That was always my plan, from the start.
What?
Goodbye.
I thought there had to be some mistake.
I tried to believe that if I just waited there,
Kouko would come back.
So I didn't move.
If I wasn't there when Kouko returned, and we missed each other,
I felt like we would be separated forever.
But... time marched on,
and Kouko never returned.
Tada-kun.
What a coincidence.
Paradise Lost
Ah, if I met you in my dream, would I be able to say it?
aa yume no naka de aetara yueru ka na
The sorrows alone scatter down from the sky
nee kanashimi dake sora kara maiochite
That voice torments you to this day
sonna koe ga kimi wo ima de mo kurushimete
Even when I put my hand on yours, I can't get over these feelings
soba de te wo kasanetemo kono omoi wa kienai kedo
When our eyes meet, even if you don't say what you mean
futari me wo awasetara hontou no koto ienakutemo
Your words shine my world brighter than anyone else's
kimi no kotoba dare yori mo sekai wo terashiteru
Next to me, you say "Goodbye" when you mean "I love you"
tonari de kimi wa sayonara wa aishiteru tte sou iu no
I can't be honest
sunao ni narenai
When I'm singing about my loneliness alone
watashi dake kodoku wo utatte mo
I can't smile
egao ni narenai
If you say "Thanks" to mean "I'm in love with you"
arigato wa koi shiteru tte sou iu no
This is love at the end of the world
ai no world's end
It's not actually a coincidence, is it?
What?
Kouko told you to come, didn't she?
Turn the car around.
I don't get any of this!
I don't understand!
Are you trying to tear me away from Kouko?!
Tada-kun, calm down.
Turn the car around!
What are you doing?!
But you didn't chase after her, did you?
You didn't chase Kouko.
Even now, you're not telling me to let you see Kouko.
Instead of trying to face her,
you're waiting for her to change her mind and return.
That's awfully laid back of you.
I don't know what Kouko was thinking when she left you.
However, she suddenly asked me something not long ago.
When does a doctor prescribe anti-anxiety medication for a patient?
Anti-anxiety medication...
She asked if it meant the patient was insecure and in pain.
I nodded, and the conversation ended.
Tada-kun, have you been prescribed any medications?
I don't intend to draw any conclusions from your answer.
However, I think it may be the reason that
Kouko reconsidered her relationship with you.
Did Kouko know...
that I was taking that medication?
What are you doing?
Nana-senpai.
You'll catch a cold.
Come on, let's get inside.
I'm going to stay out here a little longer.
What are you going to do a little longer?
I'm going... to the convenience store!
Really? The convenience store, huh?
Fine, then. Let's go together.
I sort of know what's going on.
Linda told me a long time ago.
You bought red-bean soup without looking?
Go figure.
Homemade Style
Red-Bean Soup
I heard about your fall from the bridge and your amnesia...
Homemade Style
Red-Bean Soup
from Linda last year, when she was a first-year.
I didn't say anything because it wasn't my place to get involved.
Hey, I ate beef yesterday.
Kouko's beef, right?
The way you said that...
Well, whatever.
Linda, that first-year, and I wolfed down
that beef like it was the best we'd ever had.
Her parents must be amazing if she could afford to bring that.
They're doctors.
Pretty important ones, apparently.
Anyway, what were you doing yesterday?
I... was running away.
Honestly, I just wanted to die.
Don't say you want to die so easily.
I'll kill you!
Sorry.
I think I'm going to disappear soon...
and be replaced by the former personality of Tada Banri.
I don't think there's anything I can do about it.
That's my normal, healthy state, after all.
But it still hurts.
I just keep falling.
Linda told me your accident was her fault.
"How could I just abandon him like this?"
"I don't know what to do," she said.
Well, I don't believe there's a 20-year-old who does know what they should do.
You meet someone and then part ways.
It's a natural part of the human experience.
No one can promise they'll be together forever.
Life is suffering, pain, and misery.
That's harsh... harsh.
Try to make it through today.
Kaga Kouko's the one trying not to hurt you.
Kouko seems to have given up on me.
Huh?
She just told me it was time to call it quits.
Say something.
Sorry.
The one who pretends to know everything never knows anything at all.
I feel like apologizing to Linda too.
I'm the worst.
Making light of others' pain,
denying it, averting my eyes...
I'm not even generous enough to share their burdens and help lighten them!
Hold on.
Why are you apologizing?
You told me because you trust me, right?
But I ignored you.
I've come to hate myself in these last few seconds!
Please don't think that!
You have no idea how much it helped to have you listen to me tonight.
If I had stayed that way, I really might have...
Don't be so thoughtless, you moron.
You're the next to the next to the next to the next to the next person I like as much as Linda.
In any case, go home and sleep.
Then try talking to Kaga Kouko again tomorrow.
If there's anything I can do, I'll help.
This special super sweet red-bean soup version is just for tonight.
Okay.
I'm going to have a proper conversation with Kouko.
Banri!
I'm glad I ran into you.
I've been waiting for you to apologize for yesterday.
Kou...
I just went off on you unilaterally,
and I didn't even call you afterward.
I'm sorry.
Are you mad?
I left you after saying such mean things to you.
The truth is, I got really worried a while after that and went back for you.
Huh?
You were standing there forever, weren't you?
But I just couldn't say anything.
That's why I sent my father to get you.
Really?
Let's go.
Morning!
Good morning.
You guys have first period, too?
Kaga-san, that sweater you're wearing is amazing!
Hey, stop!
You're going to make static electricity!
Banri, is your nose okay?
Yeah, it's totally fine.
I see.
That's good, then.
Anyway, I'm relieved.
You seem totally fine.
Sorry for making you worry.
I've been a little high-strung lately.
And, well...
Actually, I've even been prescribed medication.
I guess I wasn't taking it properly, though.
I see.
But whatever happens,
don't you feel like you'll be fine as long as you have Kouko?
Yeah.
Here you go, Oka-chan.
Have a free cup of coffee I poured just for the hell of it,
without any special feelings behind it.
I don't feel particularly grateful.
Mine seems a little weak.
Here, Kouko.
Thanks.
Kaga-san, your cup is super-specially rich with Banri's love for you!
Oh, my.
Wasn't Banri just telling you?
Telling me what?
We broke up.
What?
Banri and I broke up.
I thought I should let you all know.
But don't worry.
We're back to being just friends.
If you could keep treating us the way you have been...
Why?!
Where did that come from?
We talked about this.
Did you already forget what happened yesterday?
It was long past time to end our relationship.
After calmly thinking things through,
I decided I'd lost my feelings for you.
So let's go back to being friends.
What are you talking about?
It's already been decided.
I broke up with you.
If you'd like to change my mind, go ahead.
Then...
Then why did you talk to me this morning?
Just like always.
Normally!
I told you, I wanted to apologize.
Weren't you listening?
Oh, don't get the wrong idea.
I was only being considerate because we're still friends.
If you have a problem with that,
it might be difficult for us to even be friends.
Anyway, class is starting.
We have the same lecture, don't we?
Banri!
Please, don't accept this.
You know better than anyone how nonsensical she can be.
There's no way she's serious, so—
This has nothing to do with you!
If you won't let this go, I'll start avoiding all of you!
Look, you...
Shut up!
Hey, where are you going?
To class.
Or is it too awkward for you to be with me?
In that case, I don't mind skipping.
I don't care about lectures anyway.
In fact, I don't care about college anymore.
This place, the people here,
the time I spent here...
I don't care about any of it!
What are you looking at?!
I really don't care.
Wait, Kouko!
Banri...
Did she...
2D-kun, you have a lecture, don't you?
You should go.
Yeah, but...
Sorry.
I want to be alone for a while.
All right.
But if anything comes up, let me know.
Huh?
I feel like I can do it.
I feel like I can reach you now.
Come back already.
Sorry, Banri.
I wanted to ask Kaga-san something,
but I couldn't catch up to her.
The other day, remember how I asked you to film me in your apartment?
Everything that happened after that was recorded.
Who... are you?
Huh? What?
I'm going to fast forward.
Don't... Don't tell Kouko.
After this, you left.
Then we went to Nana-senpai's room to eat beef.
Kaga-san said she forgot something in your room and went back by herself.
So you're saying Kouko saw all that?
Probably.
I see.
So that's it.
There's nothing I can do, then.
Don't be like that!
Let's explain it to her!
We'll show her the video
you filmed yesterday too!
Thanks, but it's okay.
What do you mean, okay?
Kouko already knows everything.
She knew I had amnesia before we started dating.
Kouko fell in love with me,
even though I made no sense.
She supported me plenty of times.
I was such a burden to her.
You don't know how much pain I caused her.
She did her best for me.
I can't ask her to do any more.
Does this mean it's over?
What about this, then?
I'm...
My name is Tada Banri.
I'd like to talk about the things that have happened to me up to now.
Do whatever you want with it.
Erase it or use it for something else.
It's up to you.
There's no way I could do that!
Really, do whatever you want with it.
You can keep it.
That has meaning enough for me.
Don't make that face.
Now we're both members of the broken hearts club.
Hey, Senpai!
My brokenhearted senpai!
You're making a painful face.
Is my face that painful?
Yeah, kinda.
I can clearly tell you're forcing yourself to look happy.
Of course, I only know because I've made the same face.
I'm going to edit it together and
present it at the school festival
as the diaries of a depressed co-ed!
Don't miss it!
What? You're going to show it to Yana-san too?
I won't mention who broke my heart.
Well, Yana might figure it out anyway,
but I guess I don't care anymore.
He might as well just figure it out!
Do you want to film my brokenhearted face too?
You can use me to accent your co-ed's diary.
What? Really?
If you say that, I really will film you and use the footage.
I told you, all the footage you take of me using the Okamera...
belongs to you.
Okay.
Hello to everyone watching Oka-chan's co-ed diaries.
I was just dumped.
I feel really awkward.
I don't know what I should do now.
I know how you feel.
You're even in the same club.
The club...
Huh?
You suddenly got all gloomy.
That kind of stung.
Sorry, did I hit a painful spot?
Really painful.
It was a fatal blow.
I'm going to die now.
If you want, you can use it for the last scene of your film.
Three, two, one...
Goodbye.
What?! You broke up?
Looks like she got sick of me.
Is something wrong with you?
So I want you to talk to Kouko like you did over the summer, when she misunderstood things.
So she doesn't quit the Festival Club.
What? What are you saying?
How can you be so calm?!
Because she gave up on me.
It really hurts.
How can you accept that?!
Let go.
Is that all there was to your relationship?
Let go!
No!
I don't understand!
I can't help it!
Whoa, Banri.
She dumped me!
Gave up on me!
What am I supposed to do now?!
Go after her!
Chase her and tell her you still love her!
If I could do that, I would've done it already!
You hurt me first, didn't you?!
Don't be stupid!
Hey, cut it out!
I'll never accept this!
I don't understand how you can!
Don't you understand what the incident the other day means?
It's over for me!
I'm just going to fall apart and disappear!
Disappear?
There's no way anyone can believe in the love of a person like me!
I believe!
My disappearance is inevitable now.
I have no future.
I'm just a ghost!
You're you!
No matter what happens, you're Tada Banri!
I'm not me!
I'm not the man you know!
Who the hell is Tada Banri, anyway?
I've always wanted to know!
Everyone calls me Tada Banri,
but I have no clue who he is!
What does that make me, then?
If you can just give up like that,
what am I supposed to do with my own feelings?!
What do you mean, your feelings?!
You didn't accept me, either!
What?
You didn't come to the bridge!
I did go, but I was too late!
Why didn't you wait for me?
I know I was late!
But how...
how could you let that happen?
It's not fair.
If I could, I'd go back and redo that day!
Let me redo it!
Let me do it one more time!
If I can, I won't screw it up again.
I swear I won't be late.
Let me go back!
Let me do it again!
But you still have time!
There seems to be something going on.
Linda and I have known each other a long time.
I've been keeping it from everyone.
Yana-san.
Banri...
I'm sorry, Yana-san.
I've been lying to you too.
Linda and I have been together since high school.
Always in the same clubs and classes.
I loved Linda.
I wanted to be with her forever,
so I confessed my feelings to her the day of our graduation.
But the next day,
while waiting for her answer, I got in an accident and was seriously injured.
I lost all my memories up to that day.
My name, my parents, my home, my friends, Linda...
Everything disappeared from my memories.
I forgot everything I ever knew.
The person who was reborn is the man before you.
I'm sorry for lying to you until now.
I was in on it too.
In fact, it's all my fault.
Why... Why didn't you say anything?!
President, I...
Resignation
Wait!
No, no, that's not what I'm getting at
chigau yo mou chigau tte ba
Ah, you still haven't noticed
aa mada kizukanai no ne
Since a couple of hours ago
nisanjikan mo mae kara
I've been dying to grab onto your arm
sono ude ni furetai no ni
I have so many pent-up feelings that I want to let out
sakebitai kimochi wa hora komaru hodo aru no ni
But why? Why can't you take a hint?
dou shite dou shite chitto mo aa satotte kurenai no
Hey
nee
Are you really, really in love with me?
hontou ni hontou ni watashi ni koi shiteru
You can skip the sweet talk
kosobayui kotoba wa iranai
Love me semipermanently
han'eikyuuteki ni aishite yo
I don't care about five thousand years in the future
gosennen go nado kyoumi wa nai
My life's not endless
watashi endoresu de wa nai no
I'll die someday
itsuka wa shinu no yo
Telling me you'll love me forever
eien ni aishiteru yo nante
Won't make me happy
iwarete mo ureshikunai
For now just focus on
mazu wa watashi wo shinu made
Loving me until we die
ai suru koto dake wo kangaete
Last Smile
Sorry, Banri. You can have this back.
But hair that falls out can't go back in!
The hair on a man's head affects his future!
There's no fixing this!
Why did you pull it?!
Shut up already!
And you're scary.