Excuse me.
Um, I made reservations for Fukurai University's Japanese cultural research group.
Return to Yesterday
Ah, if I met you in my dream, would I be able to say it?
aa yume no naka de aetara yueru ka na
The sorrows alone scatter down from the sky
nee kanashimi dake sora kara maiochite
That voice torments you to this day
sonna koe ga kimi wo ima de mo kurushimete
Even when I put my hand on yours, I can't get over these feelings
soba de te wo kasanetemo kono omoi wa kienai kedo
When our eyes meet, even if you don't say what you mean
futari me wo awasetara hontou no koto ienakutemo
Your words shine my world brighter than anyone else's
kimi no kotoba dare yori mo sekai wo terashiteru
Next to me, you say "Goodbye" when you mean "I love you"
tonari de kimi wa sayonara wa aishiteru tte sou iu no
I can't be honest
sunao ni narenai
When I'm singing about my loneliness alone
watashi dake kodoku wo utatte mo
I can't smile
egao ni narenai
If you say "Thanks" to mean "I'm in love with you"
arigato wa koi shiteru tte sou iu no
This is love at the end of the world
ai no world's end
Hey.
Huh?
Everyone's already here?
I'm so sorry.
I'll help.
It's Tada Banri.
Tada Banri.
It's Banri.
Oh, my.
Huh? What is it?
What's going on?
Why are you looking at me like that?!
It's nothing.
Come over here, Tada Banri.
Let's do this together.
We're hanging up these lights before the fourth years arrive.
Don't forget about these lanterns.
N-No! You're scaring me!
Why?
We're not scary.
Yes, you are!
You're acting weird!
There's nothing weird about us.
We didn't get to go on our overnight trip,
but let's have fun today to make up for it.
The president's connections got us this place too.
Isn't it great?
Right? Isn't this fun?
The Festival Club is so much fun, isn't it?
Hey, Tada Banri!
It's been a while.
I've really, really missed you.
What have you been up to lately?
Well, lately... I... just, um...
"Just"?
Well, you can't help that, can you?
I guess you could say we see you and RoboGirl as... well...
sort of like a fertilized egg.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Two life forms that have become one.
That's what I mean.
It's like you and RoboGirl were always one.
You're the genes that will carry our souls on to the next generation.
Yeah, yeah.
Huh?
Linda-senpai isn't here?
Her?
She said she'd come here from home.
But forget about that.
Oh, she went home to Shizuoka?
Don't talk about it right after I told you to forget it.
Anyway, what about you?
No, I mean you guys.
Um, I really don't understand.
What I'm trying to say is...
We all want to include you and RoboGirl.
You get it, don't you?
No, I don't.
You don't?
In any case...
It's that! Get it?
I don't get it.
In other words, just because you broke up with RoboGirl,
neither of you should quit the club.
What?
You don't have to tell us.
We understand.
We've been calling and texting RoboGirl lately,
but we can't get in touch with her.
Even when we called you,
when we asked about RoboGirl, you gave vague answers.
Isn't that what it means?
Actually, I...
But!
Even if you're not a couple anymore, that doesn't mean your bond with us is lost.
Right, guys?
That's right!
We'll soothe the pain of lost love!
Come on!
Let's cheer up Tada Banri!
Tada!
Banri!
No, no, no!
Tada! Banri!
Why would you assume that?
Kouko and I are...
Sorry I'm late.
RoboGirl!
RoboGirl's here!
RoboGirl's returned from the heart-repair factory!
Let's give a warm welcome to the nearly broken RoboGirl.
RoboGirl!
Huh? Huh?
What's going on? What?
It's not like that! You've got the wrong idea!
You don't have to tell us.
We understand.
No, you don't understand!
We didn't break up!
What?
Well, this is stupid.
We wasted our time trying to be nice to them.
We were really worried about what we'd do if you quit.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Aw, don't blame them.
It's not their fault.
Yeah, you're the one to blame!
You were the first to assume they broke up.
You guys said you were sure about it too!
Are you trying to blame us?
It's your fault for jumping to conclusions!
We might have come dangerously close to it, though.
That wasn't close at all.
That wasn't even within the range of "close."
What?
Nothing.
I just thought you look good in your yukata.
This? I made it this year.
I decided I wanted to go, so I will go and see fireworks with you this summer!
It rained the other day, though.
Yeah.
Listen up, everyone.
I just got word.
Mind if I come to today's
fireworks extravaganza?
It's okay, right?
Of course it is!
See you later!
Mind if I come to today's
fireworks extravaganza?
It's okay, right?
Of course it is!
See you later!
Mind if I come to today's
fireworks extravaganza?
It's okay, right?
Of course it is!
See you later!
Former president Hoshino-senpai is coming here today.
Seriously? Hosshi-san's coming?
He said he wouldn't come if he couldn't find a job.
That means...
...he found work!
That's great.
He'd been looking really gloomy.
Okay! Let's celebrate with everything we have!
Yeah!
Hey, it's been a while!
Hosshi-senpai!
Your legendary pirouette is so cool.
Isn't it? Isn't it cool?
Wow, this place is awesome.
Sorry, guys.
We should've helped.
Don't be ridiculous.
Anyway...
Hosshi-senpai.
Congratulations on your employment!
Congratulations!
Yeah.
Now all the fourth years have found jobs.
Congratulations!
Huh?
Oh... yeah.
Sorry.
I haven't actually found a job yet...
you might say.
I wanted a change of pace.
That's why I came.
I'm really sorry.
Sorry I'm late.
Huh?
What's this mood in the air?
What's wrong with me, huh?
They are lousy judges of character!
I know what you mean.
It's not your fault.
Come on, drink some more.
In any case, I'm glad you're all okay.
Oka-chan's injury is better now, right?
Yeah, completely.
I'm really sorry for making you worry.
It's fine.
Even though I was at home, I felt uneasy.
Actually, how did you hear about the accident?
Oh, you know, from people.
I'm quite relieved, though.
I was worried until I finally saw you.
It was worth coming back just to see you two.
Linda-senpai.
Huh?
Did we ever light fireworks together before I lost my memory?
You were in the same class for all three years of high school, right?
That's right.
Before I fell off that bridge.
You were both on the track team, weren't you?
You must've looked so cool, Linda-senpai.
About those fireworks...
Take a look at your left leg, Banri.
My left leg?
That's a burn scar.
In the summer of our second year, when we lit fireworks on the track team's overnight trip,
a bottle rocket fell over and struck you.
What?
Now I remember!
I hurt myself protecting you!
This scar is a badge of honor!
No, no.
I ran away quickly, but you were stupidly slow to run.
We got in a lot of trouble with our adviser afterward.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
It's all in the past.
By the way, Banri,
are you going home for summer break?
I will.
My parents have been pushing me to go.
Linda-senpai, that's how it is.
If you happen to see Banri while you're back home,
I hope you'll hang out with him.
Please.
Listen, I wasn't going to bring this up,
but can I say something?
A high school class reunion?
Yeah, next week.
Our class is holding a reunion.
I was sure you wouldn't want to come, so I wasn't going to tell you,
but do you want to stop by?
Oh, I won't force you.
It's just... everyone's worried about you.
If you show them you're fine, I think they'll be really happy.
I just wanted to tell you that.
Senpai.
Banri will attend.
What?
You will, won't you?
What? You won't?
You will, right? Of course you will.
Yeah. I'll go.
I'll go to the class reunion.
Did I do something I shouldn't have?
I'm sorry for making the decision for you.
Did I make trouble for you again?
No, it's fine.
I've decided to stop running from my past.
I'll go.
Honestly, I'm nervous.
The person everyone wants to see is the Tada Banri from before I lost my memory.
He's a completely different person from who I am now.
When they see me, they might think,
"Who is this guy?"
"You're not the one we want to see."
"We want to see the old Banri."
They might think something like that.
You told me the other day that I'd abandoned my friends and family and run away.
I'm really...
I'm really sorry about that.
I know you don't remember them.
I shouldn't have...
It's fine.
I'm glad you said it.
It helped me decide to face my past.
I'll go see my classmates.
I can't help what they think about me.
I'll apologize for making them worry and thank them.
I wonder why it is.
I feel like I'll finally get to see the whole Banri.
The whole me?
I think I couldn't really accept you before.
Maybe I only saw the Banri I wanted to see.
I couldn't accept that there were people
who knew a Banri that I didn't know.
I must've been jealous.
But what you said...
"I'll do my best, so you do your best too."
"Don't get out of the car."
When you said that, I realized I loved you.
I realized it was fine for me to keep loving you.
I love you because you're you.
I'm happy that you're whole.
I don't care if there are sides of you I don't know or don't like.
If that's who you are, that's fine.
As long as you're whole, that's enough for me.
But I'm struggling because I've lost sight of my whole self.
That's part of who you are too.
So go see your past with your own eyes.
See for yourself the Banri you've forgotten,
the you before you met me,
and then tell me about it.
Can I open this box?
Sure!
Oh, but could you take that box to the corner over there?
It's full of fragile stuff, so be careful.
You're a real slave driver, aren't you?
That's not true.
Kaga-san, you're staying here tonight, aren't you?
What?
It'll take until nighttime to finish putting things away.
Wait, you're going to make me work until then?
What?
But isn't that why you came here?
No!
I had no intention of helping you move.
I was a little curious, so I came to take a look.
When I heard your apartment wasn't what you imagined,
I thought I'd come laugh at you.
Is that why you brought an apron?
In any case, let's get this done quickly.
You'll be the first one to stay over!
I'm not staying!
Absolutely not. Not even if it kills me.
I won't stay over even if the world ends!
Kaga-san?
What?
Do you want me to guess what you're thinking about?
Do whatever you want.
You're thinking about Banri, aren't you?
You're wondering what he's up to in Shizuoka right now.
You're amazing.
Once you fall in love, you really love that person through thick and thin.
Isn't everyone like that?
No, they're not.
I have a lot of respect for you.
What?
Hey, what did you...
I know you're just pretending to sleep.
I knew it!
Linda-senpai, you're not leaving yet?
Yeah. I'm staying until the first train.
Once the trains start running, I'll get on a bullet train.
You're going home again?
I meant to go right back home in the first place,
but I was suddenly asked to work here, and that delayed my plans a day.
I got to see the two underclassmen too.
Um, did I do something I shouldn't have?
I made you worry by telling you about the accident.
Not at all.
I'm glad you told me.
Thanks.
I see.
Um, do you need some help?
No, that's okay.
I'm finished.
Um, how long are you going to be at home?
Until the end of summer break, I think.
I've got a class reunion,
and I have plans to hang out with some friends after that.
A reunion, huh?
Sounds like fun.
You don't have any plans like that?
None yet.
Banri's gone home too.
With fewer friends around, I don't have much to do.
Tokyo
Shizuoka
Linda-senpai, you're from Shizuoka?
Yeah.
Banri said he's from Shizuoka too.
Maybe you'll run into Banri somewhere.
That won't happen!
Shizuoka's a big place.
Hey! What are you doing?
Give it back!
What?
Give it back.
Why are you doing this?
Why do you think I'm doing this?
Actually, I'm going back to my apartment first.
Later.
Three is fine, thank you.
Oh, but make them all different flavors.
Very well.
And where's the restroom?
This way.
I'm glad Kaga-san's feeling better.
I'm so glad.
Yeah.
I wish I could've seen Oka-chan too.
I guess she can't help it.
She said she's not done unpacking.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Is something bothering you today?
I wouldn't say it's bothering me, but...
Listen, Banri's from Shizuoka, isn't he?
Do you know what high school he attended?
No.
You know he doesn't really talk about his past.
Now that you mention it...
Maybe he doesn't want to
remember because of his accident.
Accident?
You mean the one the other day?
No, not that.
Huh?
You haven't heard, Yana-san?
About when Banri fell from a bridge and got badly hurt?
Badly hurt?
We were tricked by some weird cult and taken to their campsite.
Banri told us about it then.
He fell from a bridge and was hospitalized for a while.
Anyway, he said, "I'm interested in religion because I've had that experience."
"No one else is interested, so let them go."
Is that really true, though?
I thought it was a lie too.
I assumed he made something up so we could escape. But...
when we went to the beach the other day, I saw a faint scar.
Around here.
I pretended not to notice,
but maybe what he said at that camp was true.
He said a bunch of other things too.
What do you mean, other things?
Well, I don't know how much is true and how much is false.
Besides, we shouldn't look into it too much if he doesn't want to talk about it.
Thank you for waiting.
These look delicious.
Take whichever one you want.
It's on me...
because I made you guys worry.
You've got a big heart, Kaga-san!
What?
What are you saying about my nice body?
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
You're very thin.
Kouko, did you know?
Know what?
That Banri was hospitalized.
Hey, Yana-san!
Who knows?
What are you talking about?
I have no idea.
Here, take a spoon.
Thanks...
You too, Mitsuo.
I guess I'll dig in, then.
Go ahead.
Oh, right. Kaga-san, how was Oka-chan's place?
You stayed over, didn't you?
I did.
In fact, she even made me help her move.
You were doing work? Sounds cool.
Right?
No, no, that's not what I'm getting at
chigau yo mou chigau tte ba
Ah, you still haven't noticed
aa mada kizukanai no ne
Since a couple of hours ago
nisanjikan mo mae kara
I've been dying to grab onto your arm
sono ude ni furetai no ni
I have so many pent-up feelings that I want to let out
sakebitai kimochi wa hora komaru hodo aru no ni
But why? Why can't you take a hint?
dou shite dou shite chitto mo aa satotte kurenai no
Hey
nee
Are you really, really in love with me?
hontou ni hontou ni watashi ni koi shiteru
You can skip the sweet talk
kosobayui kotoba wa iranai
Love me semipermanently
han'eikyuuteki ni aishite yo
I don't care about five thousand years in the future
gosennen go nado kyoumi wa nai
My life's not endless
watashi endoresu de wa nai no
I'll die someday
itsuka wa shinu no yo
Telling me you'll love me forever
eien ni aishiteru yo nante
Won't make me happy
iwarete mo ureshikunai
For now just focus on
mazu wa watashi wo shinu made
Loving me until we die
ai suru koto dake wo kangaete
My Hometown
I want a job.
It's okay!
You'll find a job before Jack Frost arrives.
Yeah.
You'll be fine, Hosshi-senpai.
Hey there, future prime minister!
Jack Frost, huh?
I wonder if he'll come.