All right! I'm better now.
Good morning, Tada-kun.
Good morning, Kaga-san.
RoboGirl?
Yes, RoboGirl.
Lately, people at the Festival Club have been calling me that.
You know, because I look like I'm dancing the robot.
Ah, yeah, it's true.
Your Awa dance is like this.
What?
I'm not that bad.
I was holding back quite a bit on my impression too.
Once summer break starts,
there's the Awa dance festival.
And...
And the beach, right?
Kaga-san...
Thanks to Kaga-san coming to see me every day,
my injury has mostly healed.
But...
I still can't ask her about the missing photo.
Did Kaga-san find out that Linda and I used to know each other?
And... that I still have feelings...
Trouble Party
for Linda?
hand in hand let's go party night
hand
in
let's
go
par
ty
night
My heart's dancing, and it won't stop
kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
We share so many memories, both happy and sad
naite waratte kimi to no kioku
I'll never forget them
zutto wasurenai
I'm supposed to find the real me and stuff
hontou no jibun wa doko ni iru to ka
Coming of age isn't easy
otona ni naru tte taihen de
But I guess I can forget about that for now
ima wa wasuretemo ii ka na
Because the night is waiting
yoru ga matte iru kara
When I think about seeing you, I get so excited
kokoro wo hazumase aeru toki wo
As I jump around in anticipation
hashagi mawareba
I might just notice the feelings inside me
tsutaetai omoi ni ima
That I want to get across to you
kizuiteshimaisou de
Even if we're afraid of the past and the future
kako to mirai osorete ite mo
We can't move on with nothing behind us
karappo no mama ja ugokenai
It's all right as long as we have fun
tanoshimeba it's all right
it's
all
right
Let's start
hajimeyou
ha
ji
me
you
When I forget everything I don't like
ya na koto zenbu wasurete
And dance through the night with you
kimi to issho ni odoriakaseba
I become a more wonderful person
motto suteki na jibun ni nareru
I can feel it
sonna ki ga suru no
let's get together
let's
ther
Our golden time will never end
owaranai golden time
time
As we pull each other closer
gyutto chikazuku kimi to no kyori wa
Not too close, not too far
tsukazu hanarezu
Even if we have to take the long way to get there
mawarimichi de mo
I'll cherish every second
taisetsu ni shitai
Hey, Banri, RoboGirl.
President, come on!
Now, now.
He calls you that with love.
Hey, Tada Banri, has your fever gone down?
Yeah.
Thanks to you guys, I'm back to normal.
Thank you for everything you and Nana-senpai have done.
Tada-kun scarfed down his oyakodon at lunch today.
He's doing fine.
Right?
Um, don't say that in front of others.
Annoying.
So annoying.
Fine. Yeah, yeah.
Stop feeling sorry for yourselves.
Let me explain the festival we'll be
participating in over summer break.
Here.
Thank you.
Awa Dance
Make sure you're aware of the date and time,
as well as your costumes, clogs, and accessories.
We actually only have two
more days to practice together.
What?!
I couldn't reserve this room.
Even if we're not that great, don't worry about it.
I'm sure Linda and I will stand out, though.
Stand out?
What do you mean?
Kosshi-senpai and I are going to be at the front.
Our outfits are fancier than yours.
That's great!
Your dancing is beautiful.
I'm sure it'll be wonderful.
Want to switch with me?
Let's do our best, Linda.
Yeah.
What am I worried about?
I don't have any reason or right to feel jealous,
no matter who Linda-senpai is friendly with.
All right, dismissed!
If you're unsure of your dancing, practice on your own.
That's all!
See you guys!
Tada-kun, let's go to a café.
I'll treat you to celebrate your recovery.
Ah, sorry, you go on ahead.
I need to talk to the seniors.
Um, Kosshi-senpai...
What's up, Tada Banri?
Ah, there's something I want to ask you.
Do you have a minute?
What's wrong?
Um, my girlfriend...
You mean RoboGirl?
I promised I'd take her to the beach,
but I'm not from the area,
so I don't know where to go.
Oh, is that right?
Ow, ow, ow!
First, spray RoboGirl with an anti-corrosive so the salty breeze won't make her rust.
Are you staying overnight? Huh?
One night, huh?
Why would you say that?!
Of course you'd want to stay.
Going to the beach makes
your hair and skin all gunky.
Those beach house showers
aren't enough for two young bodies.
She's likely to say she wants to take a bath or that she's tired.
That's what overnight facilities are for.
And that's your chance!
That's not what I wanted to ask!
I wanted to know where I should go,
and what train I should take.
Huh?
You're taking the train?
Don't you have a license?
A car?
No, neither.
Going to the beach by train is hard.
Yeah.
It's fine if you're going with guys, or with some normal, active girl.
But taking a classy girl
who wears heels all the time
on a train where she might not even get to sit...
You can't do that in college.
It'd be torture for RoboGirl.
Actually, show her what it really means to date an ordinary guy.
She might end up saying,
"RoboGirl can't take this! It's too much!"
Or something like that.
Don't you have any money?
Huh?
Of course I don't.
Maybe you should start by making some, then.
You're not working, right?
No.
You really should be.
Without money, you can't go anywhere.
If you let such a pretty girl go,
you'll never meet one like her again.
Work like your life depends on it!
You don't give the impression that you're working very hard.
Oh, I was thinking the same thing.
You might think you're working hard,
but there's no point if you don't show her that.
You've got to show her you're a man sometimes.
Right, Tada Banri?
No.
No?
No way. You can't get a job.
Yeah, but...
No way! I wouldn't get to see you as much.
Absolutely not.
I'll never allow it.
No way.
But I need money before I can take you to the beach.
I'll pay for myself.
No, I don't even have
my own spending money.
I think it's normal for students to work part-time.
I'm not working.
But you're from a rich family.
Let's do this, then.
I'll take you to the beach.
That's fine, right?
That solves it, doesn't it?
Are you saying you'll pay for me?
Ahem.
Do you actually understand, Tada-kun?
Understand what?
I want to see you more.
Do you understand that?
I want to spend a lot more time with you!
But I don't want you to think I'm annoying, so I'm holding myself back.
I'm actually pretty desperate.
You are?
When you're away, I always wonder what you're doing and thinking.
The truth is, I wish I could be with you 24 hours a day.
The things you see, hear, eat, feel...
I want to know everything.
I want to share it all.
Everything, completely.
But I know I'm awkward, overbearing, and annoying when I'm like that.
I know it's stalker-like and scary.
I've learned, haven't I?
You're right.
So if you work, I won't be able to hold myself back anymore.
What?
It makes me wish you were smaller.
About this size.
Then I could keep you with me all the time!
I'd feed you, put you to bed, change your clothes,
hide you from sight to protect you,
and keep you in my bag
so no one could steal you!
Ultimately, I'd put you on a sushi roll and eat you up.
What?
That's a rather shocking development.
Ah! You're flirting while it's still light out!
Miss Ultrasonic!
What are you doing here?
I saw you as I was walking by.
I heard from Yana.
Your injury must have been awful.
Thanks.
I'm fine now, though.
Tada-kun, let's go.
Miss Ultrasonic's exuding an extremely perverted aura.
I never thought I'd hear the words
"extremely perverted" from your mouth.
Oh, I've gotta get to work, anyway.
See?
Oka-chan works, too.
Everyone does it.
Huh?
Well...
I'm thinking of working part-time, but Kaga-san won't let me.
What?
It's normal to work.
In fact, we're looking for
part-timers at my job right now.
Do you want an interview?
What?
What? Seriously?
Really, really.
It's a café in Daikanyama.
Daikanyama...
...café?
This burlywood sofa is just like the one in my studio.
Really? Sounds nice.
Well, Banri?
It's a nice place, right?
Yeah, it is.
Excuse me.
Coming!
I'll see you later.
Tada-kun.
You definitely can't work.
What is it?
Um, thanks to you, I'm feeling better.
I thought I'd pay you back for the taxi.
Oh.
Bye.
A-Also...
What?
I'd like you to have these.
They're cookies from a café I went to today.
I'll take those.
They'll be my dinner.
Um...
You're just having those cookies for dinner?
Got a problem with that?
I should've brought you a real meal,
like bread or a boxed lunch.
I don't want you feeding me.
Of course you don't.
Is that funny?
Sorry.
Is that better now?
Ah, I'm fine.
I'm still taking my medicine, though.
Really, thank you.
If you hadn't helped me,
I would've been in deep trouble.
Make sure you thank Linda.
You owe her too.
What's with that hangdog look?
Something wrong with Linda?
Ah! No, nothing!
Um, well...
I'm kinda broke right now.
You can pay me another time.
Huh?
No, no, no, no.
That's not why I said that.
I'm looking for work now.
Work?
Yes.
This weekend...
I know a job where you can
earn a ton in one night.
Wanna be a waiter at a party?
That sounds great.
Is there an interview?
With my introduction, you'll be fine.
There's one condition, though.
Condition?
Can you bring Yanagisawa?
He's pretty good-looking, right?
A job?
Yeah. Want to join me?
I heard it's pretty good money.
Really.
Nana-senpai said something curious, though.
The job might be too much for you.
What do you think that meant?
It better not be some sketchy job!
Like something illegal or for adults only.
Hey!
It's Tada Banri and the hot sumo wrestler.
So you're looking for part-time work?
Sao-chan-senpai and...
...Shi-chan-senpai.
Want us to get you a job?
There's really well-paying
work through the Tea Club.
Wholesome and healthy manual labor.
Our male members work daily,
morning to night, drenched in sweat.
You'll stay in the mountains with fresh, clean air.
As an added bonus, you'll feel like you're on a trip.
However, you'll have to join the Tea Club.
It's 70-30, with 70 going to us.
Anyway, sign here.
Sign, sign! Sign here!
Contract
There's no way that's decent work.
We're fine.
We've already found jobs.
Bye.
Hey! Don't run!
If you don't like the mountains, there's a beach option too!
That was close.
They always try to capture us every chance they get.
I'll do Nana-senpai's job.
Anything's better than
whatever the Tea Club's offering.
Got it.
Oh, one more thing.
Huh?
Don't tell Kaga-san.
Hey.
Did you get any sleep?
I tried, but I couldn't.
Me neither.
New Message
Kaga Kouko
Nana-senpai?
Kaga-san.
Give me a minute.
She gets mad if I don't respond right away.
Oh, I can imagine.
She wanted to come over today,
but I finally got out of it by saying I wanted to focus on my report.
Let's see...
"Currently writing my report."
"May not be able to respond for a while."
Compose Message
Kaga Kouko
No Subject
Currently writing my report.
May not be able to respond for a while.
Sending Message
Kouko's clinginess is annoying, isn't it?
Actually, I don't mind it that much.
Seriously?
Yeah.
Kouko's lucky she met you.
Why?
Because, you know...
Not many people would accept her overwhelming stalker tendencies.
I love Kaga-san.
I really love her, so it's fine.
You're gushing about your girlfriend again.
It's so gross when you do that.
I want to go back to Linda.
There's a part of myself that feels that way.
Because I feel guilty over that,
I can forgive or endure anything Kaga-san does.
If that's how I feel...
I must be pretty awful.
Whoa.
This is my second time here.
Seriously?
You're Yanagisawa, huh?
Nana-senpai!
Nice to meet you.
I look forward to working with you.
You pass.
Let's go.
So! Which will it be?
Choose quickly and put it on.
Are you ready?
Yes, ready!
Ugly!
What?
But kind of sexy too.
U-Um, no one's really told us yet.
What's happening today?
A birthday party.
What?
It's my friend's birthday party.
She rented out this place for a masquerade.
I'm running it and paying for it,
so I can't have you wearing half-assed costumes!
Now, which will it be?
I really can't decide.
Damn it.
I never thought the day would come when I'd have to worry about this.
By the way, if you wear this one, I'll pay you ten thousand extra.
If you can't decide, why don't you choose that one?
They're both embarrassing anyway.
I'm surprised you're not embarrassed.
I'm a little impressed.
I'm used to it.
I've accepted who I am.
Now, Yana-san, get changed.
The party's about to start.
Got it.
I'm ready.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Thank you for coming to my dear friend Tesshi-chan's birthday!
I've pumped this party full of love and passion!
I'm gonna make you fall in love, so be ready!
Do we have to keep this up all night?
It'll be fine.
You look fantastic, Yana-san.
If Chinami saw me like this, I might die.
Oka-chan would probably accept it.
She'd laugh and say she wants to film you with the Okamera.
No way, no way, no way!
I couldn't take it!
Anyway, could you let Kouko see you like that?
I don't think Kaga-san would be opposed to this.
I'd be able to show her.
Seriously?
You really are amazing.
Well, I can't have her finding out I'm working, though.
Move your bodies, not your mouths.
Y-Yes, sir!
Yanagisawa-kun, come here.
Entertain the guests.
Wh-Wha—
Good luck, Yana-san.
He's so strong!
I see you've changed, Tada Banri.
Huh?
You're Nana-senpai, right?
Who did you think I was?
Anyway, you look ridiculous.
You look pretty crazy too.
Are you supposed to be a devil?
Apparently.
A devil twin.
Twin?
Hey, little sister.
Come here.
Banri!
Linda-senpai?
What are you doing here?
And why are you dressed like that?
What about you, Linda-senpai?
No one told me Linda-senpai would be working here.
Oh, I didn't tell you?
Well, not that it matters.
Nana-chan, come here.
Okay.
Work hard.
Don't look at me like that.
No, no, no. Don't stare at me, Linda-senpai.
You two!
Stop playing around and get back to work!
Yes, sir!
Incoming Call
Kaga Kouko
Calling...
You are being connected to an answering service.
Please leave your message after the tone.
Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
My favorite drink, a sweet caffè latte, in one hand
katate ni wa amaku shita okiniiri no kaferate
I enjoy the scent of love with a smile
hohoenda shunkan ni koi no kaori
I want to dress up perfectly
kanpeki ni kimetai no
I pick out a cherry-colored dress
cherii iro no wanpiisu
It looks neat and charming
sawayaka de tokimeite
Now I can go see you
kimi e isogou
Watch out for the sweet trap
ki wo tsukete amai wana
Yes, I'll whisper it in your ear
yes sasayaite ageru kara
Ah, I can't wait to see you
ah machidooshii kedo
What kind of smile should I greet you with?
donna egao de aeba ii
pretty love pretty love
You're so lovely
kimi ga itoshikute
under the sky under sunshine
Let's hold hands
te wo tsunagou
I can't bring myself to be honest, so take my hand
sunao ni narenai sonna watashi no te wo
And pull it toward you
hippatte ite ne
Don't Look Back
Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
Sao-chan here!
Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
Shi-chan here!
The Tea Club is recruiting strong young men to work like horses for our female members.
You, there!
Why don't you join the Tea Club?! And have a good gag ready!
Hiss!