Wait!
Resignation
Why do you have to quit the Festival Club just because we broke up?
Isn't the Festival Club important to you too?
Or is it because you can't stand being in the same club with me?
It is important.
It's an important place.
That's why I'm letting you have it.
You're the one who can't be in the same place as me.
You didn't come to our lecture earlier, either.
That's why I...
I see.
You're right.
I was shaken, and I skipped class.
It's my fault for being so pathetic.
But I understand now.
I understand why you broke up with me.
I've accepted that it was the natural choice.
Last Smile
Ah, if I met you in my dream, would I be able to say it?
aa yume no naka de aetara yueru ka na
The sorrows alone scatter down from the sky
nee kanashimi dake sora kara maiochite
That voice torments you to this day
sonna koe ga kimi wo ima de mo kurushimete
Even when I put my hand on yours, I can't get over these feelings
soba de te wo kasanetemo kono omoi wa kienai kedo
When our eyes meet, even if you don't say what you mean
futari me wo awasetara hontou no koto ienakutemo
Your words shine my world brighter than anyone else's
kimi no kotoba dare yori mo sekai wo terashiteru
Next to me, you say "Goodbye" when you mean "I love you"
tonari de kimi wa sayonara wa aishiteru tte sou iu no
I can't be honest
sunao ni narenai
When I'm singing about my loneliness alone
watashi dake kodoku wo utatte mo
I can't smile
egao ni narenai
If you say "Thanks" to mean "I'm in love with you"
arigato wa koi shiteru tte sou iu no
This is love at the end of the world
ai no world's end
You saw what was on the Okamera, didn't you?
You saw me go crazy.
I didn't tell you, but my memories have been returning lately.
When they do, my current memories disappear.
That's what happened at the Awa dance festival.
I think I'll revert to the former Tada Banri soon.
When I do, the one living here now will disappear.
You wanted to break up with me because you knew that, didn't you?
I don't think I can handle it.
I get that.
I love you, Kouko.
No matter what you say, I'll never hate you.
So you don't need to distance yourself from our friends,
and you don't need to quit the Festival Club.
You can continue being yourself.
Thanks for everything.
If you can act like you've forgotten all about what you and I had,
I won't quit the Festival Club.
I promise.
Then we're really broken up now.
From now on, we're just friends again.
Sure!
We're friends!
Can I promise one more thing?
If... If you don't forget me...
If you don't...
then I...
I promise I'll never leave you.
I'll stay with you my whole life.
I know I'm being selfish.
I know I'm not making any sense, either.
But let me promise you this.
Please.
Sure.
It's a promise.
Thank you.
Linda.
What's wrong?
I've been looking for Yanagisawa Mitsuo.
He ran off too.
I chased him, but I lost him.
And Kouko-chan...
My answer is no.
You said you were going to disappear and asked me to look after Banri.
This world doesn't move according to your wishes,
and you can't make people do what you want them to do.
Don't forget that.
Also, don't underestimate me!
It's RoboGirl!
RoboGirl's back!
Everyone welcomed us back with smiles.
Kouko revoked her resignation,
and we began preparing for the school festival again.
Yana-san.
Yana-san. Yana-san!
That night, I went to Yana-san's apartment,
I want to talk to you.
Call me.
but I didn't see him.
I want to talk to you.
Call me.
Banri
I want to talk to you.
Call me.
Banri
I want to talk to you.
Call me.
Banri
I want to talk to you.
Call me.
Banri
I want to talk to you.
The next morning,
I found the note I'd left for him stuck to my own door.
It must've been his way of saying he wouldn't listen to anything I had to say.
Yana-san also stopped coming to class,
and I couldn't find a chance to talk to him.
I went back to just being friends with Kouko.
I tried to act as naturally as possible during class and practice.
Meanwhile, the school festival was approaching.
Days Until the
Fukurai Festival:
You're late!
The coach will yell at you.
Let him.
I'd rather run outside than do strength training.
What?
What was I just thinking about?
Days Until the
Fukurai Festival:
Good morning, Banri.
What, you didn't review at home?
Banri?
Kaga-san?
K-Kaga-san?
What's wrong?
Wait! Kaga-san!
Hey, Banri.
Oh. Morning.
Don't give me that!
What did you say to Kaga-san?
She looked like she was going to cry.
Kouko was here?
I didn't notice.
Hey, are you sure everything's okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Despite her looks, Kouko is fairly...
No, no. I'm talking about you!
You're acting weird.
Haven't you noticed?
What?
Don't act like I'm not talking about you.
You spaced out earlier too.
You think so?
Seriously.
What's been going on with everyone behind my back?
You know something, Oka-chan.
I know a little,
but I don't know how much I can tell you.
I'm not trying to pry into my friends' secrets.
Still, don't you think it's a little mean to exclude me?
There are two things I do know.
Kaga-san didn't really want to break up with Banri.
I don't know what happened,
but she's really forcing herself.
You're right.
I agree.
The other thing is...
I hate the way things are now!
Days Until the
Fukurai Festival:
On that note!
Gather 'round, everyone!
Come on, Kaga-san, hurry up!
G-Good morning, Banri.
Morning.
Okay! Let's all go hang out today!
We can go to the amusement park again or get something to eat.
Let's all meet after class!
Where did this come from?
The school festival's tomorrow.
I'm busy today.
You remember our pact, don't you?
When someone says: "Let's hang out,"
we all go unconditionally!
This is one of those times!
But there's something going on between me and Yana-san right now.
Yeah.
There!
There it is!
That's creepy!
Moping around behind my back!
Because you've been acting like that,
I have to invite everyone out!
Hey. Keep your voice down.
It's fine.
I'm not making any more of a scene than you usually do.
On that note, we're going to have an honest talk tonight!
Let's all get together and lay it all on the table!
If we don't...
If we don't do it...
our group really will fall apart.
Okay.
I'm sorry for everything.
I'll definitely be there.
And I'll explain what's been going on to everyone again.
I don't know if Yana-san will come, though.
Leave him to me.
Even if I have to trick him, or lay a guilt trip on him, I'll bring Mitsuo.
We should talk things out again.
Yeah. I think it's great you'll have a chance to tell them.
Do you want to come too?
No way.
Go revive your friendships.
Well, let's do our best tomorrow.
Got it.
See you tomorrow.
Um...
Wait a minute.
Who am I waiting for?
Where am I, anyway?
What am I doing here?
I brought him, Banri.
Hey.
I tricked him into coming by telling him it was an emergency.
Now, let's have a good, honest talk today!
I'm sorry too.
After learning all that so suddenly, it took me some time to cool off.
But today, I'll listen to...
Banri?
What's wrong, Banri?
Who are you?
What?
Banri...
It's me!
Kouko! Kaga Kouko!
Look! Yanagisawa Mitsuo!
I don't know you.
I don't remember.
Who are you?
I don't know.
Linda. Linda!
Where are you?
Help me, Linda!
Linda!
Linda! Linda!
Banri!
Linda! I...
Linda...
Yeah, it's okay.
It's okay.
Let's go inside.
Linda, I want to go home.
This isn't right! It's not!
I don't know this place!
Yeah, I know. Let's go home.
I've been waiting to go home.
I know. I understand.
It's okay.
I was keeping an eye on him because I was worried about him.
I'll stay at his neighbor Nana-senpai's place tonight.
Okay, talk to you later.
Wait!
Wait, wait!
Wait! Stop the car!
I can't stop here.
Banri, calm down.
What's wrong?
I saw Kouko.
Kouko was crying!
Calm down.
It's okay.
Kouko... Kouko was...
Banri.
Kouko was...
What was I saying?
What's wrong? You don't usually call.
I'm thinking of going to the hospital.
Do you have a cold?
I think my memories from before the accident are returning.
What?
And in turn, I feel like my memories since the accident are disappearing.
I don't think I can live here anymore.
I understand.
Come on home.
Should I come get you now?
Actually, could you come see the school festival tomorrow?
The school festival?
The university's cultural festival.
We're doing the Awa dance.
Linda's doing it too.
Okay.
Your father's working, so I'll come by myself.
Then... see you tomorrow.
Keep it down.
You're kidding me!
Oh, you're awake.
Linda!
I've done it now!
I slept with Nana-senpai!
You idiot!
Ow!
Why were you sleeping in my bed, Nana-senpai?
Did you forget?
I told you last night to sleep with your door unlocked,
so I could come help if something happened.
Huh? Oh, now that you mention it...
And you weren't getting up,
so I had Nana-senpai go check on you.
You were sleeping peacefully,
so I laid down with you.
Then I just drifted off.
You shouldn't have done that, Nana-senpai.
Despite how he is, he's still a guy.
"How he is"?
Well, see you later, Banri.
Good luck with your Awa dance.
I'll go check it out.
Okay.
Nana-senpai.
Yeah?
Thanks for everything you've done for me.
Hey, I'll be seeing you again.
Bye.
I haven't told Linda and Nana-senpai yet...
that I'm planning to move out.
I wrote a bunch of notes to myself last night,
Kouko = Ex-girlfriend
for after I lose my current memories.
2D-kun
Festival Club
Soon, I'm going to forget everything that's happened since the accident.
I feel certain of that.
86th Fukurai University Festival
Banri!
Good morning, Kouko-chan.
Good morning.
Morning, Banri.
Kouko...
I just checked in on some other clubs.
She was crying yesterday.
Miss Ultrasonic looked really busy too.
Did I forget something again?
Her upperclassmen are really working her hard.
Banri!
Smile.
Today's the day.
So smile!
More.
I won't let you go until you smile more.
Don't make those noises.
It's creepy.
That's a mean thing to say.
How do I look?
Awesome.
Okay, everyone's here.
A lot happened, but we overcame it.
We overcame it all.
We're the best!
Yeah!
From all over Japan, we've gathered here...
to experience this moment together as one!
Let's dance!
Dance, dance, and enjoy this miracle with everyone!
Let's prove we're living here in this moment!
Yeah!
Okay! There's nothing left for me to say.
Let's go have fun!
Excuse us.
Do you guys have a minute?
The president of the private school committee!
What's going on?
You said you couldn't help us.
Last night, Yanagisawa-kun contacted us.
He insisted the Festival Club wasn't what we thought it was.
He asked to meet with me to clear up any misunderstandings.
Yana abandoned our club's preparations and left.
The upperclassmen were furious.
You didn't need to mention that.
After seeing the video he put together of your club practicing,
we changed our minds.
The Festival Club is doing its best to perform the Awa dance.
It was a mistake for us to break our promise to assist you at the school festival.
So I reached out to my contacts and got these instruments together.
We brought outfits too.
So will you let us play for you?
Yeah!
Yana-san.
Yana-san, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry!
Kouko told me everything.
She told me what's going on with you.
And...
I was losing sight of you.
But I found you.
I was able to find you.
It's true.
I'm watching you,
so you won't disappear.
I'll always be watching you...
and waiting for you here.
Come home anytime.
Let's meet again.
Thanks.
Good.
Yeah.
All right!
It's time!
Let's go, Festival Club!
Yeah!
The present is ending.
Here, countless versions of our past selves...
are always crying, laughing...
falling in love, getting hurt, joking around...
feeling happy, and suffering.
These feelings are born all the time, and in the next moment,
they become the past and die.
It's over now.
This is the end.
But the truth is, everyone's time is like that.
Right after it's born, every moment becomes the past and dies.
But... I'm alive now.
I'm here now.
I can see this moment, the present, right now.
Right now... isn't that everything?
After that, I returned to my former self...
and lost all my memories since the accident.
No, no, that's not what I'm getting at
chigau yo mou chigau tte ba
Ah, you still haven't noticed
aa mada kizukanai no ne
Since a couple of hours ago
nisanjikan mo mae kara
I've been dying to grab onto your arm
sono ude ni furetai no ni
I have so many pent-up feelings that I want to let out
sakebitai kimochi wa hora komaru hodo aru no ni
But why? Why can't you take a hint?
dou shite dou shite chitto mo aa satotte kurenai no
Hey
nee
Are you really, really in love with me?
hontou ni hontou ni watashi ni koi shiteru
You can skip the sweet talk
kosobayui kotoba wa iranai
Love me semipermanently
han'eikyuuteki ni aishite yo
I don't care about five thousand years in the future
gosennen go nado kyoumi wa nai
My life's not endless
watashi endoresu de wa nai no
I'll die someday
itsuka wa shinu no yo
Telling me you'll love me forever
eien ni aishiteru yo nante
Won't make me happy
iwarete mo ureshikunai
For now just focus on
mazu wa watashi wo shinu made
Loving me until we die
ai suru koto dake wo kangaete
Golden Time
My name is Tada Banri.
A lot has happened.
The day after my high school graduation...
It sure has!
Oka-chan cut her hair.
Are you listening?!
The hair on top of Mitsuo's head got thinner.
You're kidding! Where?!
Next time, Banri travels to outer space in a canoe!
You'd better not miss it!