This should be the right way.
Ow.
I'm Kaga Kouko.
Nice to meet you.
Lonely Girl
Kaga-san?
hand in hand let's go party night
hand
in
let's
go
par
ty
night
My heart's dancing, and it won't stop
kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
We share so many memories, both happy and sad
naite waratte kimi to no kioku
I'll never forget them
zutto wasurenai
I'm supposed to find the real me and stuff
hontou no jibun wa doko ni iru to ka
Coming of age isn't easy
otona ni naru tte taihen de
But I guess I can forget about that for now
ima wa wasuretemo ii ka na
Because the night is waiting
yoru ga matte iru kara
When I think about seeing you, I get so excited
kokoro wo hazumase aeru toki wo
As I jump around in anticipation
hashagi mawareba
I might just notice the feelings inside me
tsutaetai omoi ni ima
That I want to get across to you
kizuiteshimaisou de
Even if we're afraid of the past and the future
kako to mirai osorete ite mo
We can't move on with nothing behind us
karappo no mama ja ugokenai
It's all right as long as we have fun
tanoshimeba it's all right
it's
all
right
Let's start
hajimeyou
ha
ji
me
you
When I forget everything I don't like
ya na koto zenbu wasurete
And dance through the night with you
kimi to issho ni odoriakaseba
I become a more wonderful person
motto suteki na jibun ni nareru
I can feel it
sonna ki ga suru no
let's get together
let's
ther
Our golden time will never end
owaranai golden time
time
As we pull each other closer
gyutto chikazuku kimi to no kyori wa
Not too close, not too far
tsukazu hanarezu
Even if we have to take the long way to get there
mawarimichi de mo
I'll cherish every second
taisetsu ni shitai
It's been one week since I started going to college in Tokyo.
Kaga Kouko-san...
Hey, who's that hottie?
A first-year named Kaga.
I hear her parents are filthy rich!
Oh, my.
Good morning, Kaga-san.
What were you looking at on your phone?
Pictures of Mitsuo.
These are all of Yana-san?
That's right.
Mitsuo and I have been together since we were this small.
Kindergarten, elementary school,
middle school, high school,
cram school, and calligraphy school.
We did everything together.
Mitsuo and I have always been together,
and we will be forever.
That's how it should be.
Don't you agree, Takada-kun?
It's Tada.
Tada Banri.
Hey, can you get in touch with Mitsuo?
He always runs away when he sees my face.
I've been waiting for him for half an hour.
I don't know why we're attending the same university if he's going to be like this.
A-Anyway, Kaga-san, have you already got your schedule?
What do you have first period?
Sports science.
Oh, really? Me, too.
I actually wanted to take the same classes as Mitsuo,
but he won't tell me anything.
So I want to use your phone again to...
Mitsuo!
Wait, Mitsuo!
Wait, Kaga-san!
He got away from me again.
L-Listen, Kaga-san...
I don't think you need to chase him at full speed like that.
That's it, Takada-kun.
My name isn't Takada.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Tanaka-kun?
Your hint is: it's two syllables.
Two syllables.
Kaga-kun?
That's your own name.
Listen, if you figure out Mitsuo's schedule, will you tell me?
Oh, and his club!
Shouldn't you ask him about that yourself?
Even if I did, I'm sure he wouldn't tell me.
I want to know everything about Mitsuo.
I want to know how he's living on his own,
and what company he keeps!
Yeah, but...
I won't ask you to do it for free. I'll pay you...
in cash!
What?
That was a joke.
Forget it.
Go ahead.
That girl's always wearing brand name stuff from head to toe.
Her parents must be rich.
Some of you may not be familiar with the term "sports science."
Sports science is...
Wow!
Your mom made some nice choices!
Look at this ramen and instant yakisoba!
Are you sure I can have these?
Yeah, she told me to share them with my friends.
Seriously?
Anyway, are you listening to me?
I'm listening.
Kouko asked you for my schedule, right?
You didn't—
No, no, no! There's no way I'd tell her!
I know you're avoiding Kaga-san.
But I've seen Kaga-san
around during this past week.
She doesn't seem to have any friends yet.
She sits alone in her classes,
and she never gets to see you.
I kinda feel bad for her.
What?
You're sympathizing with Kouko?
A little.
Just a little, really!
Attractive people really do have it easy.
No matter what they do,
as long as they put on a pretty face,
everyone feels bad for them.
Even in high school, no one cared about me.
They all said the same things.
"Just be glad she's so hot.
I'm jealous. I wish I were you."
They should put themselves in my shoes.
What are you talking about?
I've never said any of that.
I won't tell you not to ignore Kaga-san.
That's your choice.
But feeling bad for Kaga-san is my choice too!
Well, you have a point.
The fact that I'm avoiding Kouko has nothing to do with you.
Let's not do this.
There's no point in us fighting over Kouko.
Oh...
It's almost time.
Huh? Is something happening now?
The Film Club's welcoming party.
Want to come with me?
Huh?
Golden
Time
I see! You were in a Film Club in high school too?
Yes.
You'll make a great club member!
You want to be a cameraman?
Have you used one before?
I feel kinda out of place.
Just checking it out can't hurt.
Yana!
Tada-kun, you came too.
Huh? Oka-san, you're in the Film Club?
There.
Hey, Chinami.
Wait... Huh?
You two know each other?
Since when?
We're in the same required English class.
Oh, don't call me "Oka-san."
That's what people call my mom.
Oh. In that case, Oka... chan?
Yeah, that'll do!
So, what do you think?
Do you feel like joining the Film Club now?
Well, the upperclassmen seem nice.
That's what I like to hear.
What about you, Tada-kun?
Oh, I was thinking of checking out
a few other clubs before I decided.
I see. Okay, okay.
Senpai, Yanagisawa-kun here has decided to join!
New first-years are totally welcome!
You've got a nice face!
You can be an actor!
Thanks.
Oka-chan, you're in the Film Club?
Yeah.
Anyway, that pretty girl who
was with Yana the other day...
Oh, Kaga-san?
Yeah, Kaga-san!
I wonder if she's already joined a club.
I'm not sure.
I don't think she's chosen one yet.
The upperclassmen told me the
club recruiters have a hard time talking to her.
She's kind of...
Overpowering! Out of reach!
She has an aura like that.
I wish both you and Kaga-san would join the Film Club.
Well, Yana-san is avoiding Kaga-san.
Kaga-san seems to really like Yana-san, though.
Yanagisawa-kun, do you have a girlfriend?
No, not at all!
I see.
I can't explain why, but that's youth for you.
They seem to be having fun too.
I wonder if they're throwing a welcoming party as well.
Wait, don't open that!
Beyond that door is the realm of demons!
What?
Ta-da!
I'm Sao-chan of the Tea Club!
I'm Shi-chan!
Oh, it's the Film Club!
You're throwing your own party?
Hey, you're the new student who drank our tea on the day of the entrance ceremony.
You can't get away from us now.
Come party with us!
Hey, wait.
I'm not joining the Tea Club!
There!
Hey! Help me, Yana-san! Oka-chan!
Banri!
Tada-kun!
Don't go!
You'll get sucked in too!
Banri!
Tada-kun!
Go get the pitcher.
Yes!
You, pour!
Yes.
Serve up the fish!
R-Right away!
Choose a location for the after-party!
On my way!
Dance, dance!
We're out of sake!
Tea Club bowling!
Roll, roll, roll, roll...
You smell so nice.
Come on!
Drink up, drink up, drink up!
Oh, I don't...
Then you'll fight!
Wrestle with him!
What?!
Come on!
Take it off, take it off, take it off!
Put on your loincloth!
Ready... fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Why is this happening?!
Like I know!
It's a tie!
Why is this happening?!
Like I know!
This is why I hate three-dimensional girls!
You're all weird, you jerks!
From now on, I'm going to live in the world of 2D!
I see!
Then from now on, you'll be 2D-kun.
That's fine! Call me 2D-kun!
What about you?
What's your name?
It's T-Tada Banri.
Um, I need to go back to the Film Club.
Now, now.
Don't be like that.
Hang out with us.
All right! We'll party all night long!
Yeah!
I'm in hell.
The number you are trying to reach is currently outside the service area or...
Hey, Banri.
You're alive, huh?
Yana-san.
Didn't get enough sleep?
Yeah.
I ended up going to five parties with the upperclassmen in the Tea Club.
Huh?
Kaga-san?
I'm going through the rear entrance.
Don't tell her you were with me.
O-Okay.
Also, make sure you don't tell her
I'm joining the Film Club.
I won't.
I won't...
but she waits for you every day.
You should talk to her.
It may just be a ploy to get sympathy.
You think so?
In any case, no one knows what she'll do.
You should be careful.
Later.
Fukurai University
I can finally go home.
I'm with the Social Dance Club.
You're a first-year, right?
Have you already chosen a club?
Not yet.
Join us, then!
No, join our club!
At least come check it out!
Stop!
Sorry, but this kid's joining the Festival Club.
Come on, get out of here.
What, he's already been bought up?
Hey, you, have you already joined a club?
Oh, um...
Linda.
You're Tada Banri-kun, the first-year, right?
Yeah. Thank you for saving me again.
What's that club you mentioned earlier?
The Festival Club.
I'm in it.
Its formal title is the Society for
the Cultural Study of Japanese Festivals.
I see.
You can't just wander around like that.
They pounce on defenseless first-years immediately.
I'm sorry. I didn't get enough sleep.
Are you not feeling well?
Should I go to the nurse's office with you?
No, you don't need to do that.
You're a really nice person.
Not really.
Hey, after this...
Kaga-san?
She's alone again.
You know her?
Is she your girlfriend?
N-No!
Kaga-san likes someone else,
and she's from a wealthy family!
You might say we're too different.
I didn't ask about that.
Well, whatever.
See you later.
Did you see her?
What a hottie!
She looks like a model.
Isn't she the heiress of that famous major hospital?
That's a little out of our league.
I bet she'd just ignore us.
Kaga-san!
Oh, um, Yamada-kun?
It's Tada.
Tada Banri.
I was wondering what you were doing by yourself.
Hey, do you know where Mitsuo...
Even if you did, you wouldn't
tell me, would you, Tada-kun?
Or have you changed your mind?
No, I haven't.
I thought so.
Tada Banri!
So whose welcoming party are you going to today?
Are you cheating on us?
We're throwing a party today.
You're coming, right?
No, I don't think I can do two days in a row.
Don't give me that!
You should just make up your mind and join the club!
Ow, my butt.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You had someone with you.
If you change your mind, text us.
We'll be waiting.
What was that about?
Huh?
They're in the Tea Club.
I think their names are Sao-chan and Shi-chan.
That's not what I meant.
Tada-kun, what do you think of them?
What do I think?
Tada-kun, how many clubs have tried to recruit you?
Who knows?
I couldn't count all of them.
I think the same goes for all new students.
I've had zero.
Zero?
I only took this flyer because it was lying around.
I wonder why no one tries to talk to me.
It's not as though I'm interested in clubs.
If it's not with Mitsuo,
I don't want to join any of them.
We went to school and cram school together,
and I can't imagine myself without Mitsuo.
But since coming here,
I...
I feel like I've become invisible.
It's like everyone around me is ignoring me.
Am I really that strange?
Maybe that's why Mitsuo won't talk to me.
Is this an act to make me sympathize with her?
Or is she serious?
Maybe you should try talking not just to Yana-san,
but to a lot of different people.
Try starting a conversation.
You might be right.
You could try going to the
welcoming parties of various clubs.
I'll even go with you.
Oh?
Are you interested in our club?
Sorry, I had just stepped away from the booth.
We do all kinds of things.
Simply put,
we view flowers and drink in the spring,
barbecue and drink in the summer,
pick leaves and drink in the fall,
and snowboard and drink in the winter!
It's a laid-back club!
If you're interested,
there's a great café nearby. I can tell you more there!
They serve café au lait in bowls.
It's a café au lait bowl!
Oh, I'll pay, so don't worry.
Then that's that!
Come on, let's go!
Whoa!
Tada-kun, my bag!
Huh?!
Oh...
I see.
You haven't joined any clubs yet.
In that case, you should definitely join ours.
We get lots of information about lectures and exams.
And we have lots of retired members who can help you find work.
I highly recommend it!
You'll also get a lot of privileges if you join.
The truth is, I'm a student at a different university.
Talking to people from other universities is mentally stimulating.
Some questionable clubs won't let you quit once you join,
but we're not like that.
Every year, we hold our welcoming party at a seminar house.
It's three days and two nights.
We leave Saturday afternoon, get there in the evening, have dinner,
and party!
Oh, we come back early on Monday morning, so don't worry.
We don't ask new students for money, so you can take it easy.
You'll come, right?
It's a done deal, right?
Meet us in front of the main entrance tomorrow!
You'll have tons of fun! Look forward to it!
Okay?
I guess we're going.
Yeah, she was really intense.
Trying stuff like this isn't so bad, though.
We can decide later if we want to join.
You're right.
We have this opportunity,
and everything is an experience.
Well, this is as far as I go.
I'll see you tomorrow, Tada-kun.
Okay.
She feels invisible, huh?
My favorite drink, a sweet caffè latte, in one hand
katate ni wa amaku shita okiniiri no kaferate
I enjoy the scent of love with a smile
hohoenda shunkan ni koi no kaori
I want to dress up perfectly
kanpeki ni kimetai no
I pick out a cherry-colored dress
cherii iro no wanpiisu
It looks neat and charming
sawayaka de tokimeite
Now I can go see you
kimi e isogou
Watch out for the sweet trap
ki wo tsukete amai wana
Yes, I'll whisper it in your ear
yes sasayaite ageru kara
Ah, I can't wait to see you
ah machidooshii kedo
What kind of smile should I greet you with?
donna egao de aeba ii
pretty love pretty love
You're so lovely
kimi ga itoshikute
under the sky under sunshine
Let's hold hands
te wo tsunagou
I can't bring myself to be honest, so take my hand
sunao ni narenai sonna watashi no te wo
And pull it toward you
hippatte ite ne
Night Escape
Three days and two nights with Kaga-san.
With Kaga-san...
It's not like I'm excited about that!