Linda's late.
What? But you and Banri-senpai are so close!
You always go home together.
We were convinced you were dating.
Cut it out.
I mean, are you guys stupid?
I look out for him.
You know, Banri's unreliable.
I can't just leave him alone.
I see.
You're saying you can't leave
Banri-senpai alone because you like him.
No!
I don't even see him as a guy in the first place.
There you go again.
You actually like him, don't you?
No! No!
I don't like him at all!
Come on. Let's go home.
Banri, wait!
Hey, Banri!
Wait, Banri!
Hey, Banri...
Banri, about the other day...
I don't like him at all!
It's so cold.
It's actually the opposite, Banri.
Sometimes... I'm really stupid.
Forgive me for being stupid.
I won't.
I don't like you at all, either.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry, Banri.
Forget it.
Let's go home.
Okay.
At that moment, I think a fire was lit in my heart.
Linda said she didn't like me at all.
If those words were the opposite of how she really felt,
Reset
then maybe Linda...
hand in hand let's go party night
hand
in
let's
go
par
ty
night
kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
My heart's dancing, and it won't stop
naite waratte kimi to no kioku
We share so many memories, both happy and sad
zutto wasurenai
I'll never forget them
hontou no jibun wa doko ni iru to ka
I'm supposed to find the real me and stuff
otona ni naru tte taihen de
Coming of age isn't easy
ima wa wasuretemo ii ka na
But I guess I can forget about that for now
yoru ga matte iru kara
Because the night is waiting
kokoro wo hazumase aeru toki wo
When I think about seeing you, I get so excited
hashagi mawareba
As I jump around in anticipation
tsutaetai omoi ni ima
I might just notice the feelings inside me
kizuiteshimaisou de
That I want to get across to you
kako to mirai osorete ite mo
Even if we're afraid of the past and the future
karappo no mama ja ugokenai
We can't move on with nothing behind us
tanoshimeba it's all right
It's all right as long as we have fun
it's
all
right
hajimeyou
Let's start
ha
ji
me
you
ya na koto zenbu wasurete
When I forget everything I don't like
kimi to issho ni odoriakaseba
And dance through the night with you
motto suteki na jibun ni nareru
I become a more wonderful person
sonna ki ga suru no
I can feel it
let's get together
let's
ther
owaranai golden time
Our golden time will never end
time
gyutto chikazuku kimi to no kyori wa
As we pull each other closer
tsukazu hanarezu
Not too close, not too far
mawarimichi de mo
Even if we have to take the long way to get there
taisetsu ni shitai
I'll cherish every second
What?
Yana-san left early?
Yes.
So, Tada-kun, will you go check on Mitsuo for me?
I mean, there's no way I can go.
Why not?
I can't go to another man's place when I have a boyfriend.
Going behind closed doors with a
member of the opposite sex is cheating.
Y-You're right.
I'm going next door.
Later.
Tada-kun, are you listening?
I'm listening.
Okay.
I'll go check on him.
Yeah.
I haven't forgotten my feelings for Linda.
Got it.
I'll call you later.
Not even now, as a ghost.
Okay.
But that has nothing to do
with the current Tada Banri.
Bye.
The current Banri... is dating Kaga Kouko.
Let's see.
Is this it?
Come on, Yana.
Let me in.
No, seriously.
I'm not feeling well today.
You shouldn't push yourself so hard.
Um...
I thought I'd make you dinner.
Do you like meat and potatoes?
No, I really...
I don't have anything to do today.
I was thinking I could stay over.
Seriously, seriously, seriously, seriously...
Hi, Yana-san!
What?
Banri?
My boyfriend!
Wait, what?
He's my boyfriend.
No one can come between us.
We're lovers from a past life.
Right?
Yeah!
I was a shepherd in a past life.
And I was a nun at a convent.
Gross!
There's something wrong with you two!
Y-You saved me.
Who was she?
Reina-senpai from the Film Club.
I was scared.
She was shoving her cleavage in my face.
Right.
Whoa...
This room is a mess.
Thanks.
Thanks for coming over.
Kaga-san told me.
Something happened with Oka-chan again?
Yes.
Hey, Yana!
You won't get away today.
Chinami, wait.
Sorry, but could you not talk to me?
A lot of people know about
what happened at the party.
Do you mean forever?
Forever.
If that's what you want, then fine.
H-Hi.
When did you get here?
You're the one who just sat down next to me.
Hey, that's...
It's the guy who confessed to Chinami
at the party and got shot down on the spot.
Ouch.
Yana-san?
Everyone around me seems
to know that Chinami rejected me.
No matter what I do, I feel so self-conscious.
I see.
I know.
I should act normal around Chinami, like nothing ever happened.
But I freak out every time I see her.
I feel embarrassed and sad.
I'm the worst.
I understand how you feel.
Yana-san, look at yourself!
I've got seaweed in my teeth.
It's from the sushi I bought at the convenience store.
That's not what I meant!
You're attractive! You should have more confidence in yourself!
In any case, you can't keep acting like this.
Just like Linda-senpai helped me,
it's my turn to help you.
What did Linda-senpai do?
Hello, 2D-kun?
Listen, I want to throw a party to cheer up Yana-san.
National Gourmet Festival
Get a One-Day Pass and enjoy up
to 27 rides all you want!
Hey! Tada-kun, you're fifteen minutes late!
Sorry.
Just kidding.
I'm not mad.
I'm happy to see you, Tada-kun.
I'm happy to see you, Yana-san.
I'm...
not happy.
That's cold!
Look, I appreciate what you're all trying to do...
but I don't get why she's here.
When Banri called me,
I had just left class with Kaga-san,
and she overheard.
I just want to be with Tada-kun all the time.
I don't care about you.
Going to an amusement park was my suggestion.
If you don't like it, why don't you go home?
You're only getting in the way here.
Wait, wait, wait!
Kaga-san!
Oka Chinami
Wh-What should I do?
It's Oka-chan.
Should I answer? Should I answer?
Yana-san.
I...
I... I...
National Gourmet Festival
Get a One-Day Pass and enjoy up
to 27 rides all you want!
It's me.
We're throwing a party to cheer up Mitsuo.
You should come too.
I don't want you to come,
but I'm reluctantly inviting you for Mitsuo's sake.
You...
Hello?
Yeah, that's right.
I used up some of my kindness on Mitsuo again.
We're at...
Replenish!
You!
What did you just do?
You heard me.
So what are you going to do?
Leave? Or stay?
Hello, Oka-chan?
Yeah.
We'll be waiting at the ticket gate.
Bye.
I wish I could've come only with you.
Let's come back together sometime, then.
The pool will be opening soon.
Or would you rather go to the beach?
Oh, my!
The beach with you!
What should I do? I'm so excited!
Banri!
Kaga-san, you came to meet me too.
Thanks.
That phone call really surprised me.
I was shocked when Kaga-san suddenly answered and said Yana was there.
I knew I had to go.
I was pretty flustered.
See?
I brought this.
Noodles?
I see.
You really were flustered.
Oh, yeah! I heard you two are dating now!
Oh, you knew?
2D-kun told me the other day.
I've seen you holding hands too.
You saw that?
I sure did.
I didn't actually want you to come.
I want you to stay out of my sight.
Kaga-san, you invited her.
I just pitied Mitsuo because he's hurt.
He's my childhood friend, after all.
You can see him,
but don't hurt him anymore.
If you can't do that, leave.
Why would you say that?
It doesn't have anything to do with you.
Whatever happens between me
and Yana has nothing to do with you.
You're dating Banri, right?
Why don't you pay more
attention to what you have?
Give me back my noodles.
A-Are you okay?
No way.
Thank you for visiting
It's okay.
It's not broken.
I wonder if it still works.
This is Kaga-san, Kaga Kouko.
This is my first time filming her with the Okamera.
Hello.
Hey, Kaga-san, it's hard for me too.
I know it may not seem that way.
After all...
After all, Yana said...
He told me to never speak to him again.
No!
I'm the only one who can act cute and cry in front of Tada-kun!
Suck it up!
I'll keep doing this until you stop crying!
K-Kaga-san!
You're suffocating Oka-chan!
Let me know when you're done crying!
I'm going to keep doing this until you do!
You're going to kill Oka-chan!
Are you done crying?
A-Are you alive?
Hey, Banri, don't I look really funny right now?
What? You want me to film you?
Seriously?
Yeah, seriously.
O-Okay.
Kaga-san, could you try letting go?
It feels really stable right now.
Here we go.
Expiration Date
Steamed
Keep Refrigerated
Expiration Date
Steamed
Keep Refrigerated
Expiration Date
Steamed
Keep Refrigerated
Expiration Date
Steamed
Keep Refrigerated
Thank you for visiting
What am I doing?
W-Well, then.
What should we ride first?
A roller coaster!
Haunted House
Have they made up?
Tada-kun, look only at me.
Cheers!
Oh, that's called Face Yakisoba.
Face Yakisoba?
Yeah.
What kind of name is that?
Is it good, Yana-san?
Have some.
Thank you.
Yeah, it's good.
Hey, why don't we make a pact?
A pact?
Yeah.
If any of us ever decides to hang out
or go drinking, like today,
we'll all try to go.
That way, we'll always have
a few people to hang out with.
I'm in.
If Tada-kun's in, I'm in.
I don't like that Mitsuo's involved, though.
I could say the same about you.
Count me in, too.
Ready, and...
Yeah!
Is anyone awake?
Linda-senpai
No subject
Are you awake?
Sending Message
Linda-senpai.
Banri.
Can I speak casually with you, just for now?
It feels more right that way.
You guys were noisy.
Were you in Nana-senpai's room this whole time?
Yeah.
I was just reminiscing about you.
So I really freaked out when I got your text.
How did you know I was awake?
I didn't know.
I just felt like you were.
You've always been like that.
Sometimes we'd go on trips with our club.
Whenever I couldn't sleep,
you'd come into the girls' room and ask,
"Hey, Linda, are you awake?"
What?
So I was a pervert?
You did cause trouble doing that, but you'd nervously tell me,
"I can't sleep. I'm going to be
exhausted at practice tomorrow."
Whoa.
Yeah, I definitely had some naughty intentions.
Seriously?
Then when my panties went missing, could you have...
Huh?
I'm kidding.
You know... for some reason...
What?
I think I used to like you then.
Saying I couldn't sleep was just an excuse.
I think I had a sort of perverted desire to watch you sleep.
So... sorry about that.
We should've talked about the past like this from the beginning.
Once you miss the opportunity to say something, the words become increasingly toxic.
The best thing to do is to come clean about everything.
There's nothing between us that we can't say anymore.
We haven't changed.
We're still alive.
We're looking at the same sky.
That hasn't changed at all.
Banri?
There's something I haven't asked you yet.
What?
I was wondering...
what your answer was to my
confession the day after graduation.
That's obvious.
It was "no."
I just couldn't think of you romantically.
I was going to tell you that
we should stay friends.
I see.
Linda-senpai.
Do you want to go back?
To the place where I used to be.
I...
I want to go back!
What did I just say?
Wow, you fell asleep for a second.
Fell asleep?
Looks like you should get to bed.
Lack of sleep isn't good for you.
You'll become oversensitive
and think things you shouldn't.
Good night, Tada Banri.
I still love Linda.
If I can, I want to be with Linda forever.
But I can't leave you.
If I do, I'll disappear.
I feel like I will.
katate ni wa amaku shita okiniiri no kaferate
My favorite drink, a sweet caffè latte, in one hand
hohoenda shunkan ni koi no kaori
I enjoy the scent of love with a smile
kanpeki ni kimetai no
I want to dress up perfectly
cherii iro no wanpiisu
I pick out a cherry-colored dress
sawayaka de tokimeite
It looks neat and charming
kimi e isogou
Now I can go see you
ki wo tsukete amai wana
Watch out for the sweet trap
yes sasayaite ageru kara
Yes, I'll whisper it in your ear
ah machidooshii kedo
Ah, I can't wait to see you
donna egao de aeba ii
What kind of smile should I greet you with?
pretty love pretty love
kimi ga itoshikute
You're so lovely
under the sky under sunshine
te wo tsunagou
Let's hold hands
sunao ni narenai sonna watashi no te wo
I can't bring myself to be honest, so take my hand
hippatte ite ne
And pull it toward you
With You Again
Oh, wow!
Tada-kun, you're so good at impersonating me.
Mitsuo, your room is filthy, and your feet stink.
Butt chin!
Yana-san, back to your house!
Your house!