When Kaga-san and I were lost in the mountains,
Linda-senpai happened to show up and help us.
Linda-senpai had come to the university's seminar house
for an overnight trip with the Festival Club.
We had somehow ended up near the seminar house.
Blackout
hand in hand let's go party night
hand
in
let's
go
par
ty
night
My heart's dancing, and it won't stop
kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
We share so many memories, both happy and sad
naite waratte kimi to no kioku
I'll never forget them
zutto wasurenai
I'm supposed to find the real me and stuff
hontou no jibun wa doko ni iru to ka
Coming of age isn't easy
otona ni naru tte taihen de
But I guess I can forget about that for now
ima wa wasuretemo ii ka na
Because the night is waiting
yoru ga matte iru kara
When I think about seeing you, I get so excited
kokoro wo hazumase aeru toki wo
As I jump around in anticipation
hashagi mawareba
I might just notice the feelings inside me
tsutaetai omoi ni ima
That I want to get across to you
kizuiteshimaisou de
Even if we're afraid of the past and the future
kako to mirai osorete ite mo
We can't move on with nothing behind us
karappo no mama ja ugokenai
It's all right as long as we have fun
tanoshimeba it's all right
it's
all
right
Let's start
hajimeyou
ha
ji
me
you
When I forget everything I don't like
ya na koto zenbu wasurete
And dance through the night with you
kimi to issho ni odoriakaseba
I become a more wonderful person
motto suteki na jibun ni nareru
I can feel it
sonna ki ga suru no
let's get together
let's
ther
Our golden time will never end
owaranai golden time
time
As we pull each other closer
gyutto chikazuku kimi to no kyori wa
Not too close, not too far
tsukazu hanarezu
Even if we have to take the long way to get there
mawarimichi de mo
I'll cherish every second
taisetsu ni shitai
Tada Banri!
I'm glad you're okay.
I was worried about what might've happened to you and Kaga-san.
I was relieved to hear from you.
Sorry to make you worry.
I'm glad you're all right.
Tada-kun!
Banri.
Yana-san, Oka-chan.
I see.
So you went on the same trip with them.
It sounds like a rough time.
It was.
I couldn't stop worrying about Banri and Kaga-san.
I was worried too.
I texted you and Kouko a few times,
but you didn't answer.
You texted Kaga-san?
I couldn't help worrying.
We're old friends.
I see.
I'm sure Kaga-san must have been overjoyed.
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
You're going on an overnight trip?
No subject
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
You're going on an overnight trip?
No subject
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
No subject
You're going on an overnight trip?
Well, I've got class. I'm going to go.
Sure, see you later.
Bye bye, 2D-kun!
Kaga-san did a lot of introspection.
She said she's done a lot of
things to make you hate her.
Ah, youth.
Hey, Chinami, don't you have class?
Nope! I'm free until this afternoon!
Hang out with us, then.
All right!
What are you doing, Mitsuo?
How is that your business?
K-Kaga-san.
It is my business.
I don't want my boyfriend speaking to other girls.
I'm not your boyfriend.
How many times do I have to tell you that talking is cheating?
How many times do I have to tell you that I'm not your boyfriend?
I don't want you to do things I don't like.
Why are you not even hearing me?
Because I didn't ask for your opinion.
What's going on?
What is that thing?
Do you mean me?
Where are you speaking from?
M-My mouth.
Your mouth!
That voice is coming from your mouth?
How does that work?
Hey.
I don't care how mysterious creatures do what they do,
but keep your hands off Mitsuo.
That's not a request.
It's an order.
Mitsuo isn't just my boyfriend.
I plan on marrying him.
It's been decided by fate.
Anyway, we live in a different world from you.
Do you understand?
I insist you understand here and now!
Kaga-san.
Stop it, Kouko.
What's your name?
O-Oka Chinami.
What kind of name is that?
I don't know what that's supposed to mean, but call yourself whatever you want.
Live however you'd like.
Do what you want.
Um, my foot...
But do it in a world that has nothing to do with ours.
Don't butt in, don't get in our way, and don't come near Mitsuo.
Then—
I just wanted to warn you.
Next time, you won't get off so easily.
That's enough.
Just go.
Mitsuo, you texted me.
Thank you.
Listen, about that...
Chinami.
Banri!
Um...
I want to talk to Kaga-san
about thanking the Festival Club.
Fine.
Kaga-san, did you really have to...
And do you really have to do that?!
Are you hiding your armpit sweat?
You do realize you went too far.
You look like a toad.
Are you okay?
I think I should wipe off my sweat in the bathroom.
Ten minutes.
Thanks for waiting.
Are—
Don't ask me if I'm okay.
I'm fine.
But—
Don't "but" me.
I'm fine.
Kaga—
Don't ask me what I was doing.
Don't tell me I was being stupid.
I know I'm dumb.
Yes, I made a huge mistake.
I made him hate me again today.
I've been doing the same thing for years.
But I couldn't stop myself.
I couldn't turn back.
After all, I'm an idiot!
I'm sorry.
I don't mind.
You wanted to thank the people from the Festival Club, right?
Yeah.
I texted Linda-senpai.
I thought we could go see her during lunch.
You're right.
I'll go with you.
I told the Student Affairs Office about yesterday.
I said some weird organization had infiltrated the school.
Thank you for taking care of that.
The people who tried to recruit you
have been causing problems at other schools.
They make you buy really
expensive accessories and charms.
They even run pyramid schemes.
Whoa.
I'm glad you got out safely.
Thank you so much.
I'm sure this is more than just a coincidence.
Why don't you join our club?
Um...
I'd like to check it out before I decide.
I understand!
Well, we'd be glad to have you.
We didn't get too many new members this year.
The Festival Club usually practices in that ward assembly hall.
Make sure you remember.
Don't forget, Tada Banri.
What's wrong, Tada-kun?
Nothing.
What brought that on?
I almost remembered something just now.
I brought the kids from yesterday.
Oh, good work.
Excuse us.
Thank you for yesterday.
I'm glad you're all right.
I'm the president, Koshino.
Third year.
Everyone calls him Kosshi-senpai.
As long as you're here, why don't you jump in?
We were just practicing our Awa dance.
I had no idea Awa dancing was so difficult.
Kaga-san, you looked like
you were dancing the robot.
Are you joining the Festival Club, Tada-kun?
Yeah.
It seemed like fun.
I might.
I can't.
I'm not confident enough.
Besides, I intend to join the same club as Mitsuo.
Kaga-san.
I won't give up.
I'll win Mitsuo over!
I'm going home.
Thanks for everything.
Bye.
As first-year law students,
you'll spend the next four years studying law.
Is Chinami-chan your girlfriend?
She's three-dimensional, but she's cute.
She's not my girlfriend yet!
It'd be nice if it worked out.
Is Chinami-chan your girlfriend?
She's three-dimensional, but she's cute.
She's not my girlfriend yet!
It'd be nice if it worked out.
Is Chinami-chan your girlfriend?
She's three-dimensional, but she's cute.
She's not my girlfriend yet!
It'd be nice if it worked out.
Is Chinami-chan your girlfriend?
She's three-dimensional, but she's cute.
She's not my girlfriend yet!
It'd be nice if it worked out.
While we call it the study of law,
it actually encompasses a variety of studies.
She's more than just cute. She's funny, has a good
personality, and is smart. She's everything I want!!!!!
For example, there is positive law, basic law, the philosophy of law,
legal history, and comparative law.
She's more than just cute. She's funny, has a good
personality, and is smart. She's everything I want!!!!!
What are you going to do about Kaga-san?
Fields of study are further subdivided within these categories.
Wasn't Kaga-san a childhood friend?
As you advance in your studies,
Kaga-san is in love with Yana-san.
Wasn't Kaga-san a childhood friend?
you will be required to choose a specialty.
What?!
Without becoming too attached to your specialty,
I'll make it clear to Kouko!
I'll make sure she understands.
I want a serious
relationship with Chinami!!
we hope you will approach law with a broad perspective.
Laws are the rules of society, and...
Kaga-san didn't come to college once that week.
Yo!
Even when I texted her, she only told me not to worry.
Hey!
Kaga Kouko
No subject
Don't worry.
Then on Saturday, she invited me out.
You must've been lonely without
any contact from me for four days.
I had to prepare for something.
I intend to settle things once and for all today.
Listen, should I really be here?
Stay.
You're our witness.
I'm about to prove that
Mitsuo and I should be together.
Sorry, but we need you to stick around.
Why is the mood so combative?
First, our birthplaces.
Kaga Household
Yanagisawa Household
This is the Kaga household.
This is the Yanagisawa household.
They're 800 meters apart,
in the same school district.
Even if we had attended public school, it was highly likely we would meet.
In other words, it was
inevitable that we would meet.
This is the entrance ceremony.
This is a picture of our field trip.
The sports festival, camp school, graduation.
They're all pictures of us together.
So?
We've been together since we were children.
Do you remember how I confessed my feelings for you in first grade?
You said you liked me too.
You said you loved me
and asked me to be your wife.
We were just acting for our Christmas party.
You're embellishing facts to suit yourself.
That was when I decided to marry you.
I've told you over and over. I don't intend to marry you.
Listen, Kouko.
We've never even dated.
We played together when we were little,
but we're not kids anymore.
"I like Mister Giraffe,
Mister Elephant, and Kouko-chan."
I'm past the age of saying that.
That's not true at all.
Our relationship is destined, eternal, and absolute.
I'm sick of your assumptions!
I want to go home.
There's a girl I like.
It's me, isn't it?
You met her on Monday.
Oka Chinami.
If you bother Chinami again,
I'll never forgive you.
Why?
Kaga-san.
But...
I don't understand.
Am I not special?
Who cheered you up when you cried because you didn't win a gold medal in calligraphy?
Who baked you a cake to congratulate you
when you were chosen to run in the relay race at the Sports Festival?
You did.
I was chosen to be the anchor for the girls, and we took first place.
I ran faster than everyone else
because I thought you were watching,
and I could hear you cheering for me.
The reason I can run fast,
the reason I want to be beautiful,
and the one I want to love... It's all you, Mitsuo.
I should be with you.
That's why I tried so hard to be perfect.
So why... am I not special?
Am I not important to you at all?
You're an idiot.
You've never tried to understand me.
You were always about yourself.
That's why you don't get it.
You are important to me.
That's why I can't date you just for the sake of it.
You're special, but you can't be my girlfriend.
I can't think of you as my soul mate.
Even if I dated you out of pity,
I don't think it would make you happy.
If I'm important...
If I'm special, how is that different from loving me?
Can't that be part of loving me?
Can't you...
fall in love with me and marry me?
Is it because of everything
I've done to make you hate me?
Do all our memories count for nothing?
If that's the case...
Kaga-san.
I don't need you anymore!
Forget everything!
Act like it never happened!
If there's no fixing it, just forget everything!
What have I done?
I'm sorry, Tada-kun.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Kaga-san?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry!
The old Tada Banri disappeared from this world.
It's okay, Kaga-san.
I'm sorry.
It's really okay.
You don't need to worry about me now.
I'm sorry, Tada-kun.
Kaga-san, we should get going.
I want to die.
Kaga-san...
Here.
I'm performing in that concert tonight at nine.
If you're going to die, die by music.
Um, who are you?
I'm Nana.
What? Nana?
Come and die.
I will.
Hey, are you really going?
If I can't be perfect, I'm better off falling apart completely.
But...
You don't need to come with me, Tada-kun.
I'm coming with you.
Thank you.
I'm falling apart!
Kaga-san!
Mitsuo's a moron!
I'm going to die!
Don't screw with me!
Ow...
Take her away.
This stage is mine.
Kaga-san, are you okay?
I can't move.
Oh, wow.
This room is filthy.
Kaga-san.
You heard what Mitsuo said.
He won't date me because
it wouldn't make me happy.
When he said that,
I realized I've never thought about Mitsuo's happiness.
I've just been pursuing him and telling him that I love him.
I just wanted to do things according to my plan.
If the person you love doesn't love you back,
you're worthless.
That's what I told myself.
I only insisted Mitsuo love me, accept me, and not reject me,
because I was forcing that conviction on him.
Took me long enough to notice, huh?
I think everyone's like that to some extent.
Really? Even you, Tada-kun?
It's difficult for me to accept the new me,
when everyone else rejects it.
I mean, my amnesia.
When I'm with my family,
I can tell.
They're waiting for the old me, the real Tada Banri, to return.
The personality that disappeared might simply come back one day.
If that happens, my current self will vanish.
But that would make everyone happy, right?
If I stay the way I am,
everyone will continue to be disappointed.
I...
I'm not disappointed.
What?
I'm not.
I'll never be disappointed.
After all, if you disappear,
who am I supposed to share my disgraceful self with tonight?
There's no one else.
There's only you, Tada-kun.
So don't disappear.
I...
I know I'm an idiot...
but don't forget about me.
I won't forget.
There's no way I'd forget.
Because... I...
I like you, Kaga-san.
I like you, Kaga Kouko.
I really do.
But it's not fair for me to confess to you now, is it?
Sorry.
I won't ask you to forget, though.
Anyway, tomorrow...
T-Tomorrow?
Wh-What's happening tomorrow?
We left our bags in a locker.
O-Our bags?
We're always running away without our bags, aren't we?
You're right.
I actually enjoy it, though.
It seems everything turns out fine, no matter what I leave behind.
I seem to be surprisingly strong.
You know, I lost my shoes again.
I'm going to go.
Do you know the way?
Should I go with you?
No, I'll be fine by myself.
Besides, I don't want you to see how I look now.
You can use my sandals.
Thanks.
Kaga Kouko
Worrying about rejection may be the same as rejecting yourself.
No Subject
I'm home.
Why are you here?
I didn't have anything to do, so I came home.
You did what?
If you're coming home, you should've called.
Are you hungry?
Do you want something to eat?
Yeah, sure.
Tada Banri in high school.
Tada Banri
Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
What? What is this?
Linda-senpai?
Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
Make sure you remember.
Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
Don't forget, Tada Banri.
Stupid Linda
Dumb Banri
My favorite drink, a sweet caffè latte, in one hand
katate ni wa amaku shita okiniiri no kaferate
I enjoy the scent of love with a smile
hohoenda shunkan ni koi no kaori
I want to dress up perfectly
kanpeki ni kimetai no
I pick out a cherry-colored dress
cherii iro no wanpiisu
It looks neat and charming
sawayaka de tokimeite
Now I can go see you
kimi e isogou
Watch out for the sweet trap
ki wo tsukete amai wana
Yes, I'll whisper it in your ear
yes sasayaite ageru kara
Ah, I can't wait to see you
ah machidooshii kedo
What kind of smile should I greet you with?
donna egao de aeba ii
pretty love pretty love
You're so lovely
kimi ga itoshikute
under the sky under sunshine
Let's hold hands
te wo tsunagou
I can't bring myself to be honest, so take my hand
sunao ni narenai sonna watashi no te wo
And pull it toward you
hippatte ite ne
Body and Soul
Mitsuo here.
Despite everything,
Kouko's still my childhood friend,
and I worry about her sometimes.
Hey, wait! Kouko!
Back to your house! Your house!
Not that way!