I'm glad the sun's out.
Yeah.
It's a perfect day for a dip in the sea.
Are you wearing your swimsuit under your clothes?
Of course.
It's a bikini.
What about you, Banri?
Are you wearing a jockstrap?
It's a swimsuit.
I'm wearing a Speedo.
Wow, a Speedo!
Wait, really?
I am, in place of a jockstrap.
Oh...
Anyway, I'm more worried about something else.
Oh, good.
The innocent pair's in here too.
Isn't that Mitsuo's swimsuit?
She can tell from just one look?
She really is a professional stalker.
Hey, did Mitsuo say anything?
Like what?
You mean about that time?
Yes, that time.
We decided to keep quiet and just watch, right?
Yana-san didn't say anything, and neither did I.
You're right.
I know.
I know...
but it doesn't feel right.
Just so you know,
I'm not saying this because I still have feelings for Mitsuo or anything.
I wasn't thinking that.
I'm actually more worried about how Miss Ultrasonic feels.
If Mitsuo and Linda-senpai are becoming an item,
she must be feeling something.
Who knows?
I don't like Miss Ultrasonic at all.
In fact, I hate her...
but I can imagine how she feels.
She rejected him once,
but just when she smugly thought that she'd tolerate his presence,
or that she had room to breathe, this happened!
That's what Oka-chan is like in your mind?
Because she was slow,
a mature older woman stole him away.
That has to hurt.
Maybe she didn't think Mitsuo would meet someone like Linda-senpai.
Linda-senpai's a wonderful person.
Anyone would fall in love with her, right?
Listen. Just so you know...
you're the one I love, Kouko.
That's the one thing I'm sure of.
Yeah, I know.
Accident Beach
Ah, if I met you in my dream, would I be able to say it?
aa yume no naka de aetara yueru ka na
The sorrows alone scatter down from the sky
nee kanashimi dake sora kara maiochite
That voice torments you to this day
sonna koe ga kimi wo ima de mo kurushimete
Even when I put my hand on yours, I can't get over these feelings
soba de te wo kasanetemo kono omoi wa kienai kedo
When our eyes meet, even if you don't say what you mean
futari me wo awasetara hontou no koto ienakutemo
Your words shine my world brighter than anyone else's
kimi no kotoba dare yori mo sekai wo terashiteru
Next to me, you say "Goodbye" when you mean "I love you"
tonari de kimi wa sayonara wa aishiteru tte sou iu no
I can't be honest
sunao ni narenai
When I'm singing about my loneliness alone
watashi dake kodoku wo utatte mo
I can't smile
egao ni narenai
If you say "Thanks" to mean "I'm in love with you"
arigato wa koi shiteru tte sou iu no
This is love at the end of the world
ai no world's end
2D-kun's late.
I wonder what happened.
Who knows?
He said he'd meet us at the bus stop.
This should be the right place.
I'll look for him.
I'm going with you.
2D-kun!
I finally found you.
I meant that one.
The shuttle bus stop.
Who doesn't check their voice mail
when it's 20 minutes past the meeting time?
I called you over and over
while I was driving around looking for you.
Sorry.
My phone was in my bag, so I didn't hear it.
And why are you sitting like you're in a taxi?
Huh?
You guys can be like that sometimes.
I feel like you don't show me any consideration.
Sorry.
There, there.
You can have these.
What am I, a kid?
Open wide.
Kouko?
I felt like I was hit in the face with a blast of hot air!
The air conditioning is broken.
Hello?
Oka-chan?
Some stuff came up.
We're going to be about 30 more minutes.
Okay, I'll pass the time in a café close by.
Call me when you get here.
Got it.
Later.
There you go.
I wonder if we'll get there in 30 minutes.
The number you are trying to reach is currently outside the service area...
You can't reach her?
Yeah.
Maybe she doesn't realize her phone's not getting service.
Man, what the hell?!
We know she's around here, right?
I'll go look for her.
This is why I hate the 3D world.
Uh...
Want some?
They're taking forever.
We still have to go to Yana-san's place too.
Why did Yana-san have to go back home today of all days?
We have to go out of our way for him.
He said it'd just be while his dad was on a business trip.
His timing sucks.
We haven't been cursed or something, have we?
Come on, try to think positive!
After all, we're going to the beach!
Thanks for waiting.
Scoot over, Banri.
Morning! Sorry.
I was seated downstairs and didn't realize there was no service.
Basements have a lot of junk blocking the signal, right?
Yeah.
Again, why are you sitting like you're in a taxi?
Oka-chan, you're wearing a skirt today!
Yeah, so it's easier to change.
I'm wearing my swimsuit under my clothes.
All right, let's go!
I see...
You're wearing a swimsuit under your skirt, huh?
That's right.
So tell me, Chinami. Are you wearing a school swimsuit?
I thought about it for a second,
but I ended up wearing a normal one.
So tell me, Chinami, are you worried because you forgot your panties?
I never forget to bring anything.
I see, I see.
That's a shame.
Why?!
What time is it?
10:30.
We're two hours behind schedule.
My luck's really off today.
Hey. You guys took a while.
All right! I get shotgun!
Not a word about Linda-senpai.
I know.
My lips are sealed.
Let's go, okay?
It's been a while, hasn't it?
I saw Banri the other day, though.
Y-You're right.
It's been a while, Yanao.
I mean, Mitsuo.
What's wrong with you?
You're kinda stuttery.
What? No, I'm not.
Come on, Miss Ultrasonic.
It's been a while since you've seen each other, right?
Right? Right?
Uh...
Chinami, I heard you're having a rough time.
You've got a lot on your plate?
Well, I'm sure you can handle most things,
so I'm not too worried.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Banri told me the other day.
What?
Nothing's going on.
But he said you're moving soon, and next month you'll be living on your own.
Oh! I didn't think it was anything worth telling you.
Don't worry about it.
Hey, Kaga-san, could I have some potato sticks?
Uh, sure.
What's with her?
She's kinda standoffish.
Right?
Don't you think Chinami is being cold to me?
N-Not at all!
She's acting totally normal.
That's what I think.
Don't you think so?
Because you should!
I don't think so.
It's raining.
Seriously?
Why?
Why is everything going wrong?
Yokohama
Machida-Atsugi
10 km
of traffic
Wouldn't it be faster to take side streets?
We can't for a while.
The exit's way ahead.
There's no telling when we'll get there now.
Should we turn back?
But we've come this far.
Yeah.
The rain might stop by the time we get there.
The weather report said it'd be sunny.
Hey, seriously, are we sure one of us isn't cursed?
That's really not...
funny.
I guess we should've turned back, after all.
Yeah.
Are you awake?
Banri, what should I do?
I need to go to the bathroom.
Is it a phantom urge?
No. It's real.
There seems to be a bathroom over there.
Do you have an umbrella?
No.
Me either.
Neither do I.
You're wearing your swimsuit, right?
Yeah.
Huh? Banri?
All right! Let's go!
What?!
You're kidding!
If you go now, I can go with you!
Huh? Huh?
Take it off, take it off, take it off!
Hurry up and take it off!
You've got three more seconds!
Three, two...
Wait a minute.
Underneath my clothes is...
the toxic speedo.
There!
Wait, wait!
I'll go with you!
Go! Sprint!
I'm going to drown!
No!
What are we even doing?
Awesome!
Yay!
"Awesome," nothing.
Stop acting like an observer and come with us.
What?! Hold on!
Not the Okamera!
Sheesh!
And on top of everything, it's cold!
You two must be idiots!
Wh-What is that?
Oh, no!
Banri's not wearing a jockstrap under his swimsuit!
We have no choice!
Let's go, 2D!
Yeah!
No, Mister Tada!
Your outline is clearly visible!
Uncle!
2D!
You did this for me?
Of course we did.
By swiftly taking possession of your dangling bits,
the crime-constituting conditions of embezzlement have been completely met.
Also, why is Yana-san your uncle?
He just is!
What's wrong, Kouko?
Did you wet yourself?
I just slipped, you idiot!
That's the first time she's called me an idiot.
Thanks for the food!
Banri, your ramen looks delicious.
Really?
Look, the Okamera, the Okamera!
Yay!
Whoa! Oka-chan, what was that?!
There it is!
Miss Ultrasonic's weird face!
Here we go!
Look, a shell.
Open wide.
Brain freeze!
Okay, Yana-san. Open wide.
Here, Kouko.
I'm good.
Of course you are.
Brain freeze!
Fireworks!
Yay!
Kaga-san and 2D-kun have a sparkler in each hand!
Okay, let's light this one.
Sounds good!
I'm glad the weather cleared up.
Yeah.
The stars are so beautiful.
I'm starting to feel sleepy.
Yana-san, talk to me while I drive.
If it gets too quiet, I think I really will lose consciousness.
Are you okay?
In that case, do you want me to drive instead?
You have a license?
Yeah.
See?
Are you sure?
It'd be a huge help.
Leave it to me.
You drove all the way here.
It's no wonder you're tired.
Kouko, are you sure you're okay?
Yeah.
You can't be that used to driving.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
I'll ride in the passenger seat, then.
2D-kun, you can sleep in the back.
Yeah, I totally will.
I'm so sleepy, I can't take it.
Okay, everybody. Let's go!
You're a good driver, Kouko.
Aren't I?
Don't worry.
I'll drive really safely.
Everyone's asleep.
That really was fun, though.
I thought we were done for when it started to rain.
I know.
It ended up being so much fun.
I'm glad we got to go to the beach together.
Yeah. Me, too.
As of now, this feels like the best summer of my life.
Surely you're exaggerating.
It's true.
It is.
When are you going to Barcelona?
Next week.
But... I want to stay with you.
We talked about this before.
You should go.
Bring something back for me.
I really do wish I could stay with you.
No, I can't.
I need to keep talking to Kouko.
Wake up!
This can't happen!
I didn't want things to go this far!
No! Not this!
This isn't what I want!
I didn't want this to happen!
Someone, help!
Someone!
Please! Anyone!
Tell him, "You can do it."
Oh...
I'm not supposed to say that kind of thing.
Just press on!
No, no, that's not what I'm getting at
chigau yo mou chigau tte ba
Ah, you still haven't noticed
aa mada kizukanai no ne
Since a couple of hours ago
nisanjikan mo mae kara
I've been dying to grab onto your arm
sono ude ni furetai no ni
I have so many pent-up feelings that I want to let out
sakebitai kimochi wa hora komaru hodo aru no ni
But why? Why can't you take a hint?
dou shite dou shite chitto mo aa satotte kurenai no
Hey
nee
Are you really, really in love with me?
hontou ni hontou ni watashi ni koi shiteru
You can skip the sweet talk
kosobayui kotoba wa iranai
Love me semipermanently
han'eikyuuteki ni aishite yo
I don't care about five thousand years in the future
gosennen go nado kyoumi wa nai
My life's not endless
watashi endoresu de wa nai no
I'll die someday
itsuka wa shinu no yo
Telling me you'll love me forever
eien ni aishiteru yo nante
Won't make me happy
iwarete mo ureshikunai
For now just focus on
mazu wa watashi wo shinu made
Loving me until we die
ai suru koto dake wo kangaete
Wake-up Call
It's not here! It's not here!
I forgot a change of underwear!
What's this?
You forgot your underwear even though I asked about it?
I see. That's not good.
You've got a criminal record.
What's wrong, 2D?!
Are you broken?!