Wake up!
What? What happened?
An accident?
Banri...
Banri!
Banri! Banri!
Kouko...
W-Well, in any case, let's get out.
Yeah.
Come on, Banri.
Kouko!
Wake-up Call
Ah, if I met you in my dream, would I be able to say it?
aa yume no naka de aetara yueru ka na
The sorrows alone scatter down from the sky
nee kanashimi dake sora kara maiochite
That voice torments you to this day
sonna koe ga kimi wo ima de mo kurushimete
Even when I put my hand on yours, I can't get over these feelings
soba de te wo kasanetemo kono omoi wa kienai kedo
When our eyes meet, even if you don't say what you mean
futari me wo awasetara hontou no koto ienakutemo
Your words shine my world brighter than anyone else's
kimi no kotoba dare yori mo sekai wo terashiteru
Next to me, you say "Goodbye" when you mean "I love you"
tonari de kimi wa sayonara wa aishiteru tte sou iu no
I can't be honest
sunao ni narenai
When I'm singing about my loneliness alone
watashi dake kodoku wo utatte mo
I can't smile
egao ni narenai
If you say "Thanks" to mean "I'm in love with you"
arigato wa koi shiteru tte sou iu no
This is love at the end of the world
ai no world's end
Chinami, what's wrong?
Are you hurt?
I-I'm so sorry!
I'm fine.
I just bumped it a little.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
Kaga-san, it's really not a big deal.
But... But...
Oh, right.
Really, I'm fine!
We need to call the police.
Hello?
Excuse me. Um...
There's been an accident.
Are you sure you don't need a tow truck?
I'm sure.
The bumper's just dented.
Ouch...
You fell asleep at the wheel, huh?
Well, I'm glad it wasn't serious.
Keep in mind that you'll have to pay for repairs to the guard rail.
Also, because you're a minor,
we'll have to call your parents.
What's their number?
Can we get in touch with them now?
Dad...
Oh...
Oka-chan got her bandage off?
Yeah.
She's been coming to film club meetings too.
She's worried that she can't get in touch with Kouko.
I've texted and called her numerous times, but...
My mom told me...
that Kouko's family canceled their trip to Barcelona.
Yana-san, are you free today?
Hello.
What was that for?!
I can't stand it when I run into someone and they give me a gloomy look.
What?!
I just pulled an all-nighter.
Don't make that face at me.
That's going overboard!
You've been pretty damn disheartened lately.
Your dark mood's coming through the wall, and it's pissing me off.
I don't know what happened, but get over it already.
It's a pain in my ass.
I'm sorry.
Well, if all else fails, come see one of my concerts again.
I'll let you in for free.
Banri.
Hey.
Sorry. I said we should meet, and I'm the last one here.
Banri!
Oka-chan, your lip is healed?
That's great.
It wasn't a serious injury to begin with.
Do you have work after this?
Yeah, in the evening.
Sorry you guys had to accommodate my schedule.
It's fine.
We had nothing else to do.
We wanted to check out where you work too.
Oh.
You found an apartment?
Yeah.
It's not exactly the dream home I was imagining, though.
The timing forced me to make a quick decision,
and after making several compromises, I'll be moving in this month.
I texted Kaga-san about it too.
She didn't answer?
No.
I see.
Banri, you can't get in touch with her, either?
Nope.
My parents came to Tokyo the other day,
and apparently, they met with Kaga-san's father.
I think they talked about my injury.
Kaga-san's dad came to my place too.
He talked about insurance, car repairs,
and accident reports with my dad.
In any case, he was really apologetic.
You hear people say it a lot.
Something like, "I got in a little accident the other day."
Or whatever.
But are people really saying that about such a grave situation?
Thoughts like that just keep swirling around in my head!
I was actually pretty scared, you know.
One wrong move, and we all might've died.
Kaga-san must've gotten in a lot of trouble.
I'm sure she feels terrible about it too.
What should I do?
It's really my fault.
I knew Kaga-san was just as tired as me,
and I made her drive!
It's my fault.
It only became such a big deal because I got hurt.
I'm the one who's most at fault.
I was sitting in the passenger seat.
I needed to be careful and keep talking to her so she wouldn't fall asleep.
I feel responsible too.
Kouko wasn't used to driving yet.
I should've stopped her.
Let's not look so gloomy!
Anyway, I asked everyone here...
because I wanted to think about what we should do next.
I definitely don't want to break up with Kouko.
I don't want that to happen, either!
No one does!
Of course not.
So, first and foremost, I want to know how Kouko's doing.
Yeah, but if we can't text or call her...
At this point, we should just...
Yana-san, you know where Kouko lives, right?
Y-Yeah.
You have a point.
Should we go?
Yeah!
Don't you have work now, Oka-chan?
Oh, right.
Actually, shouldn't Banri go by himself?
It'd probably be easier for her to talk to you alone.
So this is where Kouko and Yana-san grew up.
Tada-kun?
Pardon the intrusion.
Come on in.
He's very fond of me.
He follows me everywhere.
Did you have work today?
Just in the morning.
I had taken some time off for our vacation, but I gave that up.
Barcelona...
Yes.
Well, Kouko never seemed
interested in going, anyway.
Kouko!
Well, then.
What do you want?
Stay away!
Kouko...
No!
I'm sorry for putting you in danger the other day.
I'm really sorry for scaring you.
Kouko...
No! Don't come near me!
Go away!
Don't look at me!
I don't want to see anyone!
No.
I'm not leaving.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't see anyone.
I don't want anyone to see me.
So... please...
I'm sorry. I really am.
Everyone's been really worried about you.
We all feel responsible for what happened.
None of you are to blame!
That's not it.
It's not like that.
I'm feeling humiliated about myself.
I thought about it.
It's the first time I've given serious thought to how stupid I am.
I thought I could do anything.
I'm an adult now. I'm free.
I can do whatever I want.
And I ended up falling asleep behind the wheel.
One wrong step, and we'd all be dead...
because of me.
But it's not just your faul—
What are you talking about?!
It's completely my fault!
Falling asleep while driving is completely inexcusable!
It's the driver's responsibility!
But I even let my parents handle the fallout.
I didn't even realize how immature I am.
I'm truly...
truly stupid.
I'm too old to be a child.
Why can't I become an adult?
You were a high school student until last spring.
You can't suddenly expect to become an adult.
But I thought I was an adult!
I acted like I was an adult.
I walked around at night,
wore high heels and makeup,
met with the one I love, and drove a car.
I was just pretending to be an adult
with the obvious stupidity of a child.
Because of that, I put everyone in danger.
I'm feeling humiliated about myself.
I can't show my face to them anymore.
Don't say that!
Everyone's worried about you!
No!
Kouko...
I can't.
I need to take responsibility.
I can't even face you anymore.
What?
So I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry!
Does that mean... you won't see me anymore?
What are you talking about?
The accident was just an accident.
Saying you can't face me, you can't do it, you'll just disappear...
That's not taking responsibility!
Do you want to be forgiven?
By whom?
By me?
By everyone?
Will that make you feel better?
Is that why you're saying you'll disappear?
No, that isn't what I wanted to say.
You got in an accident.
You couldn't do anything afterward.
It's okay to feel ashamed about that.
But don't run from that shame.
You have to carry that
humiliation with you and live on!
You can't stop being yourself!
Or else, what?
Are you going to pretend the part of you that you can't accept never existed?
If you get in an accident again,
are you going to say it has nothing to do with your current self and run away again?
Will you start over at your own convenience and leave everyone else behind?
Shut up!
Just shut up!
What are you talking about?!
Are you...
in any place...
to say that?!
Kouko!
I don't...
I don't want to hear that from you, Banri!
Seriously, what are you saying?
What are you saying?!
What? What are you talking about?!
You abandoned everything, didn't you?
You left everything behind and started over.
You haven't accepted your past at all!
I...
I didn't ask for that!
Besides, who told me to forget about it?!
You're the one who cried and threw a fit begging me to not face my past!
What?
What are you saying?
Isn't it true?!
You said your former self was in love with Linda!
What was I supposed to do
when you said that to me?
And stop talking down to me like that!
It started before that.
You never had any intention of accepting your past self!
Isn't that why you abandoned your hometown?
You left your family and friends behind
and cut your beloved Linda-senpai out of your life!
And you're living now like it's no big deal!
You're doing it all to yourself!
And next, you're going to cut me out!
What?
If you get in an accident and lose your memories again,
it'll be my turn to be abandoned, won't it?
Isn't that right?
It is, isn't it?!
Wh-What are you talking about?
I saw it in a dream.
A dream?
A dream in which you
abandoned me and ran away.
I had a dream about it!
A dream?
You're saying this because of a dream?
I'm being yelled at and hit... because of a dream?
Don't laugh!
I'm not laughing.
Banri...
I'm terrible, aren't I?
I can't...
sleep at all.
Whenever I'm about to, I have a dream,
a dream of driving a car.
I'm driving down a freeway.
You're in the passenger seat.
Partway down the road,
there's a sign that says, "get off."
I get off by myself, and when I turn around,
the car drives away with you in it.
I can't chase after it and just watch it drive away.
The thing is, I feel like I've been having this dream for a while.
You'll leave me behind.
I believe that day will come eventually.
I'm always afraid.
Does that mean you're worried I'll lose my memories again?
Yeah.
If you leave me behind,
I really don't know what I'll do!
I don't know what I'll do, or how I'll live.
So don't leave me.
If you go somewhere, take me with you.
Okay.
If you have that dream again,
do your best not to get out of the car.
Okay.
If you can do that, I'll do my best too.
It's true that I've left a lot of people behind.
I've desperately tried to abandon the parts of myself I couldn't accept.
I've been saying, "That's not me,"
and denying who I am, always running.
Honestly, I wasn't even looking at anyone else.
But I won't run anymore.
Banri...
Accident or amnesia,
you can't rewind your life and start again.
If you struggle, you'll just hurt yourself, and the people around you.
So I...
Huh?
What?
Banri... sorry for earlier.
I'm sorry for everything.
I want to be with you.
I want to be with you because I love you.
That's all there is to it!
K-Kouko!
I'll do my best.
I'll believe you'll do your best too.
I love you, Banri.
I really...
I-Is...
my father standing there?
No!
What?
He's not there!
The only one here is the cat!
No!
It's lunchtime, so I was just wondering if you wanted to join me for some ramen!
What?!
You shouldn't lie.
Kouko, he lied to you!
Dad...
I was honest!
But he lied!
Remember that.
I've had enough!
I'm sick of this!
I'm sick of this life!
K-Kouko...
Just leave me!
Wait! Banri!
No honorific?!
I hate everyone!
Make this for me.
Are you out of your mind?!
Yes.
How can you eat in this situation?!
Why?
It's all we can do.
In these situations, we just have to act normal.
Both of you, get out already!
Where's your kitchen?
Downstairs!
Got it!
Is it ready?
Y-Yeah.
Thanks for the meal.
I'm sick of this.
No more.
I wonder if she's having that dream again.
Don't get out.
Hang in there.
No, no, that's not what I'm getting at
chigau yo mou chigau tte ba
Ah, you still haven't noticed
aa mada kizukanai no ne
Since a couple of hours ago
nisanjikan mo mae kara
I've been dying to grab onto your arm
sono ude ni furetai no ni
I have so many pent-up feelings that I want to let out
sakebitai kimochi wa hora komaru hodo aru no ni
But why? Why can't you take a hint?
dou shite dou shite chitto mo aa satotte kurenai no
Hey
nee
Are you really, really in love with me?
hontou ni hontou ni watashi ni koi shiteru
You can skip the sweet talk
kosobayui kotoba wa iranai
Love me semipermanently
han'eikyuuteki ni aishite yo
I don't care about five thousand years in the future
gosennen go nado kyoumi wa nai
My life's not endless
watashi endoresu de wa nai no
I'll die someday
itsuka wa shinu no yo
Telling me you'll love me forever
eien ni aishiteru yo nante
Won't make me happy
iwarete mo ureshikunai
For now just focus on
mazu wa watashi wo shinu made
Loving me until we die
ai suru koto dake wo kangaete
Return to Yesterday
Wow, it's my first time being in Kouko's room!
It smells like Kouko!
The pillow being flung around smells like Kouko too!