They're finished!
Let me see.
They're finally here?
Hurry up.
They're so cool.
Nice.
My name is missing.
Why is mine the only one missing?
Our graduation shirts are supposed to stay with us for the rest of our lives.
Do they all hate me?
They're so cool.
Or something...
The material's pretty nice.
The color's not bad, either.
Banri?
What's wrong?
My name...
Your name?
My name is missing!
It's true.
Banri's name is missing!
What? Really?
That's awful.
They'll replace them for free, won't they?
Come on. We'll get them replaced.
Cheer up.
F-For a second, I was afraid it was intentional.
No way.
Just how stupid are you, Banri?
I'm really worried about you.
After we graduate, we won't be together anymore.
Will you be okay?
Can you make it on your own?
Graduation Cer
Whew!
That was exciting.
Everyone cried way too much.
It made me cry too.
Banri, good luck on your entrance exams next year.
I'm going to Tokyo,
but I'll help you study when I come back.
Yes or no.
Huh?
I want you to tell me.
This will be the first and last time.
I want a simple answer.
I don't want to be away from you.
I want to be with you all the time.
I love you.
If you feel the same way,
I'll go to prep school in Tokyo.
Yes or no.
Tell me your answer.
Could you wait a little bit?
Can I think about it overnight?
Fine.
I'll wait for you on the usual bridge tomorrow.
In high school, I was in love with Linda.
I was serious about her,
but the people around us saw us as siblings or friends.
Linda only thought of me as a friend too.
The same way that Kaga Kouko...
Yes • No
calls Tada Banri her friend now.
hand in hand let's go party night
hand
in
let's
go
par
ty
night
My heart's dancing, and it won't stop
kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
We share so many memories, both happy and sad
naite waratte kimi to no kioku
I'll never forget them
zutto wasurenai
I'm supposed to find the real me and stuff
hontou no jibun wa doko ni iru to ka
Coming of age isn't easy
otona ni naru tte taihen de
But I guess I can forget about that for now
ima wa wasuretemo ii ka na
Because the night is waiting
yoru ga matte iru kara
When I think about seeing you, I get so excited
kokoro wo hazumase aeru toki wo
As I jump around in anticipation
hashagi mawareba
I might just notice the feelings inside me
tsutaetai omoi ni ima
That I want to get across to you
kizuiteshimaisou de
Even if we're afraid of the past and the future
kako to mirai osorete ite mo
We can't move on with nothing behind us
karappo no mama ja ugokenai
It's all right as long as we have fun
tanoshimeba it's all right
it's
all
right
Let's start
hajimeyou
ha
ji
me
you
When I forget everything I don't like
ya na koto zenbu wasurete
And dance through the night with you
kimi to issho ni odoriakaseba
I become a more wonderful person
motto suteki na jibun ni nareru
I can feel it
sonna ki ga suru no
let's get together
let's
ther
Our golden time will never end
owaranai golden time
time
As we pull each other closer
gyutto chikazuku kimi to no kyori wa
Not too close, not too far
tsukazu hanarezu
Even if we have to take the long way to get there
mawarimichi de mo
I'll cherish every second
taisetsu ni shitai
They fit perfectly!
My feet feel so light!
They fit someone?
They didn't fit any of us.
Could he be Cinderella?
Are his feet the ones that fit the glass sneakers?
This kid with the aura of a seedy and
unpopular comedian saturating his genes?
Terrifying!
So where did these come from?
Someone wants to sell those sneakers.
She said she'd sell them for five thousand yen if they fit.
Brand new and unused.
Normally, they'd cost over twenty thousand.
Twenty thousand...
I'll buy them!
Ah, Tada-kun! Hey!
Kaga-san...
and Linda-senpai.
Linda, Tada Banri said he'd buy these sneakers.
Really?
Linda-senpai, are these yours?
Yeah.
How do they fit?
U-Uh, right. Perfectly!
Really? Okay, then.
For Tada Banri, they're free.
You're Freebie Banri, after all.
Seriously?
That's not fair.
Well, he's our junior.
A sweet, precious first-year.
I can't take his money.
But...
They weren't my size, but it was love at first sight.
It was an impulse buy.
You should wear them instead.
Okay.
Thank you, then.
All right!
Hey.
Are you guys Awa dancing?
Senpai.
Long time, no see.
They're fourth-years.
The former club leaders.
How's the job hunting going?
Have you found anything already?
We're just getting started, you idiot.
None of us have any offers yet.
It's not easy.
You'd better prepare yourselves.
Anyway, did you bring us any goodies?
Don't worry.
We brought something.
You need these for the Awa dance, right?
Yeah, but...
The fourth-years pooled
their money to make these.
He designed them.
Come on, smile!
Don't you like them?
No.
I hate you guys!
Tada-kun, did something
happen with Linda-senpai?
Huh?
Things just seemed a little weird earlier.
Why would Linda-senpai and I...
You're imagining things.
Oh?
If something is bothering you, feel free to tell me about it.
After all, we're friends.
Yeah.
Friends...
Banri, Kaga-san!
I finally found you!
Okachi Nami.
You split it up wrong.
It's not Okachi.
It's Oka Chinami.
Say, why don't you come to our welcoming party today?
We're going to have a blast with all of our friends.
I'm the one who suggested it, so I'm organizing it.
Yeah? Where—
I'm not going!
There's no way I'd go!
What?
Tada-kun, I'm off to class.
I knew she'd turn me down.
Why do you want Kaga-san to go so badly?
Most people wouldn't, considering what happened the other day.
You think so?
Unless you're actually a really malicious person.
Huh?
Maybe you invited Kaga-san because you hate her,
and you're planning to chew her up and swallow her,
like a Rafflesia enshrined deep in the jungle.
What? Why would I do that?
What kind of creature would I be?
Well, I just...
There's something I find
irresistible about Kaga-san.
Not to mention she's really pretty.
She's definitely really pretty.
Yana's missing out.
It must be hard to be ignored by the person you love.
Since they attend the same college, they can't avoid each other.
Are you sure Kaga-san won't come?
Well, I'll try inviting her.
Izakaya
Golden Time
I'm so happy you're all here!
This will be a great party!
I'm your organizer and host, Oka Chinami!
Cheers!
Wow.
So these are all Oka-chan's friends.
There are some older students too.
Just how many people does she know?
So what are you doing here?
My friend Tada-kun convinced me to come.
He said we should dive into all kinds of new things.
Aren't your friends from the Film Club here?
Why don't you go hang out with them?
Don't order me around.
L-Look, why don't you try to get along just for today?
What's this about?
It's complicated.
Don't tell me...
It's hell in there!
We didn't see anything!
Why don't you learn from Chinami?
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm saying you should change seats and try talking to different people.
You still don't have any other friends, do you?
I do!
The seniors in the Festival Club are nice to me.
Linda-senpai is really nice.
I don't need to copy Miss Ultrasonic.
Don't call her that!
You'd never be able to gather this many people!
Well, neither could you!
Besides, you're only pretending
to like Miss Ultrasonic to spite me!
That's not true at all!
It's definitely true!
I don't know what happened,
You just think it will hurt me!
but shouldn't we separate them?
It has nothing to do with you.
Yeah.
Just how overconfident are you, anyway?
H-Hey, Kaga-san...
You'll never be able to confess your feelings to her.
Can you—
You don't have the resolve!
Don't assume I can't!
If I'm wrong, why don't you prove it?
Oh, I will.
Hey, Chinami!
Oh, Yana!
And Kaga-san, thank you for coming!
I'm so happy.
Chinami.
Yes?
I love you.
I want to go out with you!
What?
I love you.
I want to go out with you!
What?
Don't be stupid.
He's done it now.
What should we do?
Don't ask me.
K-Kaga-san?!
H-He really did it!
Ladies, I have a tribute for you!
Tada Banri, you're here?
Tribute? What tribute?
He's so hot!
Thank you!
Take her too.
Ah! It's that girl!
Her skin is so smooth and beautiful!
It looks delicious!
She's so cute that I just want to torment her.
You're a monster, Banri.
Am I?
He sprung it on you.
I know!
Ta-da!
It's the Oka Chinami camera!
The Okamera for short!
I've been filming everyone with this.
I'd like to put it all together
into a single film eventually.
Oh, right. You're in the Film Club.
This is the only time we'll be new students at a university.
These moments are precious.
Anyway, say something funny.
Uh... um...
I'm 2D-kun, Sato Takaya.
I'm nearsighted.
Next, Banri!
I-I'm Tada Banri.
I'm alive, I guess.
I can't think of anything funny!
That was fun.
Can I have your email address?
The Tea Club's going out for a second round.
This way if you're coming!
I don't think I can.
They met the same fate we did.
Pedestrians and
Bicycles Only
Come on, Kaga-san. Walk.
I've got it.
Come on, catch me.
Pedestrians and
Bicycles Only
Seriously, that's enough!
I don't feel so good.
I'm going to be sick.
Do it in here.
Let's go home.
Kaga-san, please. Take a taxi.
I want to have more fun.
You're my friend. Come with me.
It's late, and I don't have any money.
Then let's go to your place.
Let's talk all night...
about friendship and youth.
Let's badmouth Mitsuo too.
Can we stop?
What?
I don't want to be friends anymore.
Okay?
Say "Yes."
I don't want to be friends with you anymore.
Yana-san is still all you think about.
Have you thought about how it makes me feel to see that?
It's too hard for me to be with you.
I'm not your friend anymore.
Okay?
Do you still want to be friends with me?
Is it because you feel
comfortable being around me?
Because I understand your
awkward and useless self...
and still like you?
Quit acting so spoiled.
When you rejected me,
you lost the right to want those things!
I shouldn't have tried to be your friend.
I can't associate with you anymore.
I don't want to!
Wait.
I won't wait.
I won't wait for anyone anymore.
Tada-kun...
I...
She's riding.
Tada-kun, don't do this!
Please, listen to me!
No.
Goodbye.
Clean up!
The next group is coming in to use this room.
Let's clean this place up and get out!
Okay!
What's wrong, Tada Banri?
You seem down today.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Did you have a fight with Kouko-chan?
Okay.
Linda, we're leaving.
Okay!
Kouko-chan was looking at you.
You shouldn't make your girlfriend so sad.
Linda-senpai, do you think she and I are dating?
Well, you're so close.
We're not.
I see.
How can she act like she doesn't know anything?
Oh, I know.
You're more than friends but not dating yet?
What about you, Linda-senpai?
What... about me?
Don't you have a boyfriend?
Maybe someone you've been dating since high school?
Even if I ask...
I'm sure you'll tell me you don't!
No one. You'll say there's no one!
You've erased him!
How could you do that?
Don't you think it's cruel?
Don't you feel bad for me...
for the old Tada Banri?!
I'm doing the same thing.
I act like I don't know any of them.
Not Linda-senpai, nor my parents, nor anyone I knew.
The same goes for me.
Banri.
Banri!
Banri, wait!
I'm the worst.
Banri. Banri!
I don't know that name!
Who is that?!
You were like a bomb.
One wrong move, and I might have lost you again.
I didn't know what to do.
I forgot everything.
I'm afraid!
I'm so afraid, I can't help myself!
I don't know what I'd do if it was my fault.
Your fault?
The day after graduation,
I went to tell you my answer.
But I didn't make it in time.
Is it my fault?
Is it my fault because I wasn't there in time?
It can't end like that.
It can't!
Meeting Hall
Linda-senpa—
Tada-kun?
Hey...
What's wrong?
Did something happen with Linda-senpai?
The answer...
The answer is "yes"!
Tada-kun, wait!
No!
Why are you running?
Please wait!
Tada-kun!
Let me borrow that!
I don't know where this path leads.
I don't know which paths I've chosen until now.
Right and left, yes and no.
We must continuously choose which path to take.
Yes and no are tangled in an endless web,
and I don't know which path is the right one.
If I did...
If I could correctly trace back all of Tada Banri's decisions until now...
I'd find Linda-senpai there.
But...
I can't turn back.
I can't find the past I've lost.
If I fall again...
can I do everything over?
What's the answer?
Tada-kun!
I caught you.
K-Kaga-san?
Don't run anymore.
Don't go where I can't reach you!
Stay with me forever.
What?
I love you, Tada-kun.
My favorite drink, a sweet caffè latte, in one hand
katate ni wa amaku shita okiniiri no kaferate
I enjoy the scent of love with a smile
hohoenda shunkan ni koi no kaori
I want to dress up perfectly
kanpeki ni kimetai no
I pick out a cherry-colored dress
cherii iro no wanpiisu
It looks neat and charming
sawayaka de tokimeite
Now I can go see you
kimi e isogou
Watch out for the sweet trap
ki wo tsukete amai wana
Yes, I'll whisper it in your ear
yes sasayaite ageru kara
Ah, I can't wait to see you
ah machidooshii kedo
What kind of smile should I greet you with?
donna egao de aeba ii
pretty love pretty love
You're so lovely
kimi ga itoshikute
under the sky under sunshine
Let's hold hands
te wo tsunagou
I can't bring myself to be honest, so take my hand
sunao ni narenai sonna watashi no te wo
And pull it toward you
hippatte ite ne
Masquerade
Ta-da! It's the Okalesia!
Ugh, it's her.
I'll eat anything.
I'm a healthy girl.
Huh? The flower under me?
It's a carnivorous flower.
Oka-chan's being eaten!