Linda-senpai.
Huh?
Do you want to go back?
To the place where I used to be.
I...
I want to go back!
What did I just say?
Wow, you just fell asleep for a second.
Fell asleep?
Looks like you should get to bed.
Lack of sleep isn't good for you.
You'll become oversensitive
and think things you shouldn't.
Good night, Tada Banri.
I still love Linda.
With You Again
If I can, I want to be with Linda forever.
hand in hand let's go party night
hand
in
let's
go
par
ty
night
kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
My heart's dancing, and it won't stop
naite waratte kimi to no kioku
We share so many memories, both happy and sad
zutto wasurenai
I'll never forget them
hontou no jibun wa doko ni iru to ka
I'm supposed to find the real me and stuff
otona ni naru tte taihen de
Coming of age isn't easy
ima wa wasuretemo ii ka na
But I guess I can forget about that for now
yoru ga matte iru kara
Because the night is waiting
kokoro wo hazumase aeru toki wo
When I think about seeing you, I get so excited
hashagi mawareba
As I jump around in anticipation
tsutaetai omoi ni ima
I might just notice the feelings inside me
kizuiteshimaisou de
That I want to get across to you
kako to mirai osorete ite mo
Even if we're afraid of the past and the future
karappo no mama ja ugokenai
We can't move on with nothing behind us
tanoshimeba it's all right
It's all right as long as we have fun
it's
all
right
hajimeyou
Let's start
ha
ji
me
you
ya na koto zenbu wasurete
When I forget everything I don't like
kimi to issho ni odoriakaseba
And dance through the night with you
motto suteki na jibun ni nareru
I become a more wonderful person
sonna ki ga suru no
I can feel it
let's get together
let's
ther
owaranai golden time
Our golden time will never end
time
gyutto chikazuku kimi to no kyori wa
As we pull each other closer
tsukazu hanarezu
Not too close, not too far
mawarimichi de mo
Even if we have to take the long way to get there
taisetsu ni shitai
I'll cherish every second
Kaga-san, wait.
Banri, Kaga-san and I are leaving now.
Okay.
Thanks for waiting.
Kaga-san, you don't look well.
Really?
What? Kaga-san's sick?
Yeah.
She wanted me to tell you she didn't think she'd make it to class today.
I see.
Well, I've got class.
Sure, thanks.
No subject
How's your cold?
Sending Message
In our discussion of natural law,
Kaga-san didn't come to class for a while after that.
we cannot ignore the existence of
an English man named Jeremy Bentham...
According to her texts,
her condition worsened, and she felt terrible.
How's your cold?
Sending Message
I didn't get to see Kaga-san over the weekend, either.
Then, on Monday...
Tada-kun!
Kaga-san!
Good morning, Tada-kun.
I'm sorry I couldn't come meet you today.
That's fine.
Are you sure you're okay?
You still look a little sick.
I can't stay home forever.
We have practice with the Festival Club today.
Kaga-san, you really shouldn't force yourself.
I'm fine.
Anyway, you should get changed.
Yeah, but...
You seem to be getting along well.
We heard you're dating.
I saw you holding hands
and walking together the other day.
Didn't you say you were just friends?
I'm sorry!
I wasn't lying!
Okay, okay, okay.
Stop!
Don't bully the cute little underclassman.
Yeah, yeah.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Hey!
Our outfits are here!
These are for the guys,
and those are for the ladies.
Try them on.
Those are loaners, so make sure you don't lose them.
Kaga-san?
Take good care of them.
Let's go.
It might be a little tight.
Lose some weight before the performance.
Where did Kaga-san go?
It looks good on you!
We look pretty nice in these.
Kouko-chan, you look great.
It's so cute.
Thank you.
Kaga-san, you look great in Japanese clothes too.
I'm impressed!
Thanks.
Kaga-san, there's something wrong with you.
Maybe you're still sick.
Kaga-san, do you need a towel?
I haven't used this today, so it's still clean.
Kaga-san?
Do you love me?
Wh-Why?
Of course I love you.
Really? You actually... love me?
Will you love me forever?
When will you leave me?
Do you find it annoying that I'm asking you this?
Kaga-san?
Seriously, what's wrong?
Do you still love me?
I don't understand what you're talking about.
Did I do something to you?
I'm...
I'm anxious.
I'm scared.
I keep having negative thoughts.
I want to stop.
I want to be cute for you all the time.
But...
No matter what...
No matter what I do, I feel anxious.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Kaga-san!
I'm really sorry.
It's all my fault.
You don't need to feel anxious.
There's nothing to worry about.
Everything's fine.
It's perfect.
In the summer of my third year of high school,
I comforted Linda in the same way.
The current Banri doesn't remember.
Only I, a ghost, and Linda know.
To battle!
All right! It's time to start running!
Let's burn as hot as the sun!
To battle!
Linda had an older brother.
He coached our high school's soccer team.
Linda and I both called him "Brother."
Brother!
Oh, you guys are here?
Hey! Working hard?
Y-Yes.
You seem to be working hard too.
Yeah.
I'm trying to train them as hard as I can over summer vacation.
We've finished practice, so we're leaving.
Hang in there, Brother.
Yeah!
I'll introduce my fiancée to you sometime.
Okay! Can't wait.
She's beautiful.
She's kind and good at cooking too.
I still can't believe I'm marrying her.
I hope I can meet her soon!
Look forward to it.
To battle!
He's amazing.
He works so hard at coaching,
even though he doesn't get paid.
He's even using his own summer vacation.
Linda?
Banri...
I need to talk to you about something important.
Huh?
An affair?
I saw my brother's fiancée...
leaving another man's apartment.
It must've been something else.
A friend, or maybe a brother.
They kissed when she left.
I haven't told my brother yet.
I have no proof.
I don't think he'd believe me if I told him.
He seems to really love her.
That's why I'm going to get photographic evidence
and destroy their marriage!
What?!
Unless I send the pictures to everyone in both families
and completely ruin her, I won't be satisfied!
I'll make her pay so much in reparations, she won't be able to make a living!
I want her to live a miserable life, branded a cheater,
so she'll be lonely until the day she dies!
Linda...
Am I wrong, Banri?
Am I trying to do something I shouldn't?
I'm really angry right now.
I'm probably not thinking straight.
That's why I want your opinion.
What do you think, Banri?
What would you do?
I...
I don't think you're wrong.
I don't want your brother to marry a woman like her, either.
I'll go with you.
Is that all right?
Banri...
She's here.
That's your brother's fiancée?
Yeah.
Let's go, Linda.
What's wrong?
I thought we were going to catch her in the act.
Just...
Just wait.
What do you want to do?
If we enter the apartment now,
we should be able to get even more damning pictures.
I told you, just wait.
I can't sit back and watch a nice guy
like your brother be betrayed like this.
I know, but let's try to calm down.
Hey.
Did you get a picture of them linking arms on your phone too?
I did.
I did, but we need something more decisive.
Would you erase it?
What?
All pictures
will be erased
have been erased
All pictures
Hey, what are you doing?!
I changed my mind.
Sorry.
What?!
Hey!
I'll wear the mask of an adult.
See you later.
Yeah.
What?
Nana-chan, what a coincidence.
I'd like to talk with you inside your car.
What?
I can't.
I'm busy right now.
Don't run!
What?
Who are you?
If you still want to get married,
please don't do this again.
I'll forget about this.
But please...
please stop.
Don't drive until you've calmed down.
Be careful you don't get in an accident.
Don't turn around.
What?
That guy...
He's been watching us the whole time.
Seriously?
Scary.
I told her not to do it again.
And then?
"I understand."
That's all?
Yeah.
It's better than destroying everything.
As long as I pretend like I don't know anything,
things will work out as they always have.
It'll be like nothing ever happened.
Is that really the right thing?
Well, I don't want to hurt my brother.
I'm afraid of making him sad.
It's for your brother?!
Do you really think pretending nothing happened is what's best for him?
It'll last forever.
She's going to be family.
Can you think of her as your sister-in-law?
Imagine how your parents would feel.
Stop!
Everything you've said is exactly right.
I know!
I may have been wrong.
But I can't help it!
I've already done it!
Besides, you don't need to be so harsh.
Sorry.
I crossed the line.
I've really done it now.
I wonder if I can endure this forever.
My brother's going to live in a lie.
And I'm one of the liars.
I've hurt him.
What should I do?
What can I do?
This isn't good.
I did the wrong thing, didn't I?
What should I do? What should I do?
I...
I... um...
I saw everything.
So...
So you don't have to suffer alone.
I may be unreliable, and I may not be able to do anything,
but I'm here.
I'll always be with you.
I'll never forget.
I'll always be by your side.
When you want to scream or cry, I'll be there.
I'll share your feelings and stay with you.
Even if you think I'm a nuisance,
no matter where you go, I'll find you.
How?
Well...
I'll find a way.
I'll always be listening for your voice.
When the rain falls, when the wind blows...
when the flowers scatter, when shadows loom.
In every sign, I'll search for your voice.
I promise I will.
Really?
Can I really trust you?
I didn't have the confidence to answer her then.
But because of this incident,
my feelings for Linda became so strong
that I couldn't hold them back anymore.
The seasons changed, and winter came.
I was forced to acknowledge my feelings clearly.
Banri.
Linda-senpai.
What are you doing by yourself?
Where's Kouko-chan?
Her cold came back.
She's not coming today.
I see.
She didn't seem to have much energy yesterday.
She rested all weekend.
She was acting weird yesterday.
I'm worried.
Well, well.
So you were sad because you couldn't spend the weekend with your beloved Kouko-chan.
What about you, Linda-senpai?
What did you do this weekend?
Me?
Well, I went home.
Oh, to Shizuoka?
Yeah.
I didn't go home for Golden Week,
and my parents told me to come home now and then.
I'm kind of tired.
Did something happen?
It's nothing serious,
but I saw my big brother again, among other things.
Linda-senpai, you have an older brother?
Well, I need to get to my next class!
Banri, make sure you take good care of Kouko-chan.
Huh?
Always listen for Kouko-chan's voice.
When the rain falls, when the wind blows...
when the flowers scatter, when shadows loom.
In every sign...
search for her voice.
Okay.
Kouko-chan is your girlfriend.
Later.
If I'd looked her in the eye and answered her then,
would things have turned out differently?
Would I have not become a ghost?
Would I still be by Linda's side?
Really?
Can I really trust you?
I should have told her,
"I love you, Linda."
"That's why I want you to trust me."
I should have told her that.
It's too late for regrets.
Linda and I are hopelessly far apart now.
What?
I have a body.
I can touch.
I can move.
I'm not a ghost.
Linda!
katate ni wa amaku shita okiniiri no kaferate
My favorite drink, a sweet caffè latte, in one hand
hohoenda shunkan ni koi no kaori
I enjoy the scent of love with a smile
kanpeki ni kimetai no
I want to dress up perfectly
cherii iro no wanpiisu
I pick out a cherry-colored dress
sawayaka de tokimeite
It looks neat and charming
kimi e isogou
Now I can go see you
ki wo tsukete amai wana
Watch out for the sweet trap
yes sasayaite ageru kara
Yes, I'll whisper it in your ear
ah machidooshii kedo
Ah, I can't wait to see you
donna egao de aeba ii
What kind of smile should I greet you with?
pretty love pretty love
kimi ga itoshikute
You're so lovely
under the sky under sunshine
te wo tsunagou
Let's hold hands
sunao ni narenai sonna watashi no te wo
I can't bring myself to be honest, so take my hand
hippatte ite ne
And pull it toward you
In The Mirror
To battle!
Working hard, Banri?
What? Is that, like...
the Eiffel Tower?
What? It's the Awa dance!
Oh!
Yes, I'm working hard!
I'm Awa dancing!
What did you mean by the Eiffel Tower?
Well, that's, um, it's...
I can't tell you.